pokedex = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "name": "Bulbasaur",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 49,
      "Defense": 49,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bulbasaur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bulbasaur.gif\" alt=\"bulbasaur\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bulbasaur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bulbasaur.gif\" alt=\"bulbasaur\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bulbasaur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bulbasaur.gif\" alt=\"bulbasaur\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bulbasaur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bulbasaur.gif\" alt=\"bulbasaur\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "name": "Ivysaur",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 62,
      "Defense": 63,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ivysaur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ivysaur.gif\" alt=\"ivysaur\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ivysaur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ivysaur.gif\" alt=\"ivysaur\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ivysaur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ivysaur.gif\" alt=\"ivysaur\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ivysaur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ivysaur.gif\" alt=\"ivysaur\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "name": "Venusaur",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 82,
      "Defense": 83,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venusaur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/venusaur.gif\" alt=\"venusaur\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venusaur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/venusaur.gif\" alt=\"venusaur\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venusaur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/venusaur.gif\" alt=\"venusaur\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venusaur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/venusaur.gif\" alt=\"venusaur\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "name": "Charmander",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 39,
      "Attack": 52,
      "Defense": 43,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/charmander\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/charmander.gif\" alt=\"charmander\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/charmander\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/charmander.gif\" alt=\"charmander\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/charmander\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/charmander.gif\" alt=\"charmander\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/charmander\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/charmander.gif\" alt=\"charmander\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "name": "Charmeleon",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 58,
      "Attack": 64,
      "Defense": 58,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/charmeleon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/charmeleon.gif\" alt=\"charmeleon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/charmeleon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/charmeleon.gif\" alt=\"charmeleon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/charmeleon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/charmeleon.gif\" alt=\"charmeleon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/charmeleon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/charmeleon.gif\" alt=\"charmeleon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "name": "Charizard",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 78,
      "Attack": 84,
      "Defense": 78,
      "Sp. Attack": 109,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/charizard\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/charizard.gif\" alt=\"charizard\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/charizard\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/charizard.gif\" alt=\"charizard\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/charizard\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/charizard.gif\" alt=\"charizard\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/charizard\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/charizard.gif\" alt=\"charizard\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "name": "Squirtle",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 44,
      "Attack": 48,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 64,
      "Speed": 43
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/squirtle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/squirtle.gif\" alt=\"squirtle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/squirtle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/squirtle.gif\" alt=\"squirtle\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/squirtle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/squirtle.gif\" alt=\"squirtle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/squirtle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/squirtle.gif\" alt=\"squirtle\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "name": "Wartortle",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 59,
      "Attack": 63,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 58
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wartortle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/wartortle.gif\" alt=\"wartortle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wartortle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/wartortle.gif\" alt=\"wartortle\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wartortle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/wartortle.gif\" alt=\"wartortle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wartortle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/wartortle.gif\" alt=\"wartortle\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "name": "Blastoise",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 79,
      "Attack": 83,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 105,
      "Speed": 78
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blastoise\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/blastoise.gif\" alt=\"blastoise\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blastoise\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/blastoise.gif\" alt=\"blastoise\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blastoise\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/blastoise.gif\" alt=\"blastoise\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blastoise\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/blastoise.gif\" alt=\"blastoise\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "name": "Caterpie",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 20,
      "Sp. Defense": 20,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/caterpie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/caterpie.gif\" alt=\"caterpie\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/caterpie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/caterpie.gif\" alt=\"caterpie\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/caterpie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/caterpie.gif\" alt=\"caterpie\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/caterpie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/caterpie.gif\" alt=\"caterpie\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "name": "Metapod",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 20,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 25,
      "Sp. Defense": 25,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/metapod\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/metapod.gif\" alt=\"metapod\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/metapod\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/metapod.gif\" alt=\"metapod\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/metapod\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/metapod.gif\" alt=\"metapod\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/metapod\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/metapod.gif\" alt=\"metapod\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "name": "Butterfree",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/butterfree\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/butterfree.gif\" alt=\"butterfree\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/butterfree\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/butterfree.gif\" alt=\"butterfree\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/butterfree\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/butterfree.gif\" alt=\"butterfree\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/butterfree\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/butterfree.gif\" alt=\"butterfree\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "name": "Weedle",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 35,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 20,
      "Sp. Defense": 20,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weedle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/weedle.gif\" alt=\"weedle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weedle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/weedle.gif\" alt=\"weedle\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weedle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/weedle.gif\" alt=\"weedle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weedle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/weedle.gif\" alt=\"weedle\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "name": "Kakuna",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 25,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 25,
      "Sp. Defense": 25,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kakuna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kakuna.gif\" alt=\"kakuna\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kakuna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kakuna.gif\" alt=\"kakuna\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kakuna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kakuna.gif\" alt=\"kakuna\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kakuna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kakuna.gif\" alt=\"kakuna\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "name": "Beedrill",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 75
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beedrill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/beedrill.gif\" alt=\"beedrill\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beedrill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/beedrill.gif\" alt=\"beedrill\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beedrill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/beedrill.gif\" alt=\"beedrill\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beedrill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/beedrill.gif\" alt=\"beedrill\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "name": "Pidgey",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 56
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidgey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pidgey.gif\" alt=\"pidgey\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidgey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pidgey.gif\" alt=\"pidgey\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidgey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pidgey.gif\" alt=\"pidgey\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidgey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pidgey.gif\" alt=\"pidgey\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "name": "Pidgeotto",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 63,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 71
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidgeotto\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pidgeotto.gif\" alt=\"pidgeotto\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidgeotto\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pidgeotto.gif\" alt=\"pidgeotto\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidgeotto\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pidgeotto.gif\" alt=\"pidgeotto\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidgeotto\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pidgeotto.gif\" alt=\"pidgeotto\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "name": "Pidgeot",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 83,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 101
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidgeot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pidgeot.gif\" alt=\"pidgeot\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidgeot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pidgeot.gif\" alt=\"pidgeot\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidgeot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pidgeot.gif\" alt=\"pidgeot\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidgeot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pidgeot.gif\" alt=\"pidgeot\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "name": "Rattata",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 56,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 25,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 72
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rattata\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/rattata.gif\" alt=\"rattata\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rattata\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/rattata.gif\" alt=\"rattata\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rattata\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/rattata.gif\" alt=\"rattata\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rattata\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/rattata.gif\" alt=\"rattata\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "name": "Raticate",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 81,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 97
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/raticate\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/raticate.gif\" alt=\"raticate\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/raticate\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/raticate.gif\" alt=\"raticate\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/raticate\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/raticate.gif\" alt=\"raticate\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/raticate\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/raticate.gif\" alt=\"raticate\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "name": "Spearow",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 31,
      "Sp. Defense": 31,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spearow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/spearow.gif\" alt=\"spearow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spearow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/spearow.gif\" alt=\"spearow\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spearow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/spearow.gif\" alt=\"spearow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spearow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/spearow.gif\" alt=\"spearow\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "name": "Fearow",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 61,
      "Sp. Defense": 61,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/fearow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/fearow.gif\" alt=\"fearow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/fearow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/fearow.gif\" alt=\"fearow\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/fearow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/fearow.gif\" alt=\"fearow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/fearow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/fearow.gif\" alt=\"fearow\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "name": "Ekans",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 44,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 54,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ekans\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ekans.gif\" alt=\"ekans\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ekans\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ekans.gif\" alt=\"ekans\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ekans\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ekans.gif\" alt=\"ekans\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ekans\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ekans.gif\" alt=\"ekans\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "name": "Arbok",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 69,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 79,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/arbok\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/arbok.gif\" alt=\"arbok\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/arbok\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/arbok.gif\" alt=\"arbok\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/arbok\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/arbok.gif\" alt=\"arbok\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/arbok\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/arbok.gif\" alt=\"arbok\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "name": "Pikachu",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pikachu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pikachu.gif\" alt=\"pikachu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pikachu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pikachu.gif\" alt=\"pikachu\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pikachu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pikachu.gif\" alt=\"pikachu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pikachu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pikachu.gif\" alt=\"pikachu\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "name": "Raichu",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 110
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/raichu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/raichu.gif\" alt=\"raichu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/raichu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/raichu.gif\" alt=\"raichu\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/raichu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/raichu.gif\" alt=\"raichu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/raichu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/raichu.gif\" alt=\"raichu\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "name": "Sandshrew",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 20,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sandshrew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sandshrew.gif\" alt=\"sandshrew\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sandshrew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sandshrew.gif\" alt=\"sandshrew\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sandshrew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sandshrew.gif\" alt=\"sandshrew\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sandshrew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sandshrew.gif\" alt=\"sandshrew\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "name": "Sandslash",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 110,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sandslash\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sandslash.gif\" alt=\"sandslash\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sandslash\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sandslash.gif\" alt=\"sandslash\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sandslash\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sandslash.gif\" alt=\"sandslash\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sandslash\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sandslash.gif\" alt=\"sandslash\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "name": "Nidoran\u2640",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 47,
      "Defense": 52,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 41
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoran\u2640\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/nidoran\u2640.gif\" alt=\"nidoran\u2640\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoran\u2640\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/nidoran\u2640.gif\" alt=\"nidoran\u2640\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoran\u2640\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/nidoran\u2640.gif\" alt=\"nidoran\u2640\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoran\u2640\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/nidoran\u2640.gif\" alt=\"nidoran\u2640\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "name": "Nidorina",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 62,
      "Defense": 67,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 56
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidorina\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/nidorina.gif\" alt=\"nidorina\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidorina\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/nidorina.gif\" alt=\"nidorina\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidorina\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/nidorina.gif\" alt=\"nidorina\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidorina\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/nidorina.gif\" alt=\"nidorina\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "name": "Nidoqueen",
    "type": [
      "Poison",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 92,
      "Defense": 87,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 76
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoqueen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/nidoqueen.gif\" alt=\"nidoqueen\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoqueen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/nidoqueen.gif\" alt=\"nidoqueen\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoqueen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/nidoqueen.gif\" alt=\"nidoqueen\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoqueen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/nidoqueen.gif\" alt=\"nidoqueen\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "name": "Nidoran\u2642",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 46,
      "Attack": 57,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoran\u2642\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/nidoran\u2642.gif\" alt=\"nidoran\u2642\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoran\u2642\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/nidoran\u2642.gif\" alt=\"nidoran\u2642\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoran\u2642\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/nidoran\u2642.gif\" alt=\"nidoran\u2642\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoran\u2642\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/nidoran\u2642.gif\" alt=\"nidoran\u2642\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "name": "Nidorino",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 61,
      "Attack": 72,
      "Defense": 57,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidorino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/nidorino.gif\" alt=\"nidorino\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidorino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/nidorino.gif\" alt=\"nidorino\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidorino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/nidorino.gif\" alt=\"nidorino\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidorino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/nidorino.gif\" alt=\"nidorino\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "name": "Nidoking",
    "type": [
      "Poison",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 81,
      "Attack": 102,
      "Defense": 77,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/nidoking.gif\" alt=\"nidoking\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/nidoking.gif\" alt=\"nidoking\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/nidoking.gif\" alt=\"nidoking\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nidoking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/nidoking.gif\" alt=\"nidoking\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "name": "Clefairy",
    "type": [
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 48,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/clefairy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/clefairy.gif\" alt=\"clefairy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/clefairy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/clefairy.gif\" alt=\"clefairy\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/clefairy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/clefairy.gif\" alt=\"clefairy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/clefairy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/clefairy.gif\" alt=\"clefairy\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "name": "Clefable",
    "type": [
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 73,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/clefable\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/clefable.gif\" alt=\"clefable\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/clefable\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/clefable.gif\" alt=\"clefable\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/clefable\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/clefable.gif\" alt=\"clefable\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/clefable\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/clefable.gif\" alt=\"clefable\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "name": "Vulpix",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 38,
      "Attack": 41,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vulpix\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/vulpix.gif\" alt=\"vulpix\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vulpix\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/vulpix.gif\" alt=\"vulpix\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vulpix\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/vulpix.gif\" alt=\"vulpix\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vulpix\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/vulpix.gif\" alt=\"vulpix\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "name": "Ninetales",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 73,
      "Attack": 76,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 81,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ninetales\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ninetales.gif\" alt=\"ninetales\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ninetales\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ninetales.gif\" alt=\"ninetales\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ninetales\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ninetales.gif\" alt=\"ninetales\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ninetales\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ninetales.gif\" alt=\"ninetales\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "name": "Jigglypuff",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 115,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 20,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 25,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jigglypuff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/jigglypuff.gif\" alt=\"jigglypuff\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jigglypuff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/jigglypuff.gif\" alt=\"jigglypuff\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jigglypuff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/jigglypuff.gif\" alt=\"jigglypuff\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jigglypuff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/jigglypuff.gif\" alt=\"jigglypuff\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "name": "Wigglytuff",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 140,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wigglytuff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/wigglytuff.gif\" alt=\"wigglytuff\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wigglytuff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/wigglytuff.gif\" alt=\"wigglytuff\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wigglytuff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/wigglytuff.gif\" alt=\"wigglytuff\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wigglytuff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/wigglytuff.gif\" alt=\"wigglytuff\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "name": "Zubat",
    "type": [
      "Poison",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zubat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/zubat.gif\" alt=\"zubat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zubat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/zubat.gif\" alt=\"zubat\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zubat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/zubat.gif\" alt=\"zubat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zubat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/zubat.gif\" alt=\"zubat\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "name": "Golbat",
    "type": [
      "Poison",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golbat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/golbat.gif\" alt=\"golbat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golbat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/golbat.gif\" alt=\"golbat\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golbat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/golbat.gif\" alt=\"golbat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golbat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/golbat.gif\" alt=\"golbat\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "name": "Oddish",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/oddish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/oddish.gif\" alt=\"oddish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/oddish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/oddish.gif\" alt=\"oddish\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/oddish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/oddish.gif\" alt=\"oddish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/oddish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/oddish.gif\" alt=\"oddish\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "name": "Gloom",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gloom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gloom.gif\" alt=\"gloom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gloom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gloom.gif\" alt=\"gloom\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gloom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gloom.gif\" alt=\"gloom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gloom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gloom.gif\" alt=\"gloom\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "name": "Vileplume",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 110,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vileplume\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/vileplume.gif\" alt=\"vileplume\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vileplume\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/vileplume.gif\" alt=\"vileplume\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vileplume\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/vileplume.gif\" alt=\"vileplume\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vileplume\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/vileplume.gif\" alt=\"vileplume\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "name": "Paras",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 25
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/paras\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/paras.gif\" alt=\"paras\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/paras\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/paras.gif\" alt=\"paras\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/paras\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/paras.gif\" alt=\"paras\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/paras\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/paras.gif\" alt=\"paras\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "name": "Parasect",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/parasect\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/parasect.gif\" alt=\"parasect\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/parasect\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/parasect.gif\" alt=\"parasect\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/parasect\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/parasect.gif\" alt=\"parasect\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/parasect\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/parasect.gif\" alt=\"parasect\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "name": "Venonat",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venonat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/venonat.gif\" alt=\"venonat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venonat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/venonat.gif\" alt=\"venonat\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venonat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/venonat.gif\" alt=\"venonat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venonat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/venonat.gif\" alt=\"venonat\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "name": "Venomoth",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venomoth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/venomoth.gif\" alt=\"venomoth\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venomoth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/venomoth.gif\" alt=\"venomoth\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venomoth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/venomoth.gif\" alt=\"venomoth\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venomoth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/venomoth.gif\" alt=\"venomoth\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "name": "Diglett",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 10,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 25,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/diglett\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/diglett.gif\" alt=\"diglett\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/diglett\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/diglett.gif\" alt=\"diglett\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/diglett\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/diglett.gif\" alt=\"diglett\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/diglett\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/diglett.gif\" alt=\"diglett\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "name": "Dugtrio",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 120
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dugtrio\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dugtrio.gif\" alt=\"dugtrio\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dugtrio\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dugtrio.gif\" alt=\"dugtrio\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dugtrio\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dugtrio.gif\" alt=\"dugtrio\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dugtrio\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dugtrio.gif\" alt=\"dugtrio\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "name": "Meowth",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meowth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/meowth.gif\" alt=\"meowth\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meowth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/meowth.gif\" alt=\"meowth\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meowth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/meowth.gif\" alt=\"meowth\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meowth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/meowth.gif\" alt=\"meowth\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "name": "Persian",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 115
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/persian\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/persian.gif\" alt=\"persian\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/persian\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/persian.gif\" alt=\"persian\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/persian\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/persian.gif\" alt=\"persian\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/persian\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/persian.gif\" alt=\"persian\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "name": "Psyduck",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 52,
      "Defense": 48,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/psyduck\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/psyduck.gif\" alt=\"psyduck\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/psyduck\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/psyduck.gif\" alt=\"psyduck\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/psyduck\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/psyduck.gif\" alt=\"psyduck\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/psyduck\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/psyduck.gif\" alt=\"psyduck\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "name": "Golduck",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 82,
      "Defense": 78,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golduck\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/golduck.gif\" alt=\"golduck\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golduck\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/golduck.gif\" alt=\"golduck\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golduck\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/golduck.gif\" alt=\"golduck\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golduck\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/golduck.gif\" alt=\"golduck\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "name": "Mankey",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mankey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mankey.gif\" alt=\"mankey\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mankey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mankey.gif\" alt=\"mankey\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mankey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mankey.gif\" alt=\"mankey\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mankey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mankey.gif\" alt=\"mankey\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "name": "Primeape",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/primeape\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/primeape.gif\" alt=\"primeape\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/primeape\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/primeape.gif\" alt=\"primeape\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/primeape\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/primeape.gif\" alt=\"primeape\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/primeape\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/primeape.gif\" alt=\"primeape\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "name": "Growlithe",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/growlithe\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/growlithe.gif\" alt=\"growlithe\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/growlithe\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/growlithe.gif\" alt=\"growlithe\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/growlithe\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/growlithe.gif\" alt=\"growlithe\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/growlithe\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/growlithe.gif\" alt=\"growlithe\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "name": "Arcanine",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 110,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/arcanine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/arcanine.gif\" alt=\"arcanine\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/arcanine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/arcanine.gif\" alt=\"arcanine\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/arcanine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/arcanine.gif\" alt=\"arcanine\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/arcanine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/arcanine.gif\" alt=\"arcanine\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "name": "Poliwag",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poliwag\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/poliwag.gif\" alt=\"poliwag\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poliwag\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/poliwag.gif\" alt=\"poliwag\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poliwag\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/poliwag.gif\" alt=\"poliwag\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poliwag\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/poliwag.gif\" alt=\"poliwag\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "name": "Poliwhirl",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poliwhirl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/poliwhirl.gif\" alt=\"poliwhirl\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poliwhirl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/poliwhirl.gif\" alt=\"poliwhirl\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poliwhirl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/poliwhirl.gif\" alt=\"poliwhirl\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poliwhirl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/poliwhirl.gif\" alt=\"poliwhirl\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "name": "Poliwrath",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poliwrath\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/poliwrath.gif\" alt=\"poliwrath\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poliwrath\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/poliwrath.gif\" alt=\"poliwrath\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poliwrath\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/poliwrath.gif\" alt=\"poliwrath\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poliwrath\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/poliwrath.gif\" alt=\"poliwrath\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "name": "Abra",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 25,
      "Attack": 20,
      "Defense": 15,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/abra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/abra.gif\" alt=\"abra\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/abra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/abra.gif\" alt=\"abra\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/abra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/abra.gif\" alt=\"abra\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/abra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/abra.gif\" alt=\"abra\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "name": "Kadabra",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 35,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 120,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 105
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kadabra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kadabra.gif\" alt=\"kadabra\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kadabra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kadabra.gif\" alt=\"kadabra\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kadabra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kadabra.gif\" alt=\"kadabra\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kadabra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kadabra.gif\" alt=\"kadabra\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "name": "Alakazam",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 135,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 120
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/alakazam\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/alakazam.gif\" alt=\"alakazam\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/alakazam\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/alakazam.gif\" alt=\"alakazam\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/alakazam\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/alakazam.gif\" alt=\"alakazam\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/alakazam\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/alakazam.gif\" alt=\"alakazam\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "name": "Machop",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/machop\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/machop.gif\" alt=\"machop\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/machop\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/machop.gif\" alt=\"machop\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/machop\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/machop.gif\" alt=\"machop\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/machop\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/machop.gif\" alt=\"machop\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "name": "Machoke",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/machoke\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/machoke.gif\" alt=\"machoke\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/machoke\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/machoke.gif\" alt=\"machoke\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/machoke\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/machoke.gif\" alt=\"machoke\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/machoke\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/machoke.gif\" alt=\"machoke\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "name": "Machamp",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/machamp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/machamp.gif\" alt=\"machamp\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/machamp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/machamp.gif\" alt=\"machamp\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/machamp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/machamp.gif\" alt=\"machamp\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/machamp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/machamp.gif\" alt=\"machamp\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "name": "Bellsprout",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bellsprout\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bellsprout.gif\" alt=\"bellsprout\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bellsprout\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bellsprout.gif\" alt=\"bellsprout\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bellsprout\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bellsprout.gif\" alt=\"bellsprout\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bellsprout\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bellsprout.gif\" alt=\"bellsprout\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "name": "Weepinbell",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weepinbell\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/weepinbell.gif\" alt=\"weepinbell\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weepinbell\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/weepinbell.gif\" alt=\"weepinbell\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weepinbell\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/weepinbell.gif\" alt=\"weepinbell\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weepinbell\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/weepinbell.gif\" alt=\"weepinbell\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "name": "Victreebel",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/victreebel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/victreebel.gif\" alt=\"victreebel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/victreebel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/victreebel.gif\" alt=\"victreebel\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/victreebel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/victreebel.gif\" alt=\"victreebel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/victreebel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/victreebel.gif\" alt=\"victreebel\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "name": "Tentacool",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tentacool\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tentacool.gif\" alt=\"tentacool\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tentacool\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tentacool.gif\" alt=\"tentacool\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tentacool\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tentacool.gif\" alt=\"tentacool\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tentacool\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tentacool.gif\" alt=\"tentacool\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 73,
    "name": "Tentacruel",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 120,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tentacruel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tentacruel.gif\" alt=\"tentacruel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tentacruel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tentacruel.gif\" alt=\"tentacruel\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tentacruel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tentacruel.gif\" alt=\"tentacruel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tentacruel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tentacruel.gif\" alt=\"tentacruel\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "name": "Geodude",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/geodude\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/geodude.gif\" alt=\"geodude\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/geodude\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/geodude.gif\" alt=\"geodude\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/geodude\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/geodude.gif\" alt=\"geodude\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/geodude\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/geodude.gif\" alt=\"geodude\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 75,
    "name": "Graveler",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 115,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/graveler\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/graveler.gif\" alt=\"graveler\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/graveler\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/graveler.gif\" alt=\"graveler\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/graveler\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/graveler.gif\" alt=\"graveler\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/graveler\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/graveler.gif\" alt=\"graveler\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 76,
    "name": "Golem",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 130,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/golem.gif\" alt=\"golem\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/golem.gif\" alt=\"golem\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/golem.gif\" alt=\"golem\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/golem.gif\" alt=\"golem\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 77,
    "name": "Ponyta",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ponyta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ponyta.gif\" alt=\"ponyta\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ponyta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ponyta.gif\" alt=\"ponyta\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ponyta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ponyta.gif\" alt=\"ponyta\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ponyta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ponyta.gif\" alt=\"ponyta\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 78,
    "name": "Rapidash",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 105
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rapidash\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/rapidash.gif\" alt=\"rapidash\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rapidash\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/rapidash.gif\" alt=\"rapidash\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rapidash\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/rapidash.gif\" alt=\"rapidash\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rapidash\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/rapidash.gif\" alt=\"rapidash\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 79,
    "name": "Slowpoke",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 15
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slowpoke\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/slowpoke.gif\" alt=\"slowpoke\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slowpoke\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/slowpoke.gif\" alt=\"slowpoke\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slowpoke\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/slowpoke.gif\" alt=\"slowpoke\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slowpoke\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/slowpoke.gif\" alt=\"slowpoke\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 80,
    "name": "Slowbro",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 110,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slowbro\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/slowbro.gif\" alt=\"slowbro\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slowbro\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/slowbro.gif\" alt=\"slowbro\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slowbro\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/slowbro.gif\" alt=\"slowbro\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slowbro\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/slowbro.gif\" alt=\"slowbro\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 81,
    "name": "Magnemite",
    "type": [
      "Electric",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 25,
      "Attack": 35,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magnemite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/magnemite.gif\" alt=\"magnemite\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magnemite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/magnemite.gif\" alt=\"magnemite\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magnemite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/magnemite.gif\" alt=\"magnemite\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magnemite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/magnemite.gif\" alt=\"magnemite\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 82,
    "name": "Magneton",
    "type": [
      "Electric",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 120,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magneton\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/magneton.gif\" alt=\"magneton\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magneton\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/magneton.gif\" alt=\"magneton\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magneton\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/magneton.gif\" alt=\"magneton\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magneton\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/magneton.gif\" alt=\"magneton\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "name": "Farfetch'd",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 52,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 58,
      "Sp. Defense": 62,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/farfetch'd\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/farfetch'd.gif\" alt=\"farfetch'd\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/farfetch'd\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/farfetch'd.gif\" alt=\"farfetch'd\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/farfetch'd\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/farfetch'd.gif\" alt=\"farfetch'd\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/farfetch'd\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/farfetch'd.gif\" alt=\"farfetch'd\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "name": "Doduo",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 75
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/doduo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/doduo.gif\" alt=\"doduo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/doduo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/doduo.gif\" alt=\"doduo\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/doduo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/doduo.gif\" alt=\"doduo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/doduo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/doduo.gif\" alt=\"doduo\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "name": "Dodrio",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 110,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 110
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dodrio\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dodrio.gif\" alt=\"dodrio\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dodrio\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dodrio.gif\" alt=\"dodrio\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dodrio\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dodrio.gif\" alt=\"dodrio\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dodrio\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dodrio.gif\" alt=\"dodrio\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "name": "Seel",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/seel.gif\" alt=\"seel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/seel.gif\" alt=\"seel\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/seel.gif\" alt=\"seel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/seel.gif\" alt=\"seel\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "name": "Dewgong",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dewgong\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dewgong.gif\" alt=\"dewgong\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dewgong\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dewgong.gif\" alt=\"dewgong\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dewgong\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dewgong.gif\" alt=\"dewgong\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dewgong\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dewgong.gif\" alt=\"dewgong\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "name": "Grimer",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 25
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grimer\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/grimer.gif\" alt=\"grimer\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grimer\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/grimer.gif\" alt=\"grimer\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grimer\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/grimer.gif\" alt=\"grimer\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grimer\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/grimer.gif\" alt=\"grimer\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 89,
    "name": "Muk",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 105,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/muk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/muk.gif\" alt=\"muk\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/muk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/muk.gif\" alt=\"muk\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/muk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/muk.gif\" alt=\"muk\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/muk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/muk.gif\" alt=\"muk\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "name": "Shellder",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 25,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shellder\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/shellder.gif\" alt=\"shellder\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shellder\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/shellder.gif\" alt=\"shellder\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shellder\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/shellder.gif\" alt=\"shellder\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shellder\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/shellder.gif\" alt=\"shellder\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "name": "Cloyster",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 180,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cloyster\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cloyster.gif\" alt=\"cloyster\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cloyster\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cloyster.gif\" alt=\"cloyster\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cloyster\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cloyster.gif\" alt=\"cloyster\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cloyster\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cloyster.gif\" alt=\"cloyster\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 92,
    "name": "Gastly",
    "type": [
      "Ghost",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 35,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gastly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gastly.gif\" alt=\"gastly\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gastly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gastly.gif\" alt=\"gastly\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gastly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gastly.gif\" alt=\"gastly\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gastly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gastly.gif\" alt=\"gastly\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "name": "Haunter",
    "type": [
      "Ghost",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 115,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/haunter\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/haunter.gif\" alt=\"haunter\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/haunter\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/haunter.gif\" alt=\"haunter\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/haunter\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/haunter.gif\" alt=\"haunter\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/haunter\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/haunter.gif\" alt=\"haunter\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "name": "Gengar",
    "type": [
      "Ghost",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 130,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 110
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gengar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gengar.gif\" alt=\"gengar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gengar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gengar.gif\" alt=\"gengar\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gengar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gengar.gif\" alt=\"gengar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gengar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gengar.gif\" alt=\"gengar\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "name": "Onix",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 160,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/onix\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/onix.gif\" alt=\"onix\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/onix\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/onix.gif\" alt=\"onix\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/onix\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/onix.gif\" alt=\"onix\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/onix\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/onix.gif\" alt=\"onix\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "name": "Drowzee",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 48,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 43,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 42
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drowzee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/drowzee.gif\" alt=\"drowzee\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drowzee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/drowzee.gif\" alt=\"drowzee\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drowzee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/drowzee.gif\" alt=\"drowzee\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drowzee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/drowzee.gif\" alt=\"drowzee\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "name": "Hypno",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 73,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 73,
      "Sp. Defense": 115,
      "Speed": 67
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hypno\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/hypno.gif\" alt=\"hypno\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hypno\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/hypno.gif\" alt=\"hypno\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hypno\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/hypno.gif\" alt=\"hypno\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hypno\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/hypno.gif\" alt=\"hypno\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "name": "Krabby",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 25,
      "Sp. Defense": 25,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/krabby\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/krabby.gif\" alt=\"krabby\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/krabby\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/krabby.gif\" alt=\"krabby\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/krabby\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/krabby.gif\" alt=\"krabby\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/krabby\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/krabby.gif\" alt=\"krabby\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "name": "Kingler",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 115,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 75
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kingler\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kingler.gif\" alt=\"kingler\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kingler\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kingler.gif\" alt=\"kingler\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kingler\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kingler.gif\" alt=\"kingler\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kingler\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kingler.gif\" alt=\"kingler\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "name": "Voltorb",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/voltorb\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/voltorb.gif\" alt=\"voltorb\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/voltorb\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/voltorb.gif\" alt=\"voltorb\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/voltorb\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/voltorb.gif\" alt=\"voltorb\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/voltorb\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/voltorb.gif\" alt=\"voltorb\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 101,
    "name": "Electrode",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 150
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electrode\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/electrode.gif\" alt=\"electrode\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electrode\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/electrode.gif\" alt=\"electrode\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electrode\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/electrode.gif\" alt=\"electrode\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electrode\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/electrode.gif\" alt=\"electrode\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "name": "Exeggcute",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/exeggcute\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/exeggcute.gif\" alt=\"exeggcute\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/exeggcute\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/exeggcute.gif\" alt=\"exeggcute\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/exeggcute\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/exeggcute.gif\" alt=\"exeggcute\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/exeggcute\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/exeggcute.gif\" alt=\"exeggcute\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "name": "Exeggutor",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/exeggutor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/exeggutor.gif\" alt=\"exeggutor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/exeggutor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/exeggutor.gif\" alt=\"exeggutor\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/exeggutor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/exeggutor.gif\" alt=\"exeggutor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/exeggutor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/exeggutor.gif\" alt=\"exeggutor\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "name": "Cubone",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cubone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cubone.gif\" alt=\"cubone\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cubone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cubone.gif\" alt=\"cubone\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cubone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cubone.gif\" alt=\"cubone\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cubone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cubone.gif\" alt=\"cubone\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "name": "Marowak",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 110,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/marowak\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/marowak.gif\" alt=\"marowak\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/marowak\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/marowak.gif\" alt=\"marowak\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/marowak\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/marowak.gif\" alt=\"marowak\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/marowak\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/marowak.gif\" alt=\"marowak\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "name": "Hitmonlee",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 53,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 110,
      "Speed": 87
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hitmonlee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/hitmonlee.gif\" alt=\"hitmonlee\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hitmonlee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/hitmonlee.gif\" alt=\"hitmonlee\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hitmonlee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/hitmonlee.gif\" alt=\"hitmonlee\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hitmonlee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/hitmonlee.gif\" alt=\"hitmonlee\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "name": "Hitmonchan",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 79,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 110,
      "Speed": 76
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hitmonchan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/hitmonchan.gif\" alt=\"hitmonchan\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hitmonchan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/hitmonchan.gif\" alt=\"hitmonchan\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hitmonchan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/hitmonchan.gif\" alt=\"hitmonchan\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hitmonchan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/hitmonchan.gif\" alt=\"hitmonchan\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "name": "Lickitung",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lickitung\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lickitung.gif\" alt=\"lickitung\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lickitung\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lickitung.gif\" alt=\"lickitung\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lickitung\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lickitung.gif\" alt=\"lickitung\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lickitung\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lickitung.gif\" alt=\"lickitung\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 109,
    "name": "Koffing",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/koffing\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/koffing.gif\" alt=\"koffing\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/koffing\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/koffing.gif\" alt=\"koffing\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/koffing\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/koffing.gif\" alt=\"koffing\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/koffing\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/koffing.gif\" alt=\"koffing\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "name": "Weezing",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 120,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weezing\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/weezing.gif\" alt=\"weezing\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weezing\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/weezing.gif\" alt=\"weezing\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weezing\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/weezing.gif\" alt=\"weezing\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weezing\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/weezing.gif\" alt=\"weezing\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 111,
    "name": "Rhyhorn",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 25
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rhyhorn\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/rhyhorn.gif\" alt=\"rhyhorn\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rhyhorn\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/rhyhorn.gif\" alt=\"rhyhorn\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rhyhorn\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/rhyhorn.gif\" alt=\"rhyhorn\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rhyhorn\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/rhyhorn.gif\" alt=\"rhyhorn\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 112,
    "name": "Rhydon",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 105,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 120,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rhydon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/rhydon.gif\" alt=\"rhydon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rhydon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/rhydon.gif\" alt=\"rhydon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rhydon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/rhydon.gif\" alt=\"rhydon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rhydon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/rhydon.gif\" alt=\"rhydon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 113,
    "name": "Chansey",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 250,
      "Attack": 5,
      "Defense": 5,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 105,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chansey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/chansey.gif\" alt=\"chansey\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chansey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/chansey.gif\" alt=\"chansey\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chansey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/chansey.gif\" alt=\"chansey\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chansey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/chansey.gif\" alt=\"chansey\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 114,
    "name": "Tangela",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 115,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tangela\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tangela.gif\" alt=\"tangela\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tangela\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tangela.gif\" alt=\"tangela\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tangela\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tangela.gif\" alt=\"tangela\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tangela\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tangela.gif\" alt=\"tangela\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 115,
    "name": "Kangaskhan",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 105,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kangaskhan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kangaskhan.gif\" alt=\"kangaskhan\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kangaskhan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kangaskhan.gif\" alt=\"kangaskhan\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kangaskhan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kangaskhan.gif\" alt=\"kangaskhan\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kangaskhan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kangaskhan.gif\" alt=\"kangaskhan\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 116,
    "name": "Horsea",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 25,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/horsea\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/horsea.gif\" alt=\"horsea\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/horsea\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/horsea.gif\" alt=\"horsea\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/horsea\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/horsea.gif\" alt=\"horsea\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/horsea\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/horsea.gif\" alt=\"horsea\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 117,
    "name": "Seadra",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seadra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/seadra.gif\" alt=\"seadra\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seadra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/seadra.gif\" alt=\"seadra\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seadra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/seadra.gif\" alt=\"seadra\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seadra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/seadra.gif\" alt=\"seadra\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 118,
    "name": "Goldeen",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 67,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 63
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/goldeen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/goldeen.gif\" alt=\"goldeen\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/goldeen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/goldeen.gif\" alt=\"goldeen\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/goldeen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/goldeen.gif\" alt=\"goldeen\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/goldeen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/goldeen.gif\" alt=\"goldeen\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 119,
    "name": "Seaking",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 92,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 68
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seaking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/seaking.gif\" alt=\"seaking\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seaking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/seaking.gif\" alt=\"seaking\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seaking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/seaking.gif\" alt=\"seaking\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seaking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/seaking.gif\" alt=\"seaking\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 120,
    "name": "Staryu",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/staryu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/staryu.gif\" alt=\"staryu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/staryu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/staryu.gif\" alt=\"staryu\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/staryu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/staryu.gif\" alt=\"staryu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/staryu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/staryu.gif\" alt=\"staryu\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 121,
    "name": "Starmie",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 115
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/starmie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/starmie.gif\" alt=\"starmie\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/starmie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/starmie.gif\" alt=\"starmie\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/starmie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/starmie.gif\" alt=\"starmie\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/starmie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/starmie.gif\" alt=\"starmie\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 122,
    "name": "Mr. Mime",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 120,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mr. mime\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mr. mime.gif\" alt=\"mr. mime\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mr. mime\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mr. mime.gif\" alt=\"mr. mime\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mr. mime\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mr. mime.gif\" alt=\"mr. mime\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mr. mime\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mr. mime.gif\" alt=\"mr. mime\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 123,
    "name": "Scyther",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 110,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 105
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scyther\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/scyther.gif\" alt=\"scyther\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scyther\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/scyther.gif\" alt=\"scyther\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scyther\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/scyther.gif\" alt=\"scyther\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scyther\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/scyther.gif\" alt=\"scyther\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 124,
    "name": "Jynx",
    "type": [
      "Ice",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 115,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jynx\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/jynx.gif\" alt=\"jynx\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jynx\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/jynx.gif\" alt=\"jynx\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jynx\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/jynx.gif\" alt=\"jynx\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jynx\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/jynx.gif\" alt=\"jynx\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 125,
    "name": "Electabuzz",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 83,
      "Defense": 57,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 105
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electabuzz\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/electabuzz.gif\" alt=\"electabuzz\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electabuzz\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/electabuzz.gif\" alt=\"electabuzz\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electabuzz\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/electabuzz.gif\" alt=\"electabuzz\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electabuzz\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/electabuzz.gif\" alt=\"electabuzz\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 126,
    "name": "Magmar",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 57,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 93
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magmar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/magmar.gif\" alt=\"magmar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magmar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/magmar.gif\" alt=\"magmar\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magmar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/magmar.gif\" alt=\"magmar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magmar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/magmar.gif\" alt=\"magmar\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 127,
    "name": "Pinsir",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 125,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pinsir\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pinsir.gif\" alt=\"pinsir\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pinsir\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pinsir.gif\" alt=\"pinsir\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pinsir\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pinsir.gif\" alt=\"pinsir\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pinsir\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pinsir.gif\" alt=\"pinsir\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 128,
    "name": "Tauros",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 110
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tauros\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tauros.gif\" alt=\"tauros\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tauros\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tauros.gif\" alt=\"tauros\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tauros\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tauros.gif\" alt=\"tauros\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tauros\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tauros.gif\" alt=\"tauros\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 129,
    "name": "Magikarp",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 20,
      "Attack": 10,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 15,
      "Sp. Defense": 20,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magikarp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/magikarp.gif\" alt=\"magikarp\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magikarp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/magikarp.gif\" alt=\"magikarp\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magikarp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/magikarp.gif\" alt=\"magikarp\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magikarp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/magikarp.gif\" alt=\"magikarp\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 130,
    "name": "Gyarados",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 125,
      "Defense": 79,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 81
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gyarados\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gyarados.gif\" alt=\"gyarados\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gyarados\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gyarados.gif\" alt=\"gyarados\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gyarados\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gyarados.gif\" alt=\"gyarados\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gyarados\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gyarados.gif\" alt=\"gyarados\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 131,
    "name": "Lapras",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 130,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lapras\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lapras.gif\" alt=\"lapras\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lapras\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lapras.gif\" alt=\"lapras\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lapras\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lapras.gif\" alt=\"lapras\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lapras\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lapras.gif\" alt=\"lapras\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 132,
    "name": "Ditto",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 48,
      "Attack": 48,
      "Defense": 48,
      "Sp. Attack": 48,
      "Sp. Defense": 48,
      "Speed": 48
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ditto\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ditto.gif\" alt=\"ditto\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ditto\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ditto.gif\" alt=\"ditto\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ditto\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ditto.gif\" alt=\"ditto\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ditto\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ditto.gif\" alt=\"ditto\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 133,
    "name": "Eevee",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/eevee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/eevee.gif\" alt=\"eevee\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/eevee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/eevee.gif\" alt=\"eevee\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/eevee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/eevee.gif\" alt=\"eevee\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/eevee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/eevee.gif\" alt=\"eevee\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 134,
    "name": "Vaporeon",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 130,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 110,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vaporeon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/vaporeon.gif\" alt=\"vaporeon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vaporeon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/vaporeon.gif\" alt=\"vaporeon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vaporeon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/vaporeon.gif\" alt=\"vaporeon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vaporeon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/vaporeon.gif\" alt=\"vaporeon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 135,
    "name": "Jolteon",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 110,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 130
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jolteon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/jolteon.gif\" alt=\"jolteon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jolteon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/jolteon.gif\" alt=\"jolteon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jolteon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/jolteon.gif\" alt=\"jolteon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jolteon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/jolteon.gif\" alt=\"jolteon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 136,
    "name": "Flareon",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 110,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/flareon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/flareon.gif\" alt=\"flareon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/flareon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/flareon.gif\" alt=\"flareon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/flareon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/flareon.gif\" alt=\"flareon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/flareon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/flareon.gif\" alt=\"flareon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 137,
    "name": "Porygon",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/porygon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/porygon.gif\" alt=\"porygon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/porygon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/porygon.gif\" alt=\"porygon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/porygon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/porygon.gif\" alt=\"porygon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/porygon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/porygon.gif\" alt=\"porygon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 138,
    "name": "Omanyte",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/omanyte\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/omanyte.gif\" alt=\"omanyte\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/omanyte\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/omanyte.gif\" alt=\"omanyte\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/omanyte\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/omanyte.gif\" alt=\"omanyte\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/omanyte\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/omanyte.gif\" alt=\"omanyte\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "name": "Omastar",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 125,
      "Sp. Attack": 115,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/omastar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/omastar.gif\" alt=\"omastar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/omastar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/omastar.gif\" alt=\"omastar\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/omastar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/omastar.gif\" alt=\"omastar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/omastar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/omastar.gif\" alt=\"omastar\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 140,
    "name": "Kabuto",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kabuto\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kabuto.gif\" alt=\"kabuto\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kabuto\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kabuto.gif\" alt=\"kabuto\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kabuto\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kabuto.gif\" alt=\"kabuto\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kabuto\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kabuto.gif\" alt=\"kabuto\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 141,
    "name": "Kabutops",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 115,
      "Defense": 105,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kabutops\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kabutops.gif\" alt=\"kabutops\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kabutops\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kabutops.gif\" alt=\"kabutops\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kabutops\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kabutops.gif\" alt=\"kabutops\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kabutops\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kabutops.gif\" alt=\"kabutops\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 142,
    "name": "Aerodactyl",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 130
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aerodactyl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/aerodactyl.gif\" alt=\"aerodactyl\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aerodactyl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/aerodactyl.gif\" alt=\"aerodactyl\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aerodactyl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/aerodactyl.gif\" alt=\"aerodactyl\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aerodactyl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/aerodactyl.gif\" alt=\"aerodactyl\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 143,
    "name": "Snorlax",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 160,
      "Attack": 110,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 110,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snorlax\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/snorlax.gif\" alt=\"snorlax\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snorlax\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/snorlax.gif\" alt=\"snorlax\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snorlax\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/snorlax.gif\" alt=\"snorlax\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snorlax\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/snorlax.gif\" alt=\"snorlax\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 144,
    "name": "Articuno",
    "type": [
      "Ice",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 125,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/articuno\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/articuno.gif\" alt=\"articuno\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/articuno\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/articuno.gif\" alt=\"articuno\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/articuno\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/articuno.gif\" alt=\"articuno\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/articuno\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/articuno.gif\" alt=\"articuno\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 145,
    "name": "Zapdos",
    "type": [
      "Electric",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zapdos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/zapdos.gif\" alt=\"zapdos\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zapdos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/zapdos.gif\" alt=\"zapdos\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zapdos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/zapdos.gif\" alt=\"zapdos\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zapdos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/zapdos.gif\" alt=\"zapdos\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 146,
    "name": "Moltres",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/moltres\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/moltres.gif\" alt=\"moltres\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/moltres\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/moltres.gif\" alt=\"moltres\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/moltres\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/moltres.gif\" alt=\"moltres\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/moltres\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/moltres.gif\" alt=\"moltres\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 147,
    "name": "Dratini",
    "type": [
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 41,
      "Attack": 64,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dratini\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dratini.gif\" alt=\"dratini\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dratini\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dratini.gif\" alt=\"dratini\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dratini\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dratini.gif\" alt=\"dratini\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dratini\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dratini.gif\" alt=\"dratini\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 148,
    "name": "Dragonair",
    "type": [
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 61,
      "Attack": 84,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dragonair\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dragonair.gif\" alt=\"dragonair\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dragonair\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dragonair.gif\" alt=\"dragonair\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dragonair\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dragonair.gif\" alt=\"dragonair\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dragonair\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dragonair.gif\" alt=\"dragonair\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 149,
    "name": "Dragonite",
    "type": [
      "Dragon",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 91,
      "Attack": 134,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dragonite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dragonite.gif\" alt=\"dragonite\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dragonite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dragonite.gif\" alt=\"dragonite\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dragonite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dragonite.gif\" alt=\"dragonite\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dragonite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dragonite.gif\" alt=\"dragonite\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 150,
    "name": "Mewtwo",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 106,
      "Attack": 110,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 154,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 130
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mewtwo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mewtwo.gif\" alt=\"mewtwo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mewtwo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mewtwo.gif\" alt=\"mewtwo\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mewtwo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mewtwo.gif\" alt=\"mewtwo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mewtwo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mewtwo.gif\" alt=\"mewtwo\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 151,
    "name": "Mew",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mew.gif\" alt=\"mew\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mew.gif\" alt=\"mew\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mew.gif\" alt=\"mew\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mew.gif\" alt=\"mew\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 152,
    "name": "Chikorita",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 49,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 49,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chikorita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/chikorita.gif\" alt=\"chikorita\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chikorita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/chikorita.gif\" alt=\"chikorita\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chikorita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/chikorita.gif\" alt=\"chikorita\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chikorita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/chikorita.gif\" alt=\"chikorita\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 153,
    "name": "Bayleef",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 62,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 63,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bayleef\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bayleef.gif\" alt=\"bayleef\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bayleef\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bayleef.gif\" alt=\"bayleef\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bayleef\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bayleef.gif\" alt=\"bayleef\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bayleef\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bayleef.gif\" alt=\"bayleef\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 154,
    "name": "Meganium",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 82,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 83,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meganium\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/meganium.gif\" alt=\"meganium\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meganium\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/meganium.gif\" alt=\"meganium\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meganium\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/meganium.gif\" alt=\"meganium\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meganium\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/meganium.gif\" alt=\"meganium\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 155,
    "name": "Cyndaquil",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 39,
      "Attack": 52,
      "Defense": 43,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cyndaquil\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cyndaquil.gif\" alt=\"cyndaquil\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cyndaquil\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cyndaquil.gif\" alt=\"cyndaquil\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cyndaquil\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cyndaquil.gif\" alt=\"cyndaquil\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cyndaquil\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cyndaquil.gif\" alt=\"cyndaquil\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 156,
    "name": "Quilava",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 58,
      "Attack": 64,
      "Defense": 58,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/quilava\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/quilava.gif\" alt=\"quilava\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/quilava\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/quilava.gif\" alt=\"quilava\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/quilava\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/quilava.gif\" alt=\"quilava\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/quilava\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/quilava.gif\" alt=\"quilava\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 157,
    "name": "Typhlosion",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 78,
      "Attack": 84,
      "Defense": 78,
      "Sp. Attack": 109,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/typhlosion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/typhlosion.gif\" alt=\"typhlosion\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/typhlosion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/typhlosion.gif\" alt=\"typhlosion\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/typhlosion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/typhlosion.gif\" alt=\"typhlosion\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/typhlosion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/typhlosion.gif\" alt=\"typhlosion\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 158,
    "name": "Totodile",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 64,
      "Sp. Attack": 44,
      "Sp. Defense": 48,
      "Speed": 43
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/totodile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/totodile.gif\" alt=\"totodile\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/totodile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/totodile.gif\" alt=\"totodile\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/totodile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/totodile.gif\" alt=\"totodile\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/totodile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/totodile.gif\" alt=\"totodile\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 159,
    "name": "Croconaw",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 59,
      "Sp. Defense": 63,
      "Speed": 58
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/croconaw\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/croconaw.gif\" alt=\"croconaw\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/croconaw\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/croconaw.gif\" alt=\"croconaw\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/croconaw\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/croconaw.gif\" alt=\"croconaw\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/croconaw\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/croconaw.gif\" alt=\"croconaw\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 160,
    "name": "Feraligatr",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 79,
      "Sp. Defense": 83,
      "Speed": 78
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/feraligatr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/feraligatr.gif\" alt=\"feraligatr\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/feraligatr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/feraligatr.gif\" alt=\"feraligatr\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/feraligatr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/feraligatr.gif\" alt=\"feraligatr\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/feraligatr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/feraligatr.gif\" alt=\"feraligatr\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 161,
    "name": "Sentret",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 46,
      "Defense": 34,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sentret\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sentret.gif\" alt=\"sentret\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sentret\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sentret.gif\" alt=\"sentret\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sentret\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sentret.gif\" alt=\"sentret\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sentret\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sentret.gif\" alt=\"sentret\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 162,
    "name": "Furret",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 76,
      "Defense": 64,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/furret\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/furret.gif\" alt=\"furret\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/furret\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/furret.gif\" alt=\"furret\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/furret\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/furret.gif\" alt=\"furret\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/furret\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/furret.gif\" alt=\"furret\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 163,
    "name": "Hoothoot",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 36,
      "Sp. Defense": 56,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hoothoot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/hoothoot.gif\" alt=\"hoothoot\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hoothoot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/hoothoot.gif\" alt=\"hoothoot\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hoothoot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/hoothoot.gif\" alt=\"hoothoot\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hoothoot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/hoothoot.gif\" alt=\"hoothoot\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 164,
    "name": "Noctowl",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 86,
      "Sp. Defense": 96,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/noctowl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/noctowl.gif\" alt=\"noctowl\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/noctowl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/noctowl.gif\" alt=\"noctowl\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/noctowl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/noctowl.gif\" alt=\"noctowl\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/noctowl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/noctowl.gif\" alt=\"noctowl\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 165,
    "name": "Ledyba",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 20,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ledyba\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ledyba.gif\" alt=\"ledyba\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ledyba\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ledyba.gif\" alt=\"ledyba\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ledyba\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ledyba.gif\" alt=\"ledyba\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ledyba\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ledyba.gif\" alt=\"ledyba\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 166,
    "name": "Ledian",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 35,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 110,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ledian\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ledian.gif\" alt=\"ledian\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ledian\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ledian.gif\" alt=\"ledian\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ledian\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ledian.gif\" alt=\"ledian\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ledian\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ledian.gif\" alt=\"ledian\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 167,
    "name": "Spinarak",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spinarak\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/spinarak.gif\" alt=\"spinarak\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spinarak\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/spinarak.gif\" alt=\"spinarak\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spinarak\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/spinarak.gif\" alt=\"spinarak\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spinarak\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/spinarak.gif\" alt=\"spinarak\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 168,
    "name": "Ariados",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ariados\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ariados.gif\" alt=\"ariados\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ariados\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ariados.gif\" alt=\"ariados\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ariados\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ariados.gif\" alt=\"ariados\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ariados\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ariados.gif\" alt=\"ariados\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 169,
    "name": "Crobat",
    "type": [
      "Poison",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 130
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/crobat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/crobat.gif\" alt=\"crobat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/crobat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/crobat.gif\" alt=\"crobat\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/crobat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/crobat.gif\" alt=\"crobat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/crobat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/crobat.gif\" alt=\"crobat\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 170,
    "name": "Chinchou",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 38,
      "Defense": 38,
      "Sp. Attack": 56,
      "Sp. Defense": 56,
      "Speed": 67
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chinchou\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/chinchou.gif\" alt=\"chinchou\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chinchou\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/chinchou.gif\" alt=\"chinchou\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chinchou\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/chinchou.gif\" alt=\"chinchou\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chinchou\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/chinchou.gif\" alt=\"chinchou\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 171,
    "name": "Lanturn",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 125,
      "Attack": 58,
      "Defense": 58,
      "Sp. Attack": 76,
      "Sp. Defense": 76,
      "Speed": 67
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lanturn\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lanturn.gif\" alt=\"lanturn\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lanturn\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lanturn.gif\" alt=\"lanturn\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lanturn\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lanturn.gif\" alt=\"lanturn\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lanturn\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lanturn.gif\" alt=\"lanturn\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 172,
    "name": "Pichu",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 20,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 15,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pichu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pichu.gif\" alt=\"pichu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pichu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pichu.gif\" alt=\"pichu\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pichu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pichu.gif\" alt=\"pichu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pichu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pichu.gif\" alt=\"pichu\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 173,
    "name": "Cleffa",
    "type": [
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 25,
      "Defense": 28,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 15
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cleffa\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cleffa.gif\" alt=\"cleffa\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cleffa\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cleffa.gif\" alt=\"cleffa\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cleffa\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cleffa.gif\" alt=\"cleffa\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cleffa\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cleffa.gif\" alt=\"cleffa\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 174,
    "name": "Igglybuff",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 15,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 20,
      "Speed": 15
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/igglybuff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/igglybuff.gif\" alt=\"igglybuff\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/igglybuff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/igglybuff.gif\" alt=\"igglybuff\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/igglybuff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/igglybuff.gif\" alt=\"igglybuff\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/igglybuff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/igglybuff.gif\" alt=\"igglybuff\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 175,
    "name": "Togepi",
    "type": [
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 20,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/togepi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/togepi.gif\" alt=\"togepi\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/togepi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/togepi.gif\" alt=\"togepi\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/togepi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/togepi.gif\" alt=\"togepi\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/togepi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/togepi.gif\" alt=\"togepi\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 176,
    "name": "Togetic",
    "type": [
      "Fairy",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 105,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/togetic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/togetic.gif\" alt=\"togetic\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/togetic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/togetic.gif\" alt=\"togetic\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/togetic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/togetic.gif\" alt=\"togetic\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/togetic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/togetic.gif\" alt=\"togetic\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 177,
    "name": "Natu",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/natu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/natu.gif\" alt=\"natu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/natu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/natu.gif\" alt=\"natu\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/natu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/natu.gif\" alt=\"natu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/natu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/natu.gif\" alt=\"natu\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 178,
    "name": "Xatu",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/xatu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/xatu.gif\" alt=\"xatu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/xatu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/xatu.gif\" alt=\"xatu\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/xatu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/xatu.gif\" alt=\"xatu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/xatu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/xatu.gif\" alt=\"xatu\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 179,
    "name": "Mareep",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mareep\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mareep.gif\" alt=\"mareep\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mareep\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mareep.gif\" alt=\"mareep\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mareep\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mareep.gif\" alt=\"mareep\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mareep\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mareep.gif\" alt=\"mareep\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 180,
    "name": "Flaaffy",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/flaaffy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/flaaffy.gif\" alt=\"flaaffy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/flaaffy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/flaaffy.gif\" alt=\"flaaffy\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/flaaffy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/flaaffy.gif\" alt=\"flaaffy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/flaaffy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/flaaffy.gif\" alt=\"flaaffy\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 181,
    "name": "Ampharos",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 115,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ampharos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ampharos.gif\" alt=\"ampharos\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ampharos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ampharos.gif\" alt=\"ampharos\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ampharos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ampharos.gif\" alt=\"ampharos\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ampharos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ampharos.gif\" alt=\"ampharos\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 182,
    "name": "Bellossom",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bellossom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bellossom.gif\" alt=\"bellossom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bellossom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bellossom.gif\" alt=\"bellossom\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bellossom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bellossom.gif\" alt=\"bellossom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bellossom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bellossom.gif\" alt=\"bellossom\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 183,
    "name": "Marill",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 20,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 20,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/marill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/marill.gif\" alt=\"marill\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/marill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/marill.gif\" alt=\"marill\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/marill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/marill.gif\" alt=\"marill\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/marill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/marill.gif\" alt=\"marill\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 184,
    "name": "Azumarill",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/azumarill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/azumarill.gif\" alt=\"azumarill\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/azumarill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/azumarill.gif\" alt=\"azumarill\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/azumarill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/azumarill.gif\" alt=\"azumarill\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/azumarill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/azumarill.gif\" alt=\"azumarill\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 185,
    "name": "Sudowoodo",
    "type": [
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 115,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sudowoodo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sudowoodo.gif\" alt=\"sudowoodo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sudowoodo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sudowoodo.gif\" alt=\"sudowoodo\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sudowoodo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sudowoodo.gif\" alt=\"sudowoodo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sudowoodo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sudowoodo.gif\" alt=\"sudowoodo\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 186,
    "name": "Politoed",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/politoed\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/politoed.gif\" alt=\"politoed\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/politoed\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/politoed.gif\" alt=\"politoed\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/politoed\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/politoed.gif\" alt=\"politoed\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/politoed\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/politoed.gif\" alt=\"politoed\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 187,
    "name": "Hoppip",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 35,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hoppip\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/hoppip.gif\" alt=\"hoppip\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hoppip\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/hoppip.gif\" alt=\"hoppip\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hoppip\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/hoppip.gif\" alt=\"hoppip\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hoppip\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/hoppip.gif\" alt=\"hoppip\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 188,
    "name": "Skiploom",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skiploom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/skiploom.gif\" alt=\"skiploom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skiploom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/skiploom.gif\" alt=\"skiploom\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skiploom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/skiploom.gif\" alt=\"skiploom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skiploom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/skiploom.gif\" alt=\"skiploom\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 189,
    "name": "Jumpluff",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 110
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jumpluff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/jumpluff.gif\" alt=\"jumpluff\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jumpluff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/jumpluff.gif\" alt=\"jumpluff\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jumpluff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/jumpluff.gif\" alt=\"jumpluff\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jumpluff\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/jumpluff.gif\" alt=\"jumpluff\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 190,
    "name": "Aipom",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aipom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/aipom.gif\" alt=\"aipom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aipom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/aipom.gif\" alt=\"aipom\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aipom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/aipom.gif\" alt=\"aipom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aipom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/aipom.gif\" alt=\"aipom\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 191,
    "name": "Sunkern",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sunkern\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sunkern.gif\" alt=\"sunkern\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sunkern\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sunkern.gif\" alt=\"sunkern\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sunkern\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sunkern.gif\" alt=\"sunkern\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sunkern\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sunkern.gif\" alt=\"sunkern\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 192,
    "name": "Sunflora",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sunflora\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sunflora.gif\" alt=\"sunflora\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sunflora\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sunflora.gif\" alt=\"sunflora\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sunflora\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sunflora.gif\" alt=\"sunflora\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sunflora\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sunflora.gif\" alt=\"sunflora\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 193,
    "name": "Yanma",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/yanma\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/yanma.gif\" alt=\"yanma\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/yanma\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/yanma.gif\" alt=\"yanma\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/yanma\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/yanma.gif\" alt=\"yanma\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/yanma\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/yanma.gif\" alt=\"yanma\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 194,
    "name": "Wooper",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 25,
      "Sp. Defense": 25,
      "Speed": 15
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wooper\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/wooper.gif\" alt=\"wooper\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wooper\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/wooper.gif\" alt=\"wooper\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wooper\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/wooper.gif\" alt=\"wooper\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wooper\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/wooper.gif\" alt=\"wooper\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 195,
    "name": "Quagsire",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/quagsire\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/quagsire.gif\" alt=\"quagsire\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/quagsire\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/quagsire.gif\" alt=\"quagsire\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/quagsire\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/quagsire.gif\" alt=\"quagsire\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/quagsire\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/quagsire.gif\" alt=\"quagsire\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 196,
    "name": "Espeon",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 130,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 110
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/espeon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/espeon.gif\" alt=\"espeon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/espeon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/espeon.gif\" alt=\"espeon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/espeon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/espeon.gif\" alt=\"espeon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/espeon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/espeon.gif\" alt=\"espeon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 197,
    "name": "Umbreon",
    "type": [
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 110,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 130,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/umbreon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/umbreon.gif\" alt=\"umbreon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/umbreon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/umbreon.gif\" alt=\"umbreon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/umbreon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/umbreon.gif\" alt=\"umbreon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/umbreon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/umbreon.gif\" alt=\"umbreon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 198,
    "name": "Murkrow",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 42,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 42,
      "Speed": 91
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/murkrow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/murkrow.gif\" alt=\"murkrow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/murkrow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/murkrow.gif\" alt=\"murkrow\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/murkrow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/murkrow.gif\" alt=\"murkrow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/murkrow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/murkrow.gif\" alt=\"murkrow\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 199,
    "name": "Slowking",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 110,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slowking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/slowking.gif\" alt=\"slowking\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slowking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/slowking.gif\" alt=\"slowking\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slowking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/slowking.gif\" alt=\"slowking\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slowking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/slowking.gif\" alt=\"slowking\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 200,
    "name": "Misdreavus",
    "type": [
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/misdreavus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/misdreavus.gif\" alt=\"misdreavus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/misdreavus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/misdreavus.gif\" alt=\"misdreavus\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/misdreavus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/misdreavus.gif\" alt=\"misdreavus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/misdreavus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/misdreavus.gif\" alt=\"misdreavus\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 201,
    "name": "Unown",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 48,
      "Attack": 72,
      "Defense": 48,
      "Sp. Attack": 72,
      "Sp. Defense": 48,
      "Speed": 48
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/unown\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/unown.gif\" alt=\"unown\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/unown\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/unown.gif\" alt=\"unown\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/unown\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/unown.gif\" alt=\"unown\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/unown\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/unown.gif\" alt=\"unown\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 202,
    "name": "Wobbuffet",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 190,
      "Attack": 33,
      "Defense": 58,
      "Sp. Attack": 33,
      "Sp. Defense": 58,
      "Speed": 33
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wobbuffet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/wobbuffet.gif\" alt=\"wobbuffet\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wobbuffet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/wobbuffet.gif\" alt=\"wobbuffet\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wobbuffet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/wobbuffet.gif\" alt=\"wobbuffet\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wobbuffet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/wobbuffet.gif\" alt=\"wobbuffet\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 203,
    "name": "Girafarig",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/girafarig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/girafarig.gif\" alt=\"girafarig\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/girafarig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/girafarig.gif\" alt=\"girafarig\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/girafarig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/girafarig.gif\" alt=\"girafarig\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/girafarig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/girafarig.gif\" alt=\"girafarig\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 204,
    "name": "Pineco",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 15
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pineco\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pineco.gif\" alt=\"pineco\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pineco\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pineco.gif\" alt=\"pineco\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pineco\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pineco.gif\" alt=\"pineco\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pineco\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pineco.gif\" alt=\"pineco\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 205,
    "name": "Forretress",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 140,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/forretress\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/forretress.gif\" alt=\"forretress\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/forretress\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/forretress.gif\" alt=\"forretress\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/forretress\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/forretress.gif\" alt=\"forretress\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/forretress\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/forretress.gif\" alt=\"forretress\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 206,
    "name": "Dunsparce",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dunsparce\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dunsparce.gif\" alt=\"dunsparce\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dunsparce\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dunsparce.gif\" alt=\"dunsparce\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dunsparce\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dunsparce.gif\" alt=\"dunsparce\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dunsparce\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dunsparce.gif\" alt=\"dunsparce\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 207,
    "name": "Gligar",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 105,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gligar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gligar.gif\" alt=\"gligar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gligar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gligar.gif\" alt=\"gligar\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gligar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gligar.gif\" alt=\"gligar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gligar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gligar.gif\" alt=\"gligar\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 208,
    "name": "Steelix",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 200,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/steelix\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/steelix.gif\" alt=\"steelix\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/steelix\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/steelix.gif\" alt=\"steelix\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/steelix\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/steelix.gif\" alt=\"steelix\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/steelix\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/steelix.gif\" alt=\"steelix\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 209,
    "name": "Snubbull",
    "type": [
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snubbull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/snubbull.gif\" alt=\"snubbull\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snubbull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/snubbull.gif\" alt=\"snubbull\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snubbull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/snubbull.gif\" alt=\"snubbull\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snubbull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/snubbull.gif\" alt=\"snubbull\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 210,
    "name": "Granbull",
    "type": [
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/granbull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/granbull.gif\" alt=\"granbull\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/granbull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/granbull.gif\" alt=\"granbull\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/granbull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/granbull.gif\" alt=\"granbull\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/granbull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/granbull.gif\" alt=\"granbull\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 211,
    "name": "Qwilfish",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/qwilfish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/qwilfish.gif\" alt=\"qwilfish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/qwilfish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/qwilfish.gif\" alt=\"qwilfish\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/qwilfish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/qwilfish.gif\" alt=\"qwilfish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/qwilfish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/qwilfish.gif\" alt=\"qwilfish\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 212,
    "name": "Scizor",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scizor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/scizor.gif\" alt=\"scizor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scizor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/scizor.gif\" alt=\"scizor\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scizor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/scizor.gif\" alt=\"scizor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scizor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/scizor.gif\" alt=\"scizor\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 213,
    "name": "Shuckle",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 20,
      "Attack": 10,
      "Defense": 230,
      "Sp. Attack": 10,
      "Sp. Defense": 230,
      "Speed": 5
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shuckle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/shuckle.gif\" alt=\"shuckle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shuckle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/shuckle.gif\" alt=\"shuckle\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shuckle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/shuckle.gif\" alt=\"shuckle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shuckle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/shuckle.gif\" alt=\"shuckle\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 214,
    "name": "Heracross",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 125,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/heracross\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/heracross.gif\" alt=\"heracross\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/heracross\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/heracross.gif\" alt=\"heracross\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/heracross\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/heracross.gif\" alt=\"heracross\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/heracross\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/heracross.gif\" alt=\"heracross\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 215,
    "name": "Sneasel",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 115
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sneasel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sneasel.gif\" alt=\"sneasel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sneasel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sneasel.gif\" alt=\"sneasel\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sneasel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sneasel.gif\" alt=\"sneasel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sneasel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sneasel.gif\" alt=\"sneasel\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 216,
    "name": "Teddiursa",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/teddiursa\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/teddiursa.gif\" alt=\"teddiursa\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/teddiursa\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/teddiursa.gif\" alt=\"teddiursa\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/teddiursa\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/teddiursa.gif\" alt=\"teddiursa\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/teddiursa\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/teddiursa.gif\" alt=\"teddiursa\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 217,
    "name": "Ursaring",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ursaring\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ursaring.gif\" alt=\"ursaring\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ursaring\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ursaring.gif\" alt=\"ursaring\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ursaring\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ursaring.gif\" alt=\"ursaring\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ursaring\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ursaring.gif\" alt=\"ursaring\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 218,
    "name": "Slugma",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slugma\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/slugma.gif\" alt=\"slugma\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slugma\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/slugma.gif\" alt=\"slugma\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slugma\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/slugma.gif\" alt=\"slugma\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slugma\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/slugma.gif\" alt=\"slugma\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 219,
    "name": "Magcargo",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 120,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magcargo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/magcargo.gif\" alt=\"magcargo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magcargo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/magcargo.gif\" alt=\"magcargo\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magcargo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/magcargo.gif\" alt=\"magcargo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magcargo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/magcargo.gif\" alt=\"magcargo\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 220,
    "name": "Swinub",
    "type": [
      "Ice",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swinub\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/swinub.gif\" alt=\"swinub\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swinub\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/swinub.gif\" alt=\"swinub\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swinub\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/swinub.gif\" alt=\"swinub\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swinub\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/swinub.gif\" alt=\"swinub\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 221,
    "name": "Piloswine",
    "type": [
      "Ice",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/piloswine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/piloswine.gif\" alt=\"piloswine\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/piloswine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/piloswine.gif\" alt=\"piloswine\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/piloswine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/piloswine.gif\" alt=\"piloswine\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/piloswine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/piloswine.gif\" alt=\"piloswine\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 222,
    "name": "Corsola",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/corsola\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/corsola.gif\" alt=\"corsola\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/corsola\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/corsola.gif\" alt=\"corsola\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/corsola\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/corsola.gif\" alt=\"corsola\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/corsola\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/corsola.gif\" alt=\"corsola\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 223,
    "name": "Remoraid",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/remoraid\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/remoraid.gif\" alt=\"remoraid\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/remoraid\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/remoraid.gif\" alt=\"remoraid\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/remoraid\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/remoraid.gif\" alt=\"remoraid\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/remoraid\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/remoraid.gif\" alt=\"remoraid\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 224,
    "name": "Octillery",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/octillery\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/octillery.gif\" alt=\"octillery\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/octillery\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/octillery.gif\" alt=\"octillery\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/octillery\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/octillery.gif\" alt=\"octillery\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/octillery\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/octillery.gif\" alt=\"octillery\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 225,
    "name": "Delibird",
    "type": [
      "Ice",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 75
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/delibird\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/delibird.gif\" alt=\"delibird\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/delibird\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/delibird.gif\" alt=\"delibird\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/delibird\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/delibird.gif\" alt=\"delibird\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/delibird\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/delibird.gif\" alt=\"delibird\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 226,
    "name": "Mantine",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 140,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mantine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mantine.gif\" alt=\"mantine\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mantine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mantine.gif\" alt=\"mantine\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mantine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mantine.gif\" alt=\"mantine\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mantine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mantine.gif\" alt=\"mantine\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 227,
    "name": "Skarmory",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 140,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skarmory\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/skarmory.gif\" alt=\"skarmory\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skarmory\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/skarmory.gif\" alt=\"skarmory\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skarmory\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/skarmory.gif\" alt=\"skarmory\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skarmory\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/skarmory.gif\" alt=\"skarmory\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 228,
    "name": "Houndour",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/houndour\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/houndour.gif\" alt=\"houndour\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/houndour\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/houndour.gif\" alt=\"houndour\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/houndour\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/houndour.gif\" alt=\"houndour\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/houndour\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/houndour.gif\" alt=\"houndour\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 229,
    "name": "Houndoom",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 110,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/houndoom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/houndoom.gif\" alt=\"houndoom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/houndoom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/houndoom.gif\" alt=\"houndoom\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/houndoom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/houndoom.gif\" alt=\"houndoom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/houndoom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/houndoom.gif\" alt=\"houndoom\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 230,
    "name": "Kingdra",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kingdra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kingdra.gif\" alt=\"kingdra\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kingdra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kingdra.gif\" alt=\"kingdra\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kingdra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kingdra.gif\" alt=\"kingdra\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kingdra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kingdra.gif\" alt=\"kingdra\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 231,
    "name": "Phanpy",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/phanpy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/phanpy.gif\" alt=\"phanpy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/phanpy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/phanpy.gif\" alt=\"phanpy\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/phanpy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/phanpy.gif\" alt=\"phanpy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/phanpy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/phanpy.gif\" alt=\"phanpy\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 232,
    "name": "Donphan",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 120,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/donphan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/donphan.gif\" alt=\"donphan\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/donphan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/donphan.gif\" alt=\"donphan\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/donphan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/donphan.gif\" alt=\"donphan\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/donphan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/donphan.gif\" alt=\"donphan\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 233,
    "name": "Porygon2",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/porygon2\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/porygon2.gif\" alt=\"porygon2\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/porygon2\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/porygon2.gif\" alt=\"porygon2\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/porygon2\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/porygon2.gif\" alt=\"porygon2\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/porygon2\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/porygon2.gif\" alt=\"porygon2\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 234,
    "name": "Stantler",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 73,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 62,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stantler\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/stantler.gif\" alt=\"stantler\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stantler\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/stantler.gif\" alt=\"stantler\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stantler\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/stantler.gif\" alt=\"stantler\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stantler\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/stantler.gif\" alt=\"stantler\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 235,
    "name": "Smeargle",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 20,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 20,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 75
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/smeargle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/smeargle.gif\" alt=\"smeargle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/smeargle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/smeargle.gif\" alt=\"smeargle\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/smeargle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/smeargle.gif\" alt=\"smeargle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/smeargle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/smeargle.gif\" alt=\"smeargle\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 236,
    "name": "Tyrogue",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 35,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tyrogue\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tyrogue.gif\" alt=\"tyrogue\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tyrogue\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tyrogue.gif\" alt=\"tyrogue\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tyrogue\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tyrogue.gif\" alt=\"tyrogue\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tyrogue\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tyrogue.gif\" alt=\"tyrogue\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 237,
    "name": "Hitmontop",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 110,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hitmontop\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/hitmontop.gif\" alt=\"hitmontop\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hitmontop\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/hitmontop.gif\" alt=\"hitmontop\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hitmontop\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/hitmontop.gif\" alt=\"hitmontop\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hitmontop\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/hitmontop.gif\" alt=\"hitmontop\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 238,
    "name": "Smoochum",
    "type": [
      "Ice",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 15,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/smoochum\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/smoochum.gif\" alt=\"smoochum\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/smoochum\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/smoochum.gif\" alt=\"smoochum\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/smoochum\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/smoochum.gif\" alt=\"smoochum\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/smoochum\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/smoochum.gif\" alt=\"smoochum\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 239,
    "name": "Elekid",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 63,
      "Defense": 37,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/elekid\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/elekid.gif\" alt=\"elekid\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/elekid\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/elekid.gif\" alt=\"elekid\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/elekid\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/elekid.gif\" alt=\"elekid\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/elekid\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/elekid.gif\" alt=\"elekid\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 240,
    "name": "Magby",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 37,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 83
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magby\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/magby.gif\" alt=\"magby\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magby\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/magby.gif\" alt=\"magby\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magby\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/magby.gif\" alt=\"magby\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magby\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/magby.gif\" alt=\"magby\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 241,
    "name": "Miltank",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 105,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/miltank\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/miltank.gif\" alt=\"miltank\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/miltank\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/miltank.gif\" alt=\"miltank\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/miltank\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/miltank.gif\" alt=\"miltank\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/miltank\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/miltank.gif\" alt=\"miltank\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 242,
    "name": "Blissey",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 255,
      "Attack": 10,
      "Defense": 10,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 135,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blissey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/blissey.gif\" alt=\"blissey\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blissey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/blissey.gif\" alt=\"blissey\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blissey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/blissey.gif\" alt=\"blissey\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blissey\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/blissey.gif\" alt=\"blissey\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 243,
    "name": "Raikou",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 115,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 115
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/raikou\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/raikou.gif\" alt=\"raikou\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/raikou\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/raikou.gif\" alt=\"raikou\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/raikou\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/raikou.gif\" alt=\"raikou\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/raikou\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/raikou.gif\" alt=\"raikou\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 244,
    "name": "Entei",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 115,
      "Attack": 115,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/entei\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/entei.gif\" alt=\"entei\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/entei\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/entei.gif\" alt=\"entei\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/entei\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/entei.gif\" alt=\"entei\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/entei\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/entei.gif\" alt=\"entei\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 245,
    "name": "Suicune",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 115,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 115,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/suicune\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/suicune.gif\" alt=\"suicune\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/suicune\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/suicune.gif\" alt=\"suicune\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/suicune\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/suicune.gif\" alt=\"suicune\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/suicune\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/suicune.gif\" alt=\"suicune\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 246,
    "name": "Larvitar",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 64,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 41
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/larvitar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/larvitar.gif\" alt=\"larvitar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/larvitar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/larvitar.gif\" alt=\"larvitar\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/larvitar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/larvitar.gif\" alt=\"larvitar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/larvitar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/larvitar.gif\" alt=\"larvitar\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 247,
    "name": "Pupitar",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 84,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 51
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pupitar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pupitar.gif\" alt=\"pupitar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pupitar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pupitar.gif\" alt=\"pupitar\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pupitar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pupitar.gif\" alt=\"pupitar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pupitar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pupitar.gif\" alt=\"pupitar\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 248,
    "name": "Tyranitar",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 134,
      "Defense": 110,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 61
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tyranitar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tyranitar.gif\" alt=\"tyranitar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tyranitar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tyranitar.gif\" alt=\"tyranitar\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tyranitar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tyranitar.gif\" alt=\"tyranitar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tyranitar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tyranitar.gif\" alt=\"tyranitar\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 249,
    "name": "Lugia",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 106,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 130,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 154,
      "Speed": 110
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lugia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lugia.gif\" alt=\"lugia\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lugia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lugia.gif\" alt=\"lugia\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lugia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lugia.gif\" alt=\"lugia\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lugia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lugia.gif\" alt=\"lugia\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 250,
    "name": "Ho-Oh",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 106,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 110,
      "Sp. Defense": 154,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ho-oh\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ho-oh.gif\" alt=\"ho-oh\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ho-oh\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ho-oh.gif\" alt=\"ho-oh\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ho-oh\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ho-oh.gif\" alt=\"ho-oh\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ho-oh\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ho-oh.gif\" alt=\"ho-oh\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 251,
    "name": "Celebi",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/celebi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/celebi.gif\" alt=\"celebi\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/celebi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/celebi.gif\" alt=\"celebi\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/celebi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/celebi.gif\" alt=\"celebi\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/celebi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/celebi.gif\" alt=\"celebi\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 252,
    "name": "Treecko",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/treecko\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/treecko.gif\" alt=\"treecko\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/treecko\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/treecko.gif\" alt=\"treecko\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/treecko\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/treecko.gif\" alt=\"treecko\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/treecko\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/treecko.gif\" alt=\"treecko\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 253,
    "name": "Grovyle",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grovyle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/grovyle.gif\" alt=\"grovyle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grovyle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/grovyle.gif\" alt=\"grovyle\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grovyle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/grovyle.gif\" alt=\"grovyle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grovyle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/grovyle.gif\" alt=\"grovyle\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 254,
    "name": "Sceptile",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 120
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sceptile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sceptile.gif\" alt=\"sceptile\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sceptile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sceptile.gif\" alt=\"sceptile\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sceptile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sceptile.gif\" alt=\"sceptile\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sceptile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sceptile.gif\" alt=\"sceptile\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 255,
    "name": "Torchic",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/torchic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/torchic.gif\" alt=\"torchic\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/torchic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/torchic.gif\" alt=\"torchic\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/torchic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/torchic.gif\" alt=\"torchic\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/torchic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/torchic.gif\" alt=\"torchic\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 256,
    "name": "Combusken",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/combusken\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/combusken.gif\" alt=\"combusken\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/combusken\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/combusken.gif\" alt=\"combusken\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/combusken\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/combusken.gif\" alt=\"combusken\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/combusken\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/combusken.gif\" alt=\"combusken\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 257,
    "name": "Blaziken",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 110,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blaziken\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/blaziken.gif\" alt=\"blaziken\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blaziken\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/blaziken.gif\" alt=\"blaziken\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blaziken\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/blaziken.gif\" alt=\"blaziken\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blaziken\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/blaziken.gif\" alt=\"blaziken\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 258,
    "name": "Mudkip",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mudkip\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mudkip.gif\" alt=\"mudkip\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mudkip\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mudkip.gif\" alt=\"mudkip\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mudkip\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mudkip.gif\" alt=\"mudkip\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mudkip\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mudkip.gif\" alt=\"mudkip\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 259,
    "name": "Marshtomp",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/marshtomp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/marshtomp.gif\" alt=\"marshtomp\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/marshtomp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/marshtomp.gif\" alt=\"marshtomp\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/marshtomp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/marshtomp.gif\" alt=\"marshtomp\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/marshtomp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/marshtomp.gif\" alt=\"marshtomp\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 260,
    "name": "Swampert",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 110,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swampert\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/swampert.gif\" alt=\"swampert\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swampert\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/swampert.gif\" alt=\"swampert\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swampert\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/swampert.gif\" alt=\"swampert\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swampert\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/swampert.gif\" alt=\"swampert\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 261,
    "name": "Poochyena",
    "type": [
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poochyena\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/poochyena.gif\" alt=\"poochyena\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poochyena\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/poochyena.gif\" alt=\"poochyena\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poochyena\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/poochyena.gif\" alt=\"poochyena\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/poochyena\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/poochyena.gif\" alt=\"poochyena\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 262,
    "name": "Mightyena",
    "type": [
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mightyena\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mightyena.gif\" alt=\"mightyena\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mightyena\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mightyena.gif\" alt=\"mightyena\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mightyena\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mightyena.gif\" alt=\"mightyena\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mightyena\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mightyena.gif\" alt=\"mightyena\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 263,
    "name": "Zigzagoon",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 38,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 41,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 41,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zigzagoon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/zigzagoon.gif\" alt=\"zigzagoon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zigzagoon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/zigzagoon.gif\" alt=\"zigzagoon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zigzagoon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/zigzagoon.gif\" alt=\"zigzagoon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zigzagoon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/zigzagoon.gif\" alt=\"zigzagoon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 264,
    "name": "Linoone",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 78,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 61,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 61,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/linoone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/linoone.gif\" alt=\"linoone\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/linoone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/linoone.gif\" alt=\"linoone\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/linoone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/linoone.gif\" alt=\"linoone\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/linoone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/linoone.gif\" alt=\"linoone\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 265,
    "name": "Wurmple",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 20,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wurmple\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/wurmple.gif\" alt=\"wurmple\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wurmple\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/wurmple.gif\" alt=\"wurmple\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wurmple\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/wurmple.gif\" alt=\"wurmple\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wurmple\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/wurmple.gif\" alt=\"wurmple\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 266,
    "name": "Silcoon",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 35,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 25,
      "Sp. Defense": 25,
      "Speed": 15
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/silcoon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/silcoon.gif\" alt=\"silcoon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/silcoon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/silcoon.gif\" alt=\"silcoon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/silcoon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/silcoon.gif\" alt=\"silcoon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/silcoon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/silcoon.gif\" alt=\"silcoon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 267,
    "name": "Beautifly",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beautifly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/beautifly.gif\" alt=\"beautifly\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beautifly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/beautifly.gif\" alt=\"beautifly\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beautifly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/beautifly.gif\" alt=\"beautifly\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beautifly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/beautifly.gif\" alt=\"beautifly\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 268,
    "name": "Cascoon",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 35,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 25,
      "Sp. Defense": 25,
      "Speed": 15
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cascoon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cascoon.gif\" alt=\"cascoon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cascoon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cascoon.gif\" alt=\"cascoon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cascoon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cascoon.gif\" alt=\"cascoon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cascoon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cascoon.gif\" alt=\"cascoon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 269,
    "name": "Dustox",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dustox\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dustox.gif\" alt=\"dustox\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dustox\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dustox.gif\" alt=\"dustox\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dustox\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dustox.gif\" alt=\"dustox\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dustox\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dustox.gif\" alt=\"dustox\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 270,
    "name": "Lotad",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lotad\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lotad.gif\" alt=\"lotad\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lotad\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lotad.gif\" alt=\"lotad\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lotad\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lotad.gif\" alt=\"lotad\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lotad\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lotad.gif\" alt=\"lotad\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 271,
    "name": "Lombre",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lombre\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lombre.gif\" alt=\"lombre\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lombre\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lombre.gif\" alt=\"lombre\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lombre\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lombre.gif\" alt=\"lombre\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lombre\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lombre.gif\" alt=\"lombre\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 272,
    "name": "Ludicolo",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ludicolo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ludicolo.gif\" alt=\"ludicolo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ludicolo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ludicolo.gif\" alt=\"ludicolo\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ludicolo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ludicolo.gif\" alt=\"ludicolo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ludicolo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ludicolo.gif\" alt=\"ludicolo\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 273,
    "name": "Seedot",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seedot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/seedot.gif\" alt=\"seedot\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seedot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/seedot.gif\" alt=\"seedot\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seedot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/seedot.gif\" alt=\"seedot\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seedot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/seedot.gif\" alt=\"seedot\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 274,
    "name": "Nuzleaf",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nuzleaf\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/nuzleaf.gif\" alt=\"nuzleaf\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nuzleaf\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/nuzleaf.gif\" alt=\"nuzleaf\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nuzleaf\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/nuzleaf.gif\" alt=\"nuzleaf\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nuzleaf\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/nuzleaf.gif\" alt=\"nuzleaf\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 275,
    "name": "Shiftry",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shiftry\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/shiftry.gif\" alt=\"shiftry\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shiftry\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/shiftry.gif\" alt=\"shiftry\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shiftry\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/shiftry.gif\" alt=\"shiftry\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shiftry\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/shiftry.gif\" alt=\"shiftry\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 276,
    "name": "Taillow",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/taillow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/taillow.gif\" alt=\"taillow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/taillow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/taillow.gif\" alt=\"taillow\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/taillow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/taillow.gif\" alt=\"taillow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/taillow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/taillow.gif\" alt=\"taillow\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 277,
    "name": "Swellow",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 125
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swellow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/swellow.gif\" alt=\"swellow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swellow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/swellow.gif\" alt=\"swellow\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swellow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/swellow.gif\" alt=\"swellow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swellow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/swellow.gif\" alt=\"swellow\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 278,
    "name": "Wingull",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wingull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/wingull.gif\" alt=\"wingull\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wingull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/wingull.gif\" alt=\"wingull\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wingull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/wingull.gif\" alt=\"wingull\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wingull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/wingull.gif\" alt=\"wingull\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 279,
    "name": "Pelipper",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pelipper\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pelipper.gif\" alt=\"pelipper\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pelipper\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pelipper.gif\" alt=\"pelipper\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pelipper\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pelipper.gif\" alt=\"pelipper\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pelipper\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pelipper.gif\" alt=\"pelipper\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 280,
    "name": "Ralts",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 28,
      "Attack": 25,
      "Defense": 25,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ralts\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ralts.gif\" alt=\"ralts\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ralts\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ralts.gif\" alt=\"ralts\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ralts\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ralts.gif\" alt=\"ralts\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ralts\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ralts.gif\" alt=\"ralts\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 281,
    "name": "Kirlia",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 38,
      "Attack": 35,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kirlia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kirlia.gif\" alt=\"kirlia\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kirlia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kirlia.gif\" alt=\"kirlia\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kirlia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kirlia.gif\" alt=\"kirlia\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kirlia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kirlia.gif\" alt=\"kirlia\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 282,
    "name": "Gardevoir",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 68,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 115,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gardevoir\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gardevoir.gif\" alt=\"gardevoir\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gardevoir\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gardevoir.gif\" alt=\"gardevoir\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gardevoir\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gardevoir.gif\" alt=\"gardevoir\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gardevoir\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gardevoir.gif\" alt=\"gardevoir\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 283,
    "name": "Surskit",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 32,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 52,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/surskit\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/surskit.gif\" alt=\"surskit\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/surskit\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/surskit.gif\" alt=\"surskit\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/surskit\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/surskit.gif\" alt=\"surskit\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/surskit\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/surskit.gif\" alt=\"surskit\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 284,
    "name": "Masquerain",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 62,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 82,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/masquerain\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/masquerain.gif\" alt=\"masquerain\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/masquerain\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/masquerain.gif\" alt=\"masquerain\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/masquerain\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/masquerain.gif\" alt=\"masquerain\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/masquerain\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/masquerain.gif\" alt=\"masquerain\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 285,
    "name": "Shroomish",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shroomish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/shroomish.gif\" alt=\"shroomish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shroomish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/shroomish.gif\" alt=\"shroomish\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shroomish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/shroomish.gif\" alt=\"shroomish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shroomish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/shroomish.gif\" alt=\"shroomish\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 286,
    "name": "Breloom",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/breloom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/breloom.gif\" alt=\"breloom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/breloom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/breloom.gif\" alt=\"breloom\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/breloom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/breloom.gif\" alt=\"breloom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/breloom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/breloom.gif\" alt=\"breloom\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 287,
    "name": "Slakoth",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slakoth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/slakoth.gif\" alt=\"slakoth\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slakoth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/slakoth.gif\" alt=\"slakoth\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slakoth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/slakoth.gif\" alt=\"slakoth\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slakoth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/slakoth.gif\" alt=\"slakoth\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 288,
    "name": "Vigoroth",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vigoroth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/vigoroth.gif\" alt=\"vigoroth\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vigoroth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/vigoroth.gif\" alt=\"vigoroth\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vigoroth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/vigoroth.gif\" alt=\"vigoroth\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vigoroth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/vigoroth.gif\" alt=\"vigoroth\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 289,
    "name": "Slaking",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 150,
      "Attack": 160,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slaking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/slaking.gif\" alt=\"slaking\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slaking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/slaking.gif\" alt=\"slaking\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slaking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/slaking.gif\" alt=\"slaking\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/slaking\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/slaking.gif\" alt=\"slaking\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 290,
    "name": "Nincada",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 31,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nincada\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/nincada.gif\" alt=\"nincada\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nincada\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/nincada.gif\" alt=\"nincada\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nincada\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/nincada.gif\" alt=\"nincada\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nincada\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/nincada.gif\" alt=\"nincada\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 291,
    "name": "Ninjask",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 61,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 160
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ninjask\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ninjask.gif\" alt=\"ninjask\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ninjask\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ninjask.gif\" alt=\"ninjask\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ninjask\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ninjask.gif\" alt=\"ninjask\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ninjask\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ninjask.gif\" alt=\"ninjask\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 292,
    "name": "Shedinja",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 1,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shedinja\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/shedinja.gif\" alt=\"shedinja\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shedinja\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/shedinja.gif\" alt=\"shedinja\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shedinja\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/shedinja.gif\" alt=\"shedinja\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shedinja\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/shedinja.gif\" alt=\"shedinja\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 293,
    "name": "Whismur",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 64,
      "Attack": 51,
      "Defense": 23,
      "Sp. Attack": 51,
      "Sp. Defense": 23,
      "Speed": 28
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whismur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/whismur.gif\" alt=\"whismur\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whismur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/whismur.gif\" alt=\"whismur\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whismur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/whismur.gif\" alt=\"whismur\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whismur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/whismur.gif\" alt=\"whismur\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 294,
    "name": "Loudred",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 84,
      "Attack": 71,
      "Defense": 43,
      "Sp. Attack": 71,
      "Sp. Defense": 43,
      "Speed": 48
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/loudred\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/loudred.gif\" alt=\"loudred\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/loudred\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/loudred.gif\" alt=\"loudred\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/loudred\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/loudred.gif\" alt=\"loudred\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/loudred\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/loudred.gif\" alt=\"loudred\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 295,
    "name": "Exploud",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 104,
      "Attack": 91,
      "Defense": 63,
      "Sp. Attack": 91,
      "Sp. Defense": 73,
      "Speed": 68
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/exploud\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/exploud.gif\" alt=\"exploud\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/exploud\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/exploud.gif\" alt=\"exploud\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/exploud\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/exploud.gif\" alt=\"exploud\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/exploud\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/exploud.gif\" alt=\"exploud\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 296,
    "name": "Makuhita",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 72,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 20,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 25
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/makuhita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/makuhita.gif\" alt=\"makuhita\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/makuhita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/makuhita.gif\" alt=\"makuhita\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/makuhita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/makuhita.gif\" alt=\"makuhita\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/makuhita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/makuhita.gif\" alt=\"makuhita\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 297,
    "name": "Hariyama",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 144,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hariyama\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/hariyama.gif\" alt=\"hariyama\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hariyama\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/hariyama.gif\" alt=\"hariyama\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hariyama\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/hariyama.gif\" alt=\"hariyama\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hariyama\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/hariyama.gif\" alt=\"hariyama\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 298,
    "name": "Azurill",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 20,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 20,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/azurill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/azurill.gif\" alt=\"azurill\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/azurill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/azurill.gif\" alt=\"azurill\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/azurill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/azurill.gif\" alt=\"azurill\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/azurill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/azurill.gif\" alt=\"azurill\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 299,
    "name": "Nosepass",
    "type": [
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 135,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nosepass\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/nosepass.gif\" alt=\"nosepass\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nosepass\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/nosepass.gif\" alt=\"nosepass\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nosepass\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/nosepass.gif\" alt=\"nosepass\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/nosepass\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/nosepass.gif\" alt=\"nosepass\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 300,
    "name": "Skitty",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skitty\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/skitty.gif\" alt=\"skitty\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skitty\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/skitty.gif\" alt=\"skitty\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skitty\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/skitty.gif\" alt=\"skitty\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skitty\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/skitty.gif\" alt=\"skitty\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 301,
    "name": "Delcatty",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/delcatty\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/delcatty.gif\" alt=\"delcatty\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/delcatty\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/delcatty.gif\" alt=\"delcatty\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/delcatty\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/delcatty.gif\" alt=\"delcatty\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/delcatty\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/delcatty.gif\" alt=\"delcatty\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 302,
    "name": "Sableye",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sableye\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sableye.gif\" alt=\"sableye\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sableye\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sableye.gif\" alt=\"sableye\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sableye\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sableye.gif\" alt=\"sableye\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sableye\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sableye.gif\" alt=\"sableye\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 303,
    "name": "Mawile",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mawile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mawile.gif\" alt=\"mawile\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mawile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mawile.gif\" alt=\"mawile\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mawile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mawile.gif\" alt=\"mawile\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mawile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mawile.gif\" alt=\"mawile\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 304,
    "name": "Aron",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aron\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/aron.gif\" alt=\"aron\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aron\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/aron.gif\" alt=\"aron\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aron\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/aron.gif\" alt=\"aron\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aron\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/aron.gif\" alt=\"aron\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 305,
    "name": "Lairon",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 140,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lairon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lairon.gif\" alt=\"lairon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lairon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lairon.gif\" alt=\"lairon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lairon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lairon.gif\" alt=\"lairon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lairon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lairon.gif\" alt=\"lairon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 306,
    "name": "Aggron",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 110,
      "Defense": 180,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aggron\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/aggron.gif\" alt=\"aggron\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aggron\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/aggron.gif\" alt=\"aggron\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aggron\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/aggron.gif\" alt=\"aggron\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/aggron\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/aggron.gif\" alt=\"aggron\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 307,
    "name": "Meditite",
    "type": [
      "Fighting",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meditite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/meditite.gif\" alt=\"meditite\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meditite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/meditite.gif\" alt=\"meditite\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meditite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/meditite.gif\" alt=\"meditite\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meditite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/meditite.gif\" alt=\"meditite\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 308,
    "name": "Medicham",
    "type": [
      "Fighting",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/medicham\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/medicham.gif\" alt=\"medicham\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/medicham\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/medicham.gif\" alt=\"medicham\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/medicham\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/medicham.gif\" alt=\"medicham\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/medicham\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/medicham.gif\" alt=\"medicham\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 309,
    "name": "Electrike",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electrike\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/electrike.gif\" alt=\"electrike\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electrike\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/electrike.gif\" alt=\"electrike\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electrike\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/electrike.gif\" alt=\"electrike\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electrike\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/electrike.gif\" alt=\"electrike\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 310,
    "name": "Manectric",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 105
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/manectric\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/manectric.gif\" alt=\"manectric\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/manectric\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/manectric.gif\" alt=\"manectric\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/manectric\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/manectric.gif\" alt=\"manectric\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/manectric\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/manectric.gif\" alt=\"manectric\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 311,
    "name": "Plusle",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/plusle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/plusle.gif\" alt=\"plusle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/plusle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/plusle.gif\" alt=\"plusle\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/plusle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/plusle.gif\" alt=\"plusle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/plusle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/plusle.gif\" alt=\"plusle\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 312,
    "name": "Minun",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/minun\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/minun.gif\" alt=\"minun\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/minun\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/minun.gif\" alt=\"minun\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/minun\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/minun.gif\" alt=\"minun\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/minun\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/minun.gif\" alt=\"minun\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 313,
    "name": "Volbeat",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 73,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 47,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/volbeat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/volbeat.gif\" alt=\"volbeat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/volbeat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/volbeat.gif\" alt=\"volbeat\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/volbeat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/volbeat.gif\" alt=\"volbeat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/volbeat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/volbeat.gif\" alt=\"volbeat\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 314,
    "name": "Illumise",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 47,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 73,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/illumise\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/illumise.gif\" alt=\"illumise\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/illumise\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/illumise.gif\" alt=\"illumise\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/illumise\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/illumise.gif\" alt=\"illumise\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/illumise\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/illumise.gif\" alt=\"illumise\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 315,
    "name": "Roselia",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/roselia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/roselia.gif\" alt=\"roselia\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/roselia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/roselia.gif\" alt=\"roselia\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/roselia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/roselia.gif\" alt=\"roselia\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/roselia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/roselia.gif\" alt=\"roselia\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 316,
    "name": "Gulpin",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 43,
      "Defense": 53,
      "Sp. Attack": 43,
      "Sp. Defense": 53,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gulpin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gulpin.gif\" alt=\"gulpin\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gulpin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gulpin.gif\" alt=\"gulpin\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gulpin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gulpin.gif\" alt=\"gulpin\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gulpin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gulpin.gif\" alt=\"gulpin\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 317,
    "name": "Swalot",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 73,
      "Defense": 83,
      "Sp. Attack": 73,
      "Sp. Defense": 83,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swalot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/swalot.gif\" alt=\"swalot\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swalot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/swalot.gif\" alt=\"swalot\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swalot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/swalot.gif\" alt=\"swalot\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swalot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/swalot.gif\" alt=\"swalot\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 318,
    "name": "Carvanha",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 20,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 20,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/carvanha\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/carvanha.gif\" alt=\"carvanha\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/carvanha\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/carvanha.gif\" alt=\"carvanha\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/carvanha\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/carvanha.gif\" alt=\"carvanha\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/carvanha\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/carvanha.gif\" alt=\"carvanha\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 319,
    "name": "Sharpedo",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sharpedo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sharpedo.gif\" alt=\"sharpedo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sharpedo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sharpedo.gif\" alt=\"sharpedo\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sharpedo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sharpedo.gif\" alt=\"sharpedo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sharpedo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sharpedo.gif\" alt=\"sharpedo\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 320,
    "name": "Wailmer",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 130,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wailmer\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/wailmer.gif\" alt=\"wailmer\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wailmer\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/wailmer.gif\" alt=\"wailmer\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wailmer\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/wailmer.gif\" alt=\"wailmer\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wailmer\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/wailmer.gif\" alt=\"wailmer\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 321,
    "name": "Wailord",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 170,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wailord\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/wailord.gif\" alt=\"wailord\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wailord\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/wailord.gif\" alt=\"wailord\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wailord\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/wailord.gif\" alt=\"wailord\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wailord\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/wailord.gif\" alt=\"wailord\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 322,
    "name": "Numel",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/numel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/numel.gif\" alt=\"numel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/numel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/numel.gif\" alt=\"numel\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/numel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/numel.gif\" alt=\"numel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/numel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/numel.gif\" alt=\"numel\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 323,
    "name": "Camerupt",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/camerupt\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/camerupt.gif\" alt=\"camerupt\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/camerupt\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/camerupt.gif\" alt=\"camerupt\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/camerupt\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/camerupt.gif\" alt=\"camerupt\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/camerupt\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/camerupt.gif\" alt=\"camerupt\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 324,
    "name": "Torkoal",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 140,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/torkoal\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/torkoal.gif\" alt=\"torkoal\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/torkoal\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/torkoal.gif\" alt=\"torkoal\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/torkoal\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/torkoal.gif\" alt=\"torkoal\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/torkoal\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/torkoal.gif\" alt=\"torkoal\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 325,
    "name": "Spoink",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 25,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spoink\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/spoink.gif\" alt=\"spoink\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spoink\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/spoink.gif\" alt=\"spoink\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spoink\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/spoink.gif\" alt=\"spoink\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spoink\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/spoink.gif\" alt=\"spoink\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 326,
    "name": "Grumpig",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 110,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grumpig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/grumpig.gif\" alt=\"grumpig\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grumpig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/grumpig.gif\" alt=\"grumpig\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grumpig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/grumpig.gif\" alt=\"grumpig\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grumpig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/grumpig.gif\" alt=\"grumpig\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 327,
    "name": "Spinda",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spinda\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/spinda.gif\" alt=\"spinda\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spinda\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/spinda.gif\" alt=\"spinda\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spinda\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/spinda.gif\" alt=\"spinda\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spinda\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/spinda.gif\" alt=\"spinda\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 328,
    "name": "Trapinch",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 10
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/trapinch\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/trapinch.gif\" alt=\"trapinch\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/trapinch\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/trapinch.gif\" alt=\"trapinch\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/trapinch\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/trapinch.gif\" alt=\"trapinch\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/trapinch\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/trapinch.gif\" alt=\"trapinch\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 329,
    "name": "Vibrava",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vibrava\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/vibrava.gif\" alt=\"vibrava\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vibrava\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/vibrava.gif\" alt=\"vibrava\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vibrava\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/vibrava.gif\" alt=\"vibrava\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vibrava\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/vibrava.gif\" alt=\"vibrava\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 330,
    "name": "Flygon",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/flygon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/flygon.gif\" alt=\"flygon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/flygon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/flygon.gif\" alt=\"flygon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/flygon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/flygon.gif\" alt=\"flygon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/flygon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/flygon.gif\" alt=\"flygon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 331,
    "name": "Cacnea",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cacnea\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cacnea.gif\" alt=\"cacnea\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cacnea\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cacnea.gif\" alt=\"cacnea\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cacnea\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cacnea.gif\" alt=\"cacnea\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cacnea\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cacnea.gif\" alt=\"cacnea\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 332,
    "name": "Cacturne",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 115,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 115,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cacturne\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cacturne.gif\" alt=\"cacturne\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cacturne\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cacturne.gif\" alt=\"cacturne\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cacturne\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cacturne.gif\" alt=\"cacturne\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cacturne\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cacturne.gif\" alt=\"cacturne\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 333,
    "name": "Swablu",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swablu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/swablu.gif\" alt=\"swablu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swablu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/swablu.gif\" alt=\"swablu\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swablu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/swablu.gif\" alt=\"swablu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swablu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/swablu.gif\" alt=\"swablu\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 334,
    "name": "Altaria",
    "type": [
      "Dragon",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 105,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/altaria\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/altaria.gif\" alt=\"altaria\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/altaria\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/altaria.gif\" alt=\"altaria\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/altaria\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/altaria.gif\" alt=\"altaria\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/altaria\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/altaria.gif\" alt=\"altaria\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 335,
    "name": "Zangoose",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 73,
      "Attack": 115,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zangoose\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/zangoose.gif\" alt=\"zangoose\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zangoose\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/zangoose.gif\" alt=\"zangoose\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zangoose\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/zangoose.gif\" alt=\"zangoose\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zangoose\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/zangoose.gif\" alt=\"zangoose\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 336,
    "name": "Seviper",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 73,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seviper\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/seviper.gif\" alt=\"seviper\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seviper\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/seviper.gif\" alt=\"seviper\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seviper\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/seviper.gif\" alt=\"seviper\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seviper\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/seviper.gif\" alt=\"seviper\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 337,
    "name": "Lunatone",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lunatone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lunatone.gif\" alt=\"lunatone\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lunatone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lunatone.gif\" alt=\"lunatone\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lunatone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lunatone.gif\" alt=\"lunatone\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lunatone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lunatone.gif\" alt=\"lunatone\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 338,
    "name": "Solrock",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/solrock\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/solrock.gif\" alt=\"solrock\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/solrock\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/solrock.gif\" alt=\"solrock\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/solrock\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/solrock.gif\" alt=\"solrock\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/solrock\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/solrock.gif\" alt=\"solrock\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 339,
    "name": "Barboach",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 48,
      "Defense": 43,
      "Sp. Attack": 46,
      "Sp. Defense": 41,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/barboach\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/barboach.gif\" alt=\"barboach\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/barboach\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/barboach.gif\" alt=\"barboach\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/barboach\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/barboach.gif\" alt=\"barboach\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/barboach\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/barboach.gif\" alt=\"barboach\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 340,
    "name": "Whiscash",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 110,
      "Attack": 78,
      "Defense": 73,
      "Sp. Attack": 76,
      "Sp. Defense": 71,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whiscash\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/whiscash.gif\" alt=\"whiscash\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whiscash\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/whiscash.gif\" alt=\"whiscash\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whiscash\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/whiscash.gif\" alt=\"whiscash\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whiscash\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/whiscash.gif\" alt=\"whiscash\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 341,
    "name": "Corphish",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 43,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/corphish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/corphish.gif\" alt=\"corphish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/corphish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/corphish.gif\" alt=\"corphish\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/corphish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/corphish.gif\" alt=\"corphish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/corphish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/corphish.gif\" alt=\"corphish\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 342,
    "name": "Crawdaunt",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 63,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/crawdaunt\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/crawdaunt.gif\" alt=\"crawdaunt\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/crawdaunt\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/crawdaunt.gif\" alt=\"crawdaunt\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/crawdaunt\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/crawdaunt.gif\" alt=\"crawdaunt\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/crawdaunt\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/crawdaunt.gif\" alt=\"crawdaunt\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 343,
    "name": "Baltoy",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/baltoy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/baltoy.gif\" alt=\"baltoy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/baltoy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/baltoy.gif\" alt=\"baltoy\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/baltoy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/baltoy.gif\" alt=\"baltoy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/baltoy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/baltoy.gif\" alt=\"baltoy\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 344,
    "name": "Claydol",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 105,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 120,
      "Speed": 75
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/claydol\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/claydol.gif\" alt=\"claydol\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/claydol\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/claydol.gif\" alt=\"claydol\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/claydol\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/claydol.gif\" alt=\"claydol\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/claydol\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/claydol.gif\" alt=\"claydol\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 345,
    "name": "Lileep",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 66,
      "Attack": 41,
      "Defense": 77,
      "Sp. Attack": 61,
      "Sp. Defense": 87,
      "Speed": 23
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lileep\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lileep.gif\" alt=\"lileep\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lileep\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lileep.gif\" alt=\"lileep\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lileep\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lileep.gif\" alt=\"lileep\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lileep\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lileep.gif\" alt=\"lileep\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 346,
    "name": "Cradily",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 86,
      "Attack": 81,
      "Defense": 97,
      "Sp. Attack": 81,
      "Sp. Defense": 107,
      "Speed": 43
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cradily\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cradily.gif\" alt=\"cradily\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cradily\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cradily.gif\" alt=\"cradily\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cradily\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cradily.gif\" alt=\"cradily\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cradily\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cradily.gif\" alt=\"cradily\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 347,
    "name": "Anorith",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 75
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/anorith\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/anorith.gif\" alt=\"anorith\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/anorith\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/anorith.gif\" alt=\"anorith\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/anorith\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/anorith.gif\" alt=\"anorith\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/anorith\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/anorith.gif\" alt=\"anorith\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 348,
    "name": "Armaldo",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 125,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/armaldo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/armaldo.gif\" alt=\"armaldo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/armaldo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/armaldo.gif\" alt=\"armaldo\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/armaldo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/armaldo.gif\" alt=\"armaldo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/armaldo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/armaldo.gif\" alt=\"armaldo\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 349,
    "name": "Feebas",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 20,
      "Attack": 15,
      "Defense": 20,
      "Sp. Attack": 10,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/feebas\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/feebas.gif\" alt=\"feebas\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/feebas\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/feebas.gif\" alt=\"feebas\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/feebas\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/feebas.gif\" alt=\"feebas\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/feebas\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/feebas.gif\" alt=\"feebas\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 350,
    "name": "Milotic",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 79,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 125,
      "Speed": 81
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/milotic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/milotic.gif\" alt=\"milotic\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/milotic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/milotic.gif\" alt=\"milotic\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/milotic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/milotic.gif\" alt=\"milotic\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/milotic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/milotic.gif\" alt=\"milotic\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 351,
    "name": "Castform",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/castform\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/castform.gif\" alt=\"castform\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/castform\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/castform.gif\" alt=\"castform\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/castform\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/castform.gif\" alt=\"castform\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/castform\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/castform.gif\" alt=\"castform\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 352,
    "name": "Kecleon",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 120,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kecleon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kecleon.gif\" alt=\"kecleon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kecleon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kecleon.gif\" alt=\"kecleon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kecleon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kecleon.gif\" alt=\"kecleon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kecleon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kecleon.gif\" alt=\"kecleon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 353,
    "name": "Shuppet",
    "type": [
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 44,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 63,
      "Sp. Defense": 33,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shuppet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/shuppet.gif\" alt=\"shuppet\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shuppet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/shuppet.gif\" alt=\"shuppet\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shuppet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/shuppet.gif\" alt=\"shuppet\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shuppet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/shuppet.gif\" alt=\"shuppet\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 354,
    "name": "Banette",
    "type": [
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 64,
      "Attack": 115,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 83,
      "Sp. Defense": 63,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/banette\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/banette.gif\" alt=\"banette\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/banette\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/banette.gif\" alt=\"banette\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/banette\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/banette.gif\" alt=\"banette\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/banette\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/banette.gif\" alt=\"banette\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 355,
    "name": "Duskull",
    "type": [
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 20,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 25
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/duskull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/duskull.gif\" alt=\"duskull\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/duskull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/duskull.gif\" alt=\"duskull\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/duskull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/duskull.gif\" alt=\"duskull\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/duskull\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/duskull.gif\" alt=\"duskull\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 356,
    "name": "Dusclops",
    "type": [
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 130,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 130,
      "Speed": 25
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dusclops\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dusclops.gif\" alt=\"dusclops\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dusclops\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dusclops.gif\" alt=\"dusclops\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dusclops\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dusclops.gif\" alt=\"dusclops\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dusclops\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dusclops.gif\" alt=\"dusclops\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 357,
    "name": "Tropius",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 99,
      "Attack": 68,
      "Defense": 83,
      "Sp. Attack": 72,
      "Sp. Defense": 87,
      "Speed": 51
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tropius\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tropius.gif\" alt=\"tropius\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tropius\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tropius.gif\" alt=\"tropius\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tropius\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tropius.gif\" alt=\"tropius\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tropius\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tropius.gif\" alt=\"tropius\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 358,
    "name": "Chimecho",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chimecho\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/chimecho.gif\" alt=\"chimecho\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chimecho\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/chimecho.gif\" alt=\"chimecho\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chimecho\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/chimecho.gif\" alt=\"chimecho\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chimecho\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/chimecho.gif\" alt=\"chimecho\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 359,
    "name": "Absol",
    "type": [
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 75
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/absol\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/absol.gif\" alt=\"absol\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/absol\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/absol.gif\" alt=\"absol\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/absol\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/absol.gif\" alt=\"absol\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/absol\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/absol.gif\" alt=\"absol\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 360,
    "name": "Wynaut",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 23,
      "Defense": 48,
      "Sp. Attack": 23,
      "Sp. Defense": 48,
      "Speed": 23
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wynaut\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/wynaut.gif\" alt=\"wynaut\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wynaut\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/wynaut.gif\" alt=\"wynaut\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wynaut\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/wynaut.gif\" alt=\"wynaut\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wynaut\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/wynaut.gif\" alt=\"wynaut\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 361,
    "name": "Snorunt",
    "type": [
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snorunt\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/snorunt.gif\" alt=\"snorunt\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snorunt\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/snorunt.gif\" alt=\"snorunt\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snorunt\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/snorunt.gif\" alt=\"snorunt\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snorunt\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/snorunt.gif\" alt=\"snorunt\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 362,
    "name": "Glalie",
    "type": [
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/glalie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/glalie.gif\" alt=\"glalie\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/glalie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/glalie.gif\" alt=\"glalie\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/glalie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/glalie.gif\" alt=\"glalie\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/glalie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/glalie.gif\" alt=\"glalie\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 363,
    "name": "Spheal",
    "type": [
      "Ice",
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 25
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spheal\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/spheal.gif\" alt=\"spheal\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spheal\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/spheal.gif\" alt=\"spheal\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spheal\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/spheal.gif\" alt=\"spheal\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spheal\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/spheal.gif\" alt=\"spheal\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 364,
    "name": "Sealeo",
    "type": [
      "Ice",
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sealeo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sealeo.gif\" alt=\"sealeo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sealeo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sealeo.gif\" alt=\"sealeo\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sealeo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sealeo.gif\" alt=\"sealeo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sealeo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sealeo.gif\" alt=\"sealeo\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 365,
    "name": "Walrein",
    "type": [
      "Ice",
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 110,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/walrein\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/walrein.gif\" alt=\"walrein\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/walrein\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/walrein.gif\" alt=\"walrein\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/walrein\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/walrein.gif\" alt=\"walrein\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/walrein\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/walrein.gif\" alt=\"walrein\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 366,
    "name": "Clamperl",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 64,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 74,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 32
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/clamperl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/clamperl.gif\" alt=\"clamperl\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/clamperl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/clamperl.gif\" alt=\"clamperl\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/clamperl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/clamperl.gif\" alt=\"clamperl\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/clamperl\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/clamperl.gif\" alt=\"clamperl\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 367,
    "name": "Huntail",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 104,
      "Defense": 105,
      "Sp. Attack": 94,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 52
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/huntail\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/huntail.gif\" alt=\"huntail\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/huntail\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/huntail.gif\" alt=\"huntail\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/huntail\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/huntail.gif\" alt=\"huntail\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/huntail\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/huntail.gif\" alt=\"huntail\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 368,
    "name": "Gorebyss",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 84,
      "Defense": 105,
      "Sp. Attack": 114,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 52
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gorebyss\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gorebyss.gif\" alt=\"gorebyss\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gorebyss\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gorebyss.gif\" alt=\"gorebyss\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gorebyss\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gorebyss.gif\" alt=\"gorebyss\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gorebyss\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gorebyss.gif\" alt=\"gorebyss\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 369,
    "name": "Relicanth",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 130,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/relicanth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/relicanth.gif\" alt=\"relicanth\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/relicanth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/relicanth.gif\" alt=\"relicanth\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/relicanth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/relicanth.gif\" alt=\"relicanth\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/relicanth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/relicanth.gif\" alt=\"relicanth\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 370,
    "name": "Luvdisc",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 43,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 97
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/luvdisc\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/luvdisc.gif\" alt=\"luvdisc\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/luvdisc\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/luvdisc.gif\" alt=\"luvdisc\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/luvdisc\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/luvdisc.gif\" alt=\"luvdisc\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/luvdisc\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/luvdisc.gif\" alt=\"luvdisc\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 371,
    "name": "Bagon",
    "type": [
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bagon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bagon.gif\" alt=\"bagon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bagon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bagon.gif\" alt=\"bagon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bagon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bagon.gif\" alt=\"bagon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bagon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bagon.gif\" alt=\"bagon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 372,
    "name": "Shelgon",
    "type": [
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shelgon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/shelgon.gif\" alt=\"shelgon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shelgon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/shelgon.gif\" alt=\"shelgon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shelgon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/shelgon.gif\" alt=\"shelgon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shelgon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/shelgon.gif\" alt=\"shelgon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 373,
    "name": "Salamence",
    "type": [
      "Dragon",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 135,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 110,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/salamence\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/salamence.gif\" alt=\"salamence\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/salamence\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/salamence.gif\" alt=\"salamence\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/salamence\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/salamence.gif\" alt=\"salamence\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/salamence\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/salamence.gif\" alt=\"salamence\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 374,
    "name": "Beldum",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beldum\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/beldum.gif\" alt=\"beldum\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beldum\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/beldum.gif\" alt=\"beldum\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beldum\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/beldum.gif\" alt=\"beldum\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beldum\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/beldum.gif\" alt=\"beldum\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 375,
    "name": "Metang",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/metang\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/metang.gif\" alt=\"metang\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/metang\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/metang.gif\" alt=\"metang\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/metang\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/metang.gif\" alt=\"metang\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/metang\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/metang.gif\" alt=\"metang\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 376,
    "name": "Metagross",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 135,
      "Defense": 130,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/metagross\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/metagross.gif\" alt=\"metagross\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/metagross\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/metagross.gif\" alt=\"metagross\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/metagross\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/metagross.gif\" alt=\"metagross\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/metagross\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/metagross.gif\" alt=\"metagross\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 377,
    "name": "Regirock",
    "type": [
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 200,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/regirock\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/regirock.gif\" alt=\"regirock\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/regirock\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/regirock.gif\" alt=\"regirock\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/regirock\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/regirock.gif\" alt=\"regirock\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/regirock\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/regirock.gif\" alt=\"regirock\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 378,
    "name": "Regice",
    "type": [
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 200,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/regice\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/regice.gif\" alt=\"regice\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/regice\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/regice.gif\" alt=\"regice\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/regice\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/regice.gif\" alt=\"regice\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/regice\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/regice.gif\" alt=\"regice\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 379,
    "name": "Registeel",
    "type": [
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 150,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 150,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/registeel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/registeel.gif\" alt=\"registeel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/registeel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/registeel.gif\" alt=\"registeel\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/registeel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/registeel.gif\" alt=\"registeel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/registeel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/registeel.gif\" alt=\"registeel\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 380,
    "name": "Latias",
    "type": [
      "Dragon",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 110,
      "Sp. Defense": 130,
      "Speed": 110
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/latias\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/latias.gif\" alt=\"latias\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/latias\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/latias.gif\" alt=\"latias\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/latias\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/latias.gif\" alt=\"latias\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/latias\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/latias.gif\" alt=\"latias\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 381,
    "name": "Latios",
    "type": [
      "Dragon",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 130,
      "Sp. Defense": 110,
      "Speed": 110
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/latios\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/latios.gif\" alt=\"latios\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/latios\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/latios.gif\" alt=\"latios\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/latios\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/latios.gif\" alt=\"latios\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/latios\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/latios.gif\" alt=\"latios\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 382,
    "name": "Kyogre",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 150,
      "Sp. Defense": 140,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kyogre\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kyogre.gif\" alt=\"kyogre\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kyogre\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kyogre.gif\" alt=\"kyogre\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kyogre\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kyogre.gif\" alt=\"kyogre\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kyogre\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kyogre.gif\" alt=\"kyogre\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 383,
    "name": "Groudon",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 150,
      "Defense": 140,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/groudon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/groudon.gif\" alt=\"groudon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/groudon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/groudon.gif\" alt=\"groudon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/groudon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/groudon.gif\" alt=\"groudon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/groudon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/groudon.gif\" alt=\"groudon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 384,
    "name": "Rayquaza",
    "type": [
      "Dragon",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 105,
      "Attack": 150,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 150,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rayquaza\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/rayquaza.gif\" alt=\"rayquaza\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rayquaza\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/rayquaza.gif\" alt=\"rayquaza\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rayquaza\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/rayquaza.gif\" alt=\"rayquaza\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rayquaza\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/rayquaza.gif\" alt=\"rayquaza\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 385,
    "name": "Jirachi",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jirachi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/jirachi.gif\" alt=\"jirachi\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jirachi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/jirachi.gif\" alt=\"jirachi\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jirachi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/jirachi.gif\" alt=\"jirachi\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jirachi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/jirachi.gif\" alt=\"jirachi\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 386,
    "name": "Deoxys",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 150,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 150,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 150
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/deoxys\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/deoxys.gif\" alt=\"deoxys\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/deoxys\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/deoxys.gif\" alt=\"deoxys\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/deoxys\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/deoxys.gif\" alt=\"deoxys\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/deoxys\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/deoxys.gif\" alt=\"deoxys\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 387,
    "name": "Turtwig",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 68,
      "Defense": 64,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 31
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/turtwig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/turtwig.gif\" alt=\"turtwig\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/turtwig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/turtwig.gif\" alt=\"turtwig\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/turtwig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/turtwig.gif\" alt=\"turtwig\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/turtwig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/turtwig.gif\" alt=\"turtwig\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 388,
    "name": "Grotle",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 89,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 36
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grotle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/grotle.gif\" alt=\"grotle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grotle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/grotle.gif\" alt=\"grotle\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grotle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/grotle.gif\" alt=\"grotle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/grotle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/grotle.gif\" alt=\"grotle\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 389,
    "name": "Torterra",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 109,
      "Defense": 105,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 56
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/torterra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/torterra.gif\" alt=\"torterra\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/torterra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/torterra.gif\" alt=\"torterra\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/torterra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/torterra.gif\" alt=\"torterra\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/torterra\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/torterra.gif\" alt=\"torterra\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 390,
    "name": "Chimchar",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 44,
      "Attack": 58,
      "Defense": 44,
      "Sp. Attack": 58,
      "Sp. Defense": 44,
      "Speed": 61
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chimchar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/chimchar.gif\" alt=\"chimchar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chimchar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/chimchar.gif\" alt=\"chimchar\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chimchar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/chimchar.gif\" alt=\"chimchar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chimchar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/chimchar.gif\" alt=\"chimchar\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 391,
    "name": "Monferno",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 64,
      "Attack": 78,
      "Defense": 52,
      "Sp. Attack": 78,
      "Sp. Defense": 52,
      "Speed": 81
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/monferno\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/monferno.gif\" alt=\"monferno\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/monferno\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/monferno.gif\" alt=\"monferno\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/monferno\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/monferno.gif\" alt=\"monferno\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/monferno\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/monferno.gif\" alt=\"monferno\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 392,
    "name": "Infernape",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 76,
      "Attack": 104,
      "Defense": 71,
      "Sp. Attack": 104,
      "Sp. Defense": 71,
      "Speed": 108
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/infernape\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/infernape.gif\" alt=\"infernape\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/infernape\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/infernape.gif\" alt=\"infernape\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/infernape\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/infernape.gif\" alt=\"infernape\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/infernape\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/infernape.gif\" alt=\"infernape\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 393,
    "name": "Piplup",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 53,
      "Attack": 51,
      "Defense": 53,
      "Sp. Attack": 61,
      "Sp. Defense": 56,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/piplup\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/piplup.gif\" alt=\"piplup\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/piplup\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/piplup.gif\" alt=\"piplup\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/piplup\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/piplup.gif\" alt=\"piplup\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/piplup\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/piplup.gif\" alt=\"piplup\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 394,
    "name": "Prinplup",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 64,
      "Attack": 66,
      "Defense": 68,
      "Sp. Attack": 81,
      "Sp. Defense": 76,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/prinplup\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/prinplup.gif\" alt=\"prinplup\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/prinplup\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/prinplup.gif\" alt=\"prinplup\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/prinplup\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/prinplup.gif\" alt=\"prinplup\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/prinplup\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/prinplup.gif\" alt=\"prinplup\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 395,
    "name": "Empoleon",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 84,
      "Attack": 86,
      "Defense": 88,
      "Sp. Attack": 111,
      "Sp. Defense": 101,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/empoleon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/empoleon.gif\" alt=\"empoleon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/empoleon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/empoleon.gif\" alt=\"empoleon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/empoleon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/empoleon.gif\" alt=\"empoleon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/empoleon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/empoleon.gif\" alt=\"empoleon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 396,
    "name": "Starly",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 30,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/starly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/starly.gif\" alt=\"starly\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/starly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/starly.gif\" alt=\"starly\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/starly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/starly.gif\" alt=\"starly\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/starly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/starly.gif\" alt=\"starly\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 397,
    "name": "Staravia",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/staravia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/staravia.gif\" alt=\"staravia\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/staravia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/staravia.gif\" alt=\"staravia\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/staravia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/staravia.gif\" alt=\"staravia\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/staravia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/staravia.gif\" alt=\"staravia\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 398,
    "name": "Staraptor",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/staraptor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/staraptor.gif\" alt=\"staraptor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/staraptor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/staraptor.gif\" alt=\"staraptor\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/staraptor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/staraptor.gif\" alt=\"staraptor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/staraptor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/staraptor.gif\" alt=\"staraptor\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 399,
    "name": "Bidoof",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 59,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 31
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bidoof\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bidoof.gif\" alt=\"bidoof\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bidoof\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bidoof.gif\" alt=\"bidoof\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bidoof\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bidoof.gif\" alt=\"bidoof\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bidoof\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bidoof.gif\" alt=\"bidoof\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 400,
    "name": "Bibarel",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 79,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 71
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bibarel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bibarel.gif\" alt=\"bibarel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bibarel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bibarel.gif\" alt=\"bibarel\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bibarel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bibarel.gif\" alt=\"bibarel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bibarel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bibarel.gif\" alt=\"bibarel\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 401,
    "name": "Kricketot",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 37,
      "Attack": 25,
      "Defense": 41,
      "Sp. Attack": 25,
      "Sp. Defense": 41,
      "Speed": 25
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kricketot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kricketot.gif\" alt=\"kricketot\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kricketot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kricketot.gif\" alt=\"kricketot\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kricketot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kricketot.gif\" alt=\"kricketot\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kricketot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kricketot.gif\" alt=\"kricketot\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 402,
    "name": "Kricketune",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 77,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 51,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 51,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kricketune\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kricketune.gif\" alt=\"kricketune\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kricketune\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kricketune.gif\" alt=\"kricketune\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kricketune\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kricketune.gif\" alt=\"kricketune\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kricketune\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kricketune.gif\" alt=\"kricketune\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 403,
    "name": "Shinx",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 34,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 34,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shinx\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/shinx.gif\" alt=\"shinx\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shinx\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/shinx.gif\" alt=\"shinx\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shinx\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/shinx.gif\" alt=\"shinx\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shinx\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/shinx.gif\" alt=\"shinx\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 404,
    "name": "Luxio",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 49,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 49,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/luxio\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/luxio.gif\" alt=\"luxio\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/luxio\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/luxio.gif\" alt=\"luxio\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/luxio\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/luxio.gif\" alt=\"luxio\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/luxio\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/luxio.gif\" alt=\"luxio\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 405,
    "name": "Luxray",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 79,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 79,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/luxray\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/luxray.gif\" alt=\"luxray\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/luxray\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/luxray.gif\" alt=\"luxray\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/luxray\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/luxray.gif\" alt=\"luxray\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/luxray\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/luxray.gif\" alt=\"luxray\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 406,
    "name": "Budew",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/budew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/budew.gif\" alt=\"budew\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/budew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/budew.gif\" alt=\"budew\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/budew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/budew.gif\" alt=\"budew\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/budew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/budew.gif\" alt=\"budew\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 407,
    "name": "Roserade",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 105,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/roserade\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/roserade.gif\" alt=\"roserade\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/roserade\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/roserade.gif\" alt=\"roserade\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/roserade\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/roserade.gif\" alt=\"roserade\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/roserade\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/roserade.gif\" alt=\"roserade\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 408,
    "name": "Cranidos",
    "type": [
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 67,
      "Attack": 125,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 58
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cranidos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cranidos.gif\" alt=\"cranidos\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cranidos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cranidos.gif\" alt=\"cranidos\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cranidos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cranidos.gif\" alt=\"cranidos\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cranidos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cranidos.gif\" alt=\"cranidos\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 409,
    "name": "Rampardos",
    "type": [
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 97,
      "Attack": 165,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 58
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rampardos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/rampardos.gif\" alt=\"rampardos\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rampardos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/rampardos.gif\" alt=\"rampardos\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rampardos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/rampardos.gif\" alt=\"rampardos\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rampardos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/rampardos.gif\" alt=\"rampardos\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 410,
    "name": "Shieldon",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 42,
      "Defense": 118,
      "Sp. Attack": 42,
      "Sp. Defense": 88,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shieldon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/shieldon.gif\" alt=\"shieldon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shieldon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/shieldon.gif\" alt=\"shieldon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shieldon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/shieldon.gif\" alt=\"shieldon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shieldon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/shieldon.gif\" alt=\"shieldon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 411,
    "name": "Bastiodon",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 52,
      "Defense": 168,
      "Sp. Attack": 47,
      "Sp. Defense": 138,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bastiodon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bastiodon.gif\" alt=\"bastiodon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bastiodon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bastiodon.gif\" alt=\"bastiodon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bastiodon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bastiodon.gif\" alt=\"bastiodon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bastiodon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bastiodon.gif\" alt=\"bastiodon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 412,
    "name": "Burmy",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 29,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 29,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 36
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/burmy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/burmy.gif\" alt=\"burmy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/burmy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/burmy.gif\" alt=\"burmy\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/burmy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/burmy.gif\" alt=\"burmy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/burmy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/burmy.gif\" alt=\"burmy\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 413,
    "name": "Wormadam",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 59,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 79,
      "Sp. Defense": 105,
      "Speed": 36
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wormadam\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/wormadam.gif\" alt=\"wormadam\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wormadam\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/wormadam.gif\" alt=\"wormadam\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wormadam\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/wormadam.gif\" alt=\"wormadam\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/wormadam\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/wormadam.gif\" alt=\"wormadam\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 414,
    "name": "Mothim",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 94,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 94,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 66
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mothim\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mothim.gif\" alt=\"mothim\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mothim\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mothim.gif\" alt=\"mothim\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mothim\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mothim.gif\" alt=\"mothim\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mothim\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mothim.gif\" alt=\"mothim\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 415,
    "name": "Combee",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 42,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 42,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/combee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/combee.gif\" alt=\"combee\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/combee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/combee.gif\" alt=\"combee\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/combee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/combee.gif\" alt=\"combee\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/combee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/combee.gif\" alt=\"combee\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 416,
    "name": "Vespiquen",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 102,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 102,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vespiquen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/vespiquen.gif\" alt=\"vespiquen\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vespiquen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/vespiquen.gif\" alt=\"vespiquen\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vespiquen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/vespiquen.gif\" alt=\"vespiquen\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vespiquen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/vespiquen.gif\" alt=\"vespiquen\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 417,
    "name": "Pachirisu",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pachirisu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pachirisu.gif\" alt=\"pachirisu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pachirisu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pachirisu.gif\" alt=\"pachirisu\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pachirisu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pachirisu.gif\" alt=\"pachirisu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pachirisu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pachirisu.gif\" alt=\"pachirisu\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 418,
    "name": "Buizel",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/buizel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/buizel.gif\" alt=\"buizel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/buizel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/buizel.gif\" alt=\"buizel\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/buizel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/buizel.gif\" alt=\"buizel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/buizel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/buizel.gif\" alt=\"buizel\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 419,
    "name": "Floatzel",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 115
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/floatzel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/floatzel.gif\" alt=\"floatzel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/floatzel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/floatzel.gif\" alt=\"floatzel\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/floatzel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/floatzel.gif\" alt=\"floatzel\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/floatzel\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/floatzel.gif\" alt=\"floatzel\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 420,
    "name": "Cherubi",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 35,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 62,
      "Sp. Defense": 53,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cherubi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cherubi.gif\" alt=\"cherubi\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cherubi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cherubi.gif\" alt=\"cherubi\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cherubi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cherubi.gif\" alt=\"cherubi\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cherubi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cherubi.gif\" alt=\"cherubi\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 421,
    "name": "Cherrim",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 87,
      "Sp. Defense": 78,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cherrim\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cherrim.gif\" alt=\"cherrim\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cherrim\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cherrim.gif\" alt=\"cherrim\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cherrim\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cherrim.gif\" alt=\"cherrim\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cherrim\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cherrim.gif\" alt=\"cherrim\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 422,
    "name": "Shellos",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 76,
      "Attack": 48,
      "Defense": 48,
      "Sp. Attack": 57,
      "Sp. Defense": 62,
      "Speed": 34
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shellos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/shellos.gif\" alt=\"shellos\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shellos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/shellos.gif\" alt=\"shellos\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shellos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/shellos.gif\" alt=\"shellos\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shellos\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/shellos.gif\" alt=\"shellos\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 423,
    "name": "Gastrodon",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 111,
      "Attack": 83,
      "Defense": 68,
      "Sp. Attack": 92,
      "Sp. Defense": 82,
      "Speed": 39
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gastrodon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gastrodon.gif\" alt=\"gastrodon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gastrodon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gastrodon.gif\" alt=\"gastrodon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gastrodon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gastrodon.gif\" alt=\"gastrodon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gastrodon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gastrodon.gif\" alt=\"gastrodon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 424,
    "name": "Ambipom",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 66,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 66,
      "Speed": 115
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ambipom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ambipom.gif\" alt=\"ambipom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ambipom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ambipom.gif\" alt=\"ambipom\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ambipom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ambipom.gif\" alt=\"ambipom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ambipom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ambipom.gif\" alt=\"ambipom\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 425,
    "name": "Drifloon",
    "type": [
      "Ghost",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 34,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 44,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drifloon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/drifloon.gif\" alt=\"drifloon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drifloon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/drifloon.gif\" alt=\"drifloon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drifloon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/drifloon.gif\" alt=\"drifloon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drifloon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/drifloon.gif\" alt=\"drifloon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 426,
    "name": "Drifblim",
    "type": [
      "Ghost",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 150,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 44,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 54,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drifblim\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/drifblim.gif\" alt=\"drifblim\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drifblim\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/drifblim.gif\" alt=\"drifblim\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drifblim\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/drifblim.gif\" alt=\"drifblim\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drifblim\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/drifblim.gif\" alt=\"drifblim\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 427,
    "name": "Buneary",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 66,
      "Defense": 44,
      "Sp. Attack": 44,
      "Sp. Defense": 56,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/buneary\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/buneary.gif\" alt=\"buneary\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/buneary\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/buneary.gif\" alt=\"buneary\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/buneary\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/buneary.gif\" alt=\"buneary\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/buneary\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/buneary.gif\" alt=\"buneary\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 428,
    "name": "Lopunny",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 76,
      "Defense": 84,
      "Sp. Attack": 54,
      "Sp. Defense": 96,
      "Speed": 105
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lopunny\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lopunny.gif\" alt=\"lopunny\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lopunny\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lopunny.gif\" alt=\"lopunny\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lopunny\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lopunny.gif\" alt=\"lopunny\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lopunny\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lopunny.gif\" alt=\"lopunny\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 429,
    "name": "Mismagius",
    "type": [
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 105,
      "Speed": 105
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mismagius\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mismagius.gif\" alt=\"mismagius\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mismagius\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mismagius.gif\" alt=\"mismagius\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mismagius\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mismagius.gif\" alt=\"mismagius\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mismagius\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mismagius.gif\" alt=\"mismagius\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 430,
    "name": "Honchkrow",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 125,
      "Defense": 52,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 52,
      "Speed": 71
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/honchkrow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/honchkrow.gif\" alt=\"honchkrow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/honchkrow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/honchkrow.gif\" alt=\"honchkrow\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/honchkrow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/honchkrow.gif\" alt=\"honchkrow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/honchkrow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/honchkrow.gif\" alt=\"honchkrow\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 431,
    "name": "Glameow",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 49,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 42,
      "Sp. Attack": 42,
      "Sp. Defense": 37,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/glameow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/glameow.gif\" alt=\"glameow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/glameow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/glameow.gif\" alt=\"glameow\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/glameow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/glameow.gif\" alt=\"glameow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/glameow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/glameow.gif\" alt=\"glameow\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 432,
    "name": "Purugly",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 71,
      "Attack": 82,
      "Defense": 64,
      "Sp. Attack": 64,
      "Sp. Defense": 59,
      "Speed": 112
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/purugly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/purugly.gif\" alt=\"purugly\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/purugly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/purugly.gif\" alt=\"purugly\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/purugly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/purugly.gif\" alt=\"purugly\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/purugly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/purugly.gif\" alt=\"purugly\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 433,
    "name": "Chingling",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chingling\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/chingling.gif\" alt=\"chingling\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chingling\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/chingling.gif\" alt=\"chingling\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chingling\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/chingling.gif\" alt=\"chingling\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chingling\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/chingling.gif\" alt=\"chingling\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 434,
    "name": "Stunky",
    "type": [
      "Poison",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 63,
      "Attack": 63,
      "Defense": 47,
      "Sp. Attack": 41,
      "Sp. Defense": 41,
      "Speed": 74
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stunky\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/stunky.gif\" alt=\"stunky\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stunky\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/stunky.gif\" alt=\"stunky\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stunky\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/stunky.gif\" alt=\"stunky\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stunky\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/stunky.gif\" alt=\"stunky\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 435,
    "name": "Skuntank",
    "type": [
      "Poison",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 103,
      "Attack": 93,
      "Defense": 67,
      "Sp. Attack": 71,
      "Sp. Defense": 61,
      "Speed": 84
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skuntank\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/skuntank.gif\" alt=\"skuntank\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skuntank\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/skuntank.gif\" alt=\"skuntank\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skuntank\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/skuntank.gif\" alt=\"skuntank\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skuntank\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/skuntank.gif\" alt=\"skuntank\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 436,
    "name": "Bronzor",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 57,
      "Attack": 24,
      "Defense": 86,
      "Sp. Attack": 24,
      "Sp. Defense": 86,
      "Speed": 23
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bronzor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bronzor.gif\" alt=\"bronzor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bronzor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bronzor.gif\" alt=\"bronzor\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bronzor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bronzor.gif\" alt=\"bronzor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bronzor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bronzor.gif\" alt=\"bronzor\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 437,
    "name": "Bronzong",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 67,
      "Attack": 89,
      "Defense": 116,
      "Sp. Attack": 79,
      "Sp. Defense": 116,
      "Speed": 33
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bronzong\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bronzong.gif\" alt=\"bronzong\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bronzong\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bronzong.gif\" alt=\"bronzong\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bronzong\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bronzong.gif\" alt=\"bronzong\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bronzong\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bronzong.gif\" alt=\"bronzong\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 438,
    "name": "Bonsly",
    "type": [
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 10,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 10
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bonsly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bonsly.gif\" alt=\"bonsly\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bonsly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bonsly.gif\" alt=\"bonsly\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bonsly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bonsly.gif\" alt=\"bonsly\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bonsly\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bonsly.gif\" alt=\"bonsly\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 439,
    "name": "Mime Jr.",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 20,
      "Attack": 25,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mime jr.\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mime jr..gif\" alt=\"mime jr.\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mime jr.\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mime jr..gif\" alt=\"mime jr.\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mime jr.\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mime jr..gif\" alt=\"mime jr.\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mime jr.\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mime jr..gif\" alt=\"mime jr.\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 440,
    "name": "Happiny",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 5,
      "Defense": 5,
      "Sp. Attack": 15,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/happiny\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/happiny.gif\" alt=\"happiny\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/happiny\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/happiny.gif\" alt=\"happiny\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/happiny\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/happiny.gif\" alt=\"happiny\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/happiny\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/happiny.gif\" alt=\"happiny\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 441,
    "name": "Chatot",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 76,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 92,
      "Sp. Defense": 42,
      "Speed": 91
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chatot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/chatot.gif\" alt=\"chatot\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chatot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/chatot.gif\" alt=\"chatot\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chatot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/chatot.gif\" alt=\"chatot\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chatot\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/chatot.gif\" alt=\"chatot\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 442,
    "name": "Spiritomb",
    "type": [
      "Ghost",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 92,
      "Defense": 108,
      "Sp. Attack": 92,
      "Sp. Defense": 108,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spiritomb\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/spiritomb.gif\" alt=\"spiritomb\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spiritomb\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/spiritomb.gif\" alt=\"spiritomb\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spiritomb\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/spiritomb.gif\" alt=\"spiritomb\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/spiritomb\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/spiritomb.gif\" alt=\"spiritomb\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 443,
    "name": "Gible",
    "type": [
      "Dragon",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 58,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 42
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gible\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gible.gif\" alt=\"gible\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gible\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gible.gif\" alt=\"gible\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gible\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gible.gif\" alt=\"gible\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gible\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gible.gif\" alt=\"gible\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 444,
    "name": "Gabite",
    "type": [
      "Dragon",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 68,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 82
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gabite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gabite.gif\" alt=\"gabite\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gabite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gabite.gif\" alt=\"gabite\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gabite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gabite.gif\" alt=\"gabite\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gabite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gabite.gif\" alt=\"gabite\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 445,
    "name": "Garchomp",
    "type": [
      "Dragon",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 108,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 102
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/garchomp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/garchomp.gif\" alt=\"garchomp\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/garchomp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/garchomp.gif\" alt=\"garchomp\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/garchomp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/garchomp.gif\" alt=\"garchomp\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/garchomp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/garchomp.gif\" alt=\"garchomp\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 446,
    "name": "Munchlax",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 135,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 5
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/munchlax\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/munchlax.gif\" alt=\"munchlax\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/munchlax\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/munchlax.gif\" alt=\"munchlax\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/munchlax\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/munchlax.gif\" alt=\"munchlax\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/munchlax\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/munchlax.gif\" alt=\"munchlax\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 447,
    "name": "Riolu",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/riolu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/riolu.gif\" alt=\"riolu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/riolu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/riolu.gif\" alt=\"riolu\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/riolu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/riolu.gif\" alt=\"riolu\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/riolu\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/riolu.gif\" alt=\"riolu\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 448,
    "name": "Lucario",
    "type": [
      "Fighting",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 110,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 115,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lucario\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lucario.gif\" alt=\"lucario\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lucario\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lucario.gif\" alt=\"lucario\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lucario\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lucario.gif\" alt=\"lucario\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lucario\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lucario.gif\" alt=\"lucario\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 449,
    "name": "Hippopotas",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 68,
      "Attack": 72,
      "Defense": 78,
      "Sp. Attack": 38,
      "Sp. Defense": 42,
      "Speed": 32
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hippopotas\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/hippopotas.gif\" alt=\"hippopotas\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hippopotas\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/hippopotas.gif\" alt=\"hippopotas\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hippopotas\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/hippopotas.gif\" alt=\"hippopotas\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hippopotas\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/hippopotas.gif\" alt=\"hippopotas\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 450,
    "name": "Hippowdon",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 108,
      "Attack": 112,
      "Defense": 118,
      "Sp. Attack": 68,
      "Sp. Defense": 72,
      "Speed": 47
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hippowdon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/hippowdon.gif\" alt=\"hippowdon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hippowdon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/hippowdon.gif\" alt=\"hippowdon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hippowdon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/hippowdon.gif\" alt=\"hippowdon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hippowdon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/hippowdon.gif\" alt=\"hippowdon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 451,
    "name": "Skorupi",
    "type": [
      "Poison",
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skorupi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/skorupi.gif\" alt=\"skorupi\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skorupi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/skorupi.gif\" alt=\"skorupi\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skorupi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/skorupi.gif\" alt=\"skorupi\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/skorupi\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/skorupi.gif\" alt=\"skorupi\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 452,
    "name": "Drapion",
    "type": [
      "Poison",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 110,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drapion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/drapion.gif\" alt=\"drapion\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drapion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/drapion.gif\" alt=\"drapion\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drapion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/drapion.gif\" alt=\"drapion\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drapion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/drapion.gif\" alt=\"drapion\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 453,
    "name": "Croagunk",
    "type": [
      "Poison",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 48,
      "Attack": 61,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 61,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/croagunk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/croagunk.gif\" alt=\"croagunk\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/croagunk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/croagunk.gif\" alt=\"croagunk\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/croagunk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/croagunk.gif\" alt=\"croagunk\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/croagunk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/croagunk.gif\" alt=\"croagunk\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 454,
    "name": "Toxicroak",
    "type": [
      "Poison",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 83,
      "Attack": 106,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 86,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/toxicroak\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/toxicroak.gif\" alt=\"toxicroak\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/toxicroak\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/toxicroak.gif\" alt=\"toxicroak\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/toxicroak\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/toxicroak.gif\" alt=\"toxicroak\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/toxicroak\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/toxicroak.gif\" alt=\"toxicroak\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 455,
    "name": "Carnivine",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 74,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 72,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 72,
      "Speed": 46
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/carnivine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/carnivine.gif\" alt=\"carnivine\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/carnivine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/carnivine.gif\" alt=\"carnivine\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/carnivine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/carnivine.gif\" alt=\"carnivine\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/carnivine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/carnivine.gif\" alt=\"carnivine\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 456,
    "name": "Finneon",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 49,
      "Attack": 49,
      "Defense": 56,
      "Sp. Attack": 49,
      "Sp. Defense": 61,
      "Speed": 66
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/finneon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/finneon.gif\" alt=\"finneon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/finneon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/finneon.gif\" alt=\"finneon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/finneon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/finneon.gif\" alt=\"finneon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/finneon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/finneon.gif\" alt=\"finneon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 457,
    "name": "Lumineon",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 69,
      "Attack": 69,
      "Defense": 76,
      "Sp. Attack": 69,
      "Sp. Defense": 86,
      "Speed": 91
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lumineon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lumineon.gif\" alt=\"lumineon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lumineon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lumineon.gif\" alt=\"lumineon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lumineon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lumineon.gif\" alt=\"lumineon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lumineon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lumineon.gif\" alt=\"lumineon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 458,
    "name": "Mantyke",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 20,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 120,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mantyke\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mantyke.gif\" alt=\"mantyke\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mantyke\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mantyke.gif\" alt=\"mantyke\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mantyke\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mantyke.gif\" alt=\"mantyke\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mantyke\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mantyke.gif\" alt=\"mantyke\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 459,
    "name": "Snover",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 62,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 62,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snover\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/snover.gif\" alt=\"snover\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snover\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/snover.gif\" alt=\"snover\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snover\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/snover.gif\" alt=\"snover\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snover\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/snover.gif\" alt=\"snover\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 460,
    "name": "Abomasnow",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 92,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 92,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/abomasnow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/abomasnow.gif\" alt=\"abomasnow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/abomasnow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/abomasnow.gif\" alt=\"abomasnow\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/abomasnow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/abomasnow.gif\" alt=\"abomasnow\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/abomasnow\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/abomasnow.gif\" alt=\"abomasnow\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 461,
    "name": "Weavile",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 125
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weavile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/weavile.gif\" alt=\"weavile\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weavile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/weavile.gif\" alt=\"weavile\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weavile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/weavile.gif\" alt=\"weavile\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/weavile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/weavile.gif\" alt=\"weavile\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 462,
    "name": "Magnezone",
    "type": [
      "Electric",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 115,
      "Sp. Attack": 130,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magnezone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/magnezone.gif\" alt=\"magnezone\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magnezone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/magnezone.gif\" alt=\"magnezone\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magnezone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/magnezone.gif\" alt=\"magnezone\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magnezone\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/magnezone.gif\" alt=\"magnezone\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 463,
    "name": "Lickilicky",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 110,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lickilicky\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lickilicky.gif\" alt=\"lickilicky\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lickilicky\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lickilicky.gif\" alt=\"lickilicky\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lickilicky\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lickilicky.gif\" alt=\"lickilicky\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lickilicky\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lickilicky.gif\" alt=\"lickilicky\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 464,
    "name": "Rhyperior",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 115,
      "Attack": 140,
      "Defense": 130,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rhyperior\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/rhyperior.gif\" alt=\"rhyperior\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rhyperior\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/rhyperior.gif\" alt=\"rhyperior\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rhyperior\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/rhyperior.gif\" alt=\"rhyperior\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rhyperior\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/rhyperior.gif\" alt=\"rhyperior\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 465,
    "name": "Tangrowth",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 125,
      "Sp. Attack": 110,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tangrowth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tangrowth.gif\" alt=\"tangrowth\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tangrowth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tangrowth.gif\" alt=\"tangrowth\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tangrowth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tangrowth.gif\" alt=\"tangrowth\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tangrowth\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tangrowth.gif\" alt=\"tangrowth\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 466,
    "name": "Electivire",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 123,
      "Defense": 67,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electivire\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/electivire.gif\" alt=\"electivire\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electivire\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/electivire.gif\" alt=\"electivire\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electivire\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/electivire.gif\" alt=\"electivire\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/electivire\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/electivire.gif\" alt=\"electivire\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 467,
    "name": "Magmortar",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 67,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 83
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magmortar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/magmortar.gif\" alt=\"magmortar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magmortar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/magmortar.gif\" alt=\"magmortar\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magmortar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/magmortar.gif\" alt=\"magmortar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/magmortar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/magmortar.gif\" alt=\"magmortar\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 468,
    "name": "Togekiss",
    "type": [
      "Fairy",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 120,
      "Sp. Defense": 115,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/togekiss\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/togekiss.gif\" alt=\"togekiss\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/togekiss\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/togekiss.gif\" alt=\"togekiss\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/togekiss\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/togekiss.gif\" alt=\"togekiss\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/togekiss\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/togekiss.gif\" alt=\"togekiss\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 469,
    "name": "Yanmega",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 86,
      "Attack": 76,
      "Defense": 86,
      "Sp. Attack": 116,
      "Sp. Defense": 56,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/yanmega\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/yanmega.gif\" alt=\"yanmega\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/yanmega\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/yanmega.gif\" alt=\"yanmega\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/yanmega\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/yanmega.gif\" alt=\"yanmega\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/yanmega\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/yanmega.gif\" alt=\"yanmega\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 470,
    "name": "Leafeon",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 110,
      "Defense": 130,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/leafeon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/leafeon.gif\" alt=\"leafeon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/leafeon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/leafeon.gif\" alt=\"leafeon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/leafeon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/leafeon.gif\" alt=\"leafeon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/leafeon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/leafeon.gif\" alt=\"leafeon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 471,
    "name": "Glaceon",
    "type": [
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 110,
      "Sp. Attack": 130,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/glaceon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/glaceon.gif\" alt=\"glaceon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/glaceon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/glaceon.gif\" alt=\"glaceon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/glaceon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/glaceon.gif\" alt=\"glaceon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/glaceon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/glaceon.gif\" alt=\"glaceon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 472,
    "name": "Gliscor",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 125,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gliscor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gliscor.gif\" alt=\"gliscor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gliscor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gliscor.gif\" alt=\"gliscor\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gliscor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gliscor.gif\" alt=\"gliscor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gliscor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gliscor.gif\" alt=\"gliscor\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 473,
    "name": "Mamoswine",
    "type": [
      "Ice",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 110,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mamoswine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mamoswine.gif\" alt=\"mamoswine\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mamoswine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mamoswine.gif\" alt=\"mamoswine\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mamoswine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mamoswine.gif\" alt=\"mamoswine\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mamoswine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mamoswine.gif\" alt=\"mamoswine\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 474,
    "name": "Porygon-Z",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 135,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/porygon-z\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/porygon-z.gif\" alt=\"porygon-z\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/porygon-z\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/porygon-z.gif\" alt=\"porygon-z\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/porygon-z\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/porygon-z.gif\" alt=\"porygon-z\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/porygon-z\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/porygon-z.gif\" alt=\"porygon-z\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 475,
    "name": "Gallade",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 68,
      "Attack": 125,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 115,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gallade\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gallade.gif\" alt=\"gallade\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gallade\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gallade.gif\" alt=\"gallade\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gallade\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gallade.gif\" alt=\"gallade\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gallade\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gallade.gif\" alt=\"gallade\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 476,
    "name": "Probopass",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 145,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 150,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/probopass\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/probopass.gif\" alt=\"probopass\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/probopass\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/probopass.gif\" alt=\"probopass\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/probopass\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/probopass.gif\" alt=\"probopass\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/probopass\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/probopass.gif\" alt=\"probopass\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 477,
    "name": "Dusknoir",
    "type": [
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 135,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 135,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dusknoir\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dusknoir.gif\" alt=\"dusknoir\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dusknoir\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dusknoir.gif\" alt=\"dusknoir\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dusknoir\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dusknoir.gif\" alt=\"dusknoir\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dusknoir\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dusknoir.gif\" alt=\"dusknoir\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 478,
    "name": "Froslass",
    "type": [
      "Ice",
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 110
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/froslass\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/froslass.gif\" alt=\"froslass\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/froslass\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/froslass.gif\" alt=\"froslass\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/froslass\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/froslass.gif\" alt=\"froslass\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/froslass\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/froslass.gif\" alt=\"froslass\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 479,
    "name": "Rotom",
    "type": [
      "Electric",
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 77,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 77,
      "Speed": 91
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rotom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/rotom.gif\" alt=\"rotom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rotom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/rotom.gif\" alt=\"rotom\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rotom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/rotom.gif\" alt=\"rotom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rotom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/rotom.gif\" alt=\"rotom\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 480,
    "name": "Uxie",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 130,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 130,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/uxie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/uxie.gif\" alt=\"uxie\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/uxie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/uxie.gif\" alt=\"uxie\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/uxie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/uxie.gif\" alt=\"uxie\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/uxie\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/uxie.gif\" alt=\"uxie\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 481,
    "name": "Mesprit",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 105,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 105,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mesprit\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mesprit.gif\" alt=\"mesprit\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mesprit\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mesprit.gif\" alt=\"mesprit\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mesprit\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mesprit.gif\" alt=\"mesprit\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mesprit\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mesprit.gif\" alt=\"mesprit\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 482,
    "name": "Azelf",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 125,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 115
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/azelf\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/azelf.gif\" alt=\"azelf\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/azelf\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/azelf.gif\" alt=\"azelf\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/azelf\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/azelf.gif\" alt=\"azelf\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/azelf\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/azelf.gif\" alt=\"azelf\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 483,
    "name": "Dialga",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 120,
      "Sp. Attack": 150,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dialga\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dialga.gif\" alt=\"dialga\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dialga\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dialga.gif\" alt=\"dialga\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dialga\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dialga.gif\" alt=\"dialga\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dialga\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dialga.gif\" alt=\"dialga\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 484,
    "name": "Palkia",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 150,
      "Sp. Defense": 120,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/palkia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/palkia.gif\" alt=\"palkia\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/palkia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/palkia.gif\" alt=\"palkia\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/palkia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/palkia.gif\" alt=\"palkia\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/palkia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/palkia.gif\" alt=\"palkia\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 485,
    "name": "Heatran",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 91,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 106,
      "Sp. Attack": 130,
      "Sp. Defense": 106,
      "Speed": 77
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/heatran\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/heatran.gif\" alt=\"heatran\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/heatran\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/heatran.gif\" alt=\"heatran\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/heatran\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/heatran.gif\" alt=\"heatran\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/heatran\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/heatran.gif\" alt=\"heatran\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 486,
    "name": "Regigigas",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 110,
      "Attack": 160,
      "Defense": 110,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 110,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/regigigas\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/regigigas.gif\" alt=\"regigigas\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/regigigas\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/regigigas.gif\" alt=\"regigigas\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/regigigas\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/regigigas.gif\" alt=\"regigigas\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/regigigas\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/regigigas.gif\" alt=\"regigigas\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 487,
    "name": "Giratina",
    "type": [
      "Ghost",
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 150,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 120,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 120,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/giratina\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/giratina.gif\" alt=\"giratina\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/giratina\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/giratina.gif\" alt=\"giratina\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/giratina\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/giratina.gif\" alt=\"giratina\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/giratina\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/giratina.gif\" alt=\"giratina\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 488,
    "name": "Cresselia",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 120,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 120,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 130,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cresselia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cresselia.gif\" alt=\"cresselia\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cresselia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cresselia.gif\" alt=\"cresselia\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cresselia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cresselia.gif\" alt=\"cresselia\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cresselia\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cresselia.gif\" alt=\"cresselia\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 489,
    "name": "Phione",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/phione\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/phione.gif\" alt=\"phione\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/phione\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/phione.gif\" alt=\"phione\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/phione\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/phione.gif\" alt=\"phione\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/phione\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/phione.gif\" alt=\"phione\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 490,
    "name": "Manaphy",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/manaphy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/manaphy.gif\" alt=\"manaphy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/manaphy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/manaphy.gif\" alt=\"manaphy\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/manaphy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/manaphy.gif\" alt=\"manaphy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/manaphy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/manaphy.gif\" alt=\"manaphy\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 491,
    "name": "Darkrai",
    "type": [
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 135,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 125
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/darkrai\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/darkrai.gif\" alt=\"darkrai\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/darkrai\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/darkrai.gif\" alt=\"darkrai\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/darkrai\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/darkrai.gif\" alt=\"darkrai\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/darkrai\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/darkrai.gif\" alt=\"darkrai\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 492,
    "name": "Shaymin",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shaymin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/shaymin.gif\" alt=\"shaymin\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shaymin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/shaymin.gif\" alt=\"shaymin\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shaymin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/shaymin.gif\" alt=\"shaymin\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shaymin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/shaymin.gif\" alt=\"shaymin\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 493,
    "name": "Arceus",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 120,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 120,
      "Sp. Attack": 120,
      "Sp. Defense": 120,
      "Speed": 120
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/arceus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/arceus.gif\" alt=\"arceus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/arceus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/arceus.gif\" alt=\"arceus\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/arceus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/arceus.gif\" alt=\"arceus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/arceus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/arceus.gif\" alt=\"arceus\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 494,
    "name": "Victini",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/victini\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/victini.gif\" alt=\"victini\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/victini\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/victini.gif\" alt=\"victini\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/victini\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/victini.gif\" alt=\"victini\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/victini\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/victini.gif\" alt=\"victini\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 495,
    "name": "Snivy",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 63
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snivy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/snivy.gif\" alt=\"snivy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snivy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/snivy.gif\" alt=\"snivy\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snivy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/snivy.gif\" alt=\"snivy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/snivy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/snivy.gif\" alt=\"snivy\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 496,
    "name": "Servine",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 83
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/servine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/servine.gif\" alt=\"servine\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/servine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/servine.gif\" alt=\"servine\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/servine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/servine.gif\" alt=\"servine\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/servine\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/servine.gif\" alt=\"servine\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 497,
    "name": "Serperior",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 113
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/serperior\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/serperior.gif\" alt=\"serperior\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/serperior\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/serperior.gif\" alt=\"serperior\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/serperior\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/serperior.gif\" alt=\"serperior\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/serperior\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/serperior.gif\" alt=\"serperior\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 498,
    "name": "Tepig",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 63,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tepig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tepig.gif\" alt=\"tepig\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tepig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tepig.gif\" alt=\"tepig\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tepig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tepig.gif\" alt=\"tepig\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tepig\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tepig.gif\" alt=\"tepig\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 499,
    "name": "Pignite",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 90,
      "Attack": 93,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pignite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pignite.gif\" alt=\"pignite\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pignite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pignite.gif\" alt=\"pignite\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pignite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pignite.gif\" alt=\"pignite\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pignite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pignite.gif\" alt=\"pignite\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 500,
    "name": "Emboar",
    "type": [
      "Fire",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 110,
      "Attack": 123,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/emboar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/emboar.gif\" alt=\"emboar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/emboar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/emboar.gif\" alt=\"emboar\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/emboar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/emboar.gif\" alt=\"emboar\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/emboar\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/emboar.gif\" alt=\"emboar\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 501,
    "name": "Oshawott",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 63,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/oshawott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/oshawott.gif\" alt=\"oshawott\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/oshawott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/oshawott.gif\" alt=\"oshawott\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/oshawott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/oshawott.gif\" alt=\"oshawott\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/oshawott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/oshawott.gif\" alt=\"oshawott\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 502,
    "name": "Dewott",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 83,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dewott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dewott.gif\" alt=\"dewott\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dewott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dewott.gif\" alt=\"dewott\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dewott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dewott.gif\" alt=\"dewott\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dewott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dewott.gif\" alt=\"dewott\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 503,
    "name": "Samurott",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 108,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/samurott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/samurott.gif\" alt=\"samurott\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/samurott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/samurott.gif\" alt=\"samurott\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/samurott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/samurott.gif\" alt=\"samurott\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/samurott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/samurott.gif\" alt=\"samurott\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 504,
    "name": "Patrat",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 39,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 39,
      "Speed": 42
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/patrat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/patrat.gif\" alt=\"patrat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/patrat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/patrat.gif\" alt=\"patrat\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/patrat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/patrat.gif\" alt=\"patrat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/patrat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/patrat.gif\" alt=\"patrat\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 505,
    "name": "Watchog",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 69,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 69,
      "Speed": 77
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/watchog\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/watchog.gif\" alt=\"watchog\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/watchog\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/watchog.gif\" alt=\"watchog\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/watchog\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/watchog.gif\" alt=\"watchog\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/watchog\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/watchog.gif\" alt=\"watchog\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 506,
    "name": "Lillipup",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 25,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lillipup\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lillipup.gif\" alt=\"lillipup\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lillipup\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lillipup.gif\" alt=\"lillipup\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lillipup\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lillipup.gif\" alt=\"lillipup\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lillipup\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lillipup.gif\" alt=\"lillipup\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 507,
    "name": "Herdier",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/herdier\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/herdier.gif\" alt=\"herdier\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/herdier\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/herdier.gif\" alt=\"herdier\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/herdier\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/herdier.gif\" alt=\"herdier\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/herdier\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/herdier.gif\" alt=\"herdier\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 508,
    "name": "Stoutland",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 110,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stoutland\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/stoutland.gif\" alt=\"stoutland\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stoutland\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/stoutland.gif\" alt=\"stoutland\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stoutland\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/stoutland.gif\" alt=\"stoutland\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stoutland\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/stoutland.gif\" alt=\"stoutland\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 509,
    "name": "Purrloin",
    "type": [
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 41,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 37,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 37,
      "Speed": 66
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/purrloin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/purrloin.gif\" alt=\"purrloin\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/purrloin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/purrloin.gif\" alt=\"purrloin\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/purrloin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/purrloin.gif\" alt=\"purrloin\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/purrloin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/purrloin.gif\" alt=\"purrloin\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 510,
    "name": "Liepard",
    "type": [
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 64,
      "Attack": 88,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 88,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 106
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/liepard\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/liepard.gif\" alt=\"liepard\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/liepard\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/liepard.gif\" alt=\"liepard\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/liepard\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/liepard.gif\" alt=\"liepard\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/liepard\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/liepard.gif\" alt=\"liepard\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 511,
    "name": "Pansage",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 53,
      "Defense": 48,
      "Sp. Attack": 53,
      "Sp. Defense": 48,
      "Speed": 64
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pansage\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pansage.gif\" alt=\"pansage\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pansage\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pansage.gif\" alt=\"pansage\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pansage\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pansage.gif\" alt=\"pansage\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pansage\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pansage.gif\" alt=\"pansage\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 512,
    "name": "Simisage",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 98,
      "Defense": 63,
      "Sp. Attack": 98,
      "Sp. Defense": 63,
      "Speed": 101
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/simisage\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/simisage.gif\" alt=\"simisage\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/simisage\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/simisage.gif\" alt=\"simisage\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/simisage\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/simisage.gif\" alt=\"simisage\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/simisage\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/simisage.gif\" alt=\"simisage\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 513,
    "name": "Pansear",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 53,
      "Defense": 48,
      "Sp. Attack": 53,
      "Sp. Defense": 48,
      "Speed": 64
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pansear\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pansear.gif\" alt=\"pansear\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pansear\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pansear.gif\" alt=\"pansear\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pansear\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pansear.gif\" alt=\"pansear\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pansear\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pansear.gif\" alt=\"pansear\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 514,
    "name": "Simisear",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 98,
      "Defense": 63,
      "Sp. Attack": 98,
      "Sp. Defense": 63,
      "Speed": 101
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/simisear\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/simisear.gif\" alt=\"simisear\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/simisear\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/simisear.gif\" alt=\"simisear\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/simisear\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/simisear.gif\" alt=\"simisear\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/simisear\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/simisear.gif\" alt=\"simisear\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 515,
    "name": "Panpour",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 53,
      "Defense": 48,
      "Sp. Attack": 53,
      "Sp. Defense": 48,
      "Speed": 64
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/panpour\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/panpour.gif\" alt=\"panpour\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/panpour\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/panpour.gif\" alt=\"panpour\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/panpour\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/panpour.gif\" alt=\"panpour\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/panpour\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/panpour.gif\" alt=\"panpour\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 516,
    "name": "Simipour",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 98,
      "Defense": 63,
      "Sp. Attack": 98,
      "Sp. Defense": 63,
      "Speed": 101
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/simipour\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/simipour.gif\" alt=\"simipour\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/simipour\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/simipour.gif\" alt=\"simipour\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/simipour\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/simipour.gif\" alt=\"simipour\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/simipour\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/simipour.gif\" alt=\"simipour\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 517,
    "name": "Munna",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 76,
      "Attack": 25,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 67,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 24
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/munna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/munna.gif\" alt=\"munna\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/munna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/munna.gif\" alt=\"munna\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/munna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/munna.gif\" alt=\"munna\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/munna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/munna.gif\" alt=\"munna\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 518,
    "name": "Musharna",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 116,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 107,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 29
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/musharna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/musharna.gif\" alt=\"musharna\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/musharna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/musharna.gif\" alt=\"musharna\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/musharna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/musharna.gif\" alt=\"musharna\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/musharna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/musharna.gif\" alt=\"musharna\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 519,
    "name": "Pidove",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 36,
      "Sp. Defense": 30,
      "Speed": 43
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidove\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pidove.gif\" alt=\"pidove\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidove\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pidove.gif\" alt=\"pidove\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidove\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pidove.gif\" alt=\"pidove\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pidove\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pidove.gif\" alt=\"pidove\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 520,
    "name": "Tranquill",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 62,
      "Attack": 77,
      "Defense": 62,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 42,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tranquill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tranquill.gif\" alt=\"tranquill\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tranquill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tranquill.gif\" alt=\"tranquill\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tranquill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tranquill.gif\" alt=\"tranquill\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tranquill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tranquill.gif\" alt=\"tranquill\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 521,
    "name": "Unfezant",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 115,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 93
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/unfezant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/unfezant.gif\" alt=\"unfezant\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/unfezant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/unfezant.gif\" alt=\"unfezant\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/unfezant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/unfezant.gif\" alt=\"unfezant\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/unfezant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/unfezant.gif\" alt=\"unfezant\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 522,
    "name": "Blitzle",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 32,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 32,
      "Speed": 76
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blitzle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/blitzle.gif\" alt=\"blitzle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blitzle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/blitzle.gif\" alt=\"blitzle\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blitzle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/blitzle.gif\" alt=\"blitzle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/blitzle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/blitzle.gif\" alt=\"blitzle\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 523,
    "name": "Zebstrika",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 63,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 63,
      "Speed": 116
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zebstrika\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/zebstrika.gif\" alt=\"zebstrika\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zebstrika\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/zebstrika.gif\" alt=\"zebstrika\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zebstrika\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/zebstrika.gif\" alt=\"zebstrika\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zebstrika\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/zebstrika.gif\" alt=\"zebstrika\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 524,
    "name": "Roggenrola",
    "type": [
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 25,
      "Sp. Defense": 25,
      "Speed": 15
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/roggenrola\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/roggenrola.gif\" alt=\"roggenrola\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/roggenrola\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/roggenrola.gif\" alt=\"roggenrola\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/roggenrola\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/roggenrola.gif\" alt=\"roggenrola\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/roggenrola\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/roggenrola.gif\" alt=\"roggenrola\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 525,
    "name": "Boldore",
    "type": [
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 105,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/boldore\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/boldore.gif\" alt=\"boldore\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/boldore\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/boldore.gif\" alt=\"boldore\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/boldore\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/boldore.gif\" alt=\"boldore\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/boldore\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/boldore.gif\" alt=\"boldore\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 526,
    "name": "Gigalith",
    "type": [
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 135,
      "Defense": 130,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 25
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gigalith\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gigalith.gif\" alt=\"gigalith\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gigalith\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gigalith.gif\" alt=\"gigalith\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gigalith\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gigalith.gif\" alt=\"gigalith\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gigalith\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gigalith.gif\" alt=\"gigalith\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 527,
    "name": "Woobat",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 43,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 43,
      "Speed": 72
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/woobat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/woobat.gif\" alt=\"woobat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/woobat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/woobat.gif\" alt=\"woobat\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/woobat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/woobat.gif\" alt=\"woobat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/woobat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/woobat.gif\" alt=\"woobat\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 528,
    "name": "Swoobat",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 67,
      "Attack": 57,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 77,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 114
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swoobat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/swoobat.gif\" alt=\"swoobat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swoobat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/swoobat.gif\" alt=\"swoobat\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swoobat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/swoobat.gif\" alt=\"swoobat\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swoobat\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/swoobat.gif\" alt=\"swoobat\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 529,
    "name": "Drilbur",
    "type": [
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 68
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drilbur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/drilbur.gif\" alt=\"drilbur\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drilbur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/drilbur.gif\" alt=\"drilbur\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drilbur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/drilbur.gif\" alt=\"drilbur\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/drilbur\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/drilbur.gif\" alt=\"drilbur\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 530,
    "name": "Excadrill",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 110,
      "Attack": 135,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 88
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/excadrill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/excadrill.gif\" alt=\"excadrill\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/excadrill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/excadrill.gif\" alt=\"excadrill\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/excadrill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/excadrill.gif\" alt=\"excadrill\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/excadrill\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/excadrill.gif\" alt=\"excadrill\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 531,
    "name": "Audino",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 103,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 86,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 86,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/audino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/audino.gif\" alt=\"audino\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/audino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/audino.gif\" alt=\"audino\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/audino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/audino.gif\" alt=\"audino\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/audino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/audino.gif\" alt=\"audino\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 532,
    "name": "Timburr",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 25,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/timburr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/timburr.gif\" alt=\"timburr\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/timburr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/timburr.gif\" alt=\"timburr\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/timburr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/timburr.gif\" alt=\"timburr\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/timburr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/timburr.gif\" alt=\"timburr\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 533,
    "name": "Gurdurr",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gurdurr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gurdurr.gif\" alt=\"gurdurr\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gurdurr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gurdurr.gif\" alt=\"gurdurr\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gurdurr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gurdurr.gif\" alt=\"gurdurr\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gurdurr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gurdurr.gif\" alt=\"gurdurr\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 534,
    "name": "Conkeldurr",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 105,
      "Attack": 140,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/conkeldurr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/conkeldurr.gif\" alt=\"conkeldurr\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/conkeldurr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/conkeldurr.gif\" alt=\"conkeldurr\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/conkeldurr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/conkeldurr.gif\" alt=\"conkeldurr\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/conkeldurr\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/conkeldurr.gif\" alt=\"conkeldurr\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 535,
    "name": "Tympole",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 64
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tympole\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tympole.gif\" alt=\"tympole\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tympole\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tympole.gif\" alt=\"tympole\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tympole\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tympole.gif\" alt=\"tympole\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tympole\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tympole.gif\" alt=\"tympole\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 536,
    "name": "Palpitoad",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 69
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/palpitoad\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/palpitoad.gif\" alt=\"palpitoad\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/palpitoad\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/palpitoad.gif\" alt=\"palpitoad\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/palpitoad\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/palpitoad.gif\" alt=\"palpitoad\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/palpitoad\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/palpitoad.gif\" alt=\"palpitoad\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 537,
    "name": "Seismitoad",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ground"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 105,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 74
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seismitoad\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/seismitoad.gif\" alt=\"seismitoad\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seismitoad\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/seismitoad.gif\" alt=\"seismitoad\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seismitoad\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/seismitoad.gif\" alt=\"seismitoad\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/seismitoad\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/seismitoad.gif\" alt=\"seismitoad\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 538,
    "name": "Throh",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 120,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/throh\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/throh.gif\" alt=\"throh\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/throh\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/throh.gif\" alt=\"throh\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/throh\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/throh.gif\" alt=\"throh\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/throh\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/throh.gif\" alt=\"throh\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 539,
    "name": "Sawk",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 125,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 85
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sawk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sawk.gif\" alt=\"sawk\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sawk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sawk.gif\" alt=\"sawk\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sawk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sawk.gif\" alt=\"sawk\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sawk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sawk.gif\" alt=\"sawk\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 540,
    "name": "Sewaddle",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 53,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 42
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sewaddle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sewaddle.gif\" alt=\"sewaddle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sewaddle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sewaddle.gif\" alt=\"sewaddle\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sewaddle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sewaddle.gif\" alt=\"sewaddle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sewaddle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sewaddle.gif\" alt=\"sewaddle\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 541,
    "name": "Swadloon",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 63,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 42
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swadloon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/swadloon.gif\" alt=\"swadloon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swadloon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/swadloon.gif\" alt=\"swadloon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swadloon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/swadloon.gif\" alt=\"swadloon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swadloon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/swadloon.gif\" alt=\"swadloon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 542,
    "name": "Leavanny",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 103,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 92
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/leavanny\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/leavanny.gif\" alt=\"leavanny\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/leavanny\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/leavanny.gif\" alt=\"leavanny\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/leavanny\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/leavanny.gif\" alt=\"leavanny\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/leavanny\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/leavanny.gif\" alt=\"leavanny\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 543,
    "name": "Venipede",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 30,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 59,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 39,
      "Speed": 57
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venipede\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/venipede.gif\" alt=\"venipede\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venipede\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/venipede.gif\" alt=\"venipede\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venipede\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/venipede.gif\" alt=\"venipede\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/venipede\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/venipede.gif\" alt=\"venipede\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 544,
    "name": "Whirlipede",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 99,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 79,
      "Speed": 47
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whirlipede\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/whirlipede.gif\" alt=\"whirlipede\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whirlipede\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/whirlipede.gif\" alt=\"whirlipede\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whirlipede\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/whirlipede.gif\" alt=\"whirlipede\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whirlipede\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/whirlipede.gif\" alt=\"whirlipede\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 545,
    "name": "Scolipede",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 89,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 69,
      "Speed": 112
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scolipede\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/scolipede.gif\" alt=\"scolipede\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scolipede\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/scolipede.gif\" alt=\"scolipede\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scolipede\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/scolipede.gif\" alt=\"scolipede\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scolipede\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/scolipede.gif\" alt=\"scolipede\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 546,
    "name": "Cottonee",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 27,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 37,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 66
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cottonee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cottonee.gif\" alt=\"cottonee\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cottonee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cottonee.gif\" alt=\"cottonee\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cottonee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cottonee.gif\" alt=\"cottonee\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cottonee\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cottonee.gif\" alt=\"cottonee\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 547,
    "name": "Whimsicott",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Fairy"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 67,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 77,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 116
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whimsicott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/whimsicott.gif\" alt=\"whimsicott\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whimsicott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/whimsicott.gif\" alt=\"whimsicott\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whimsicott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/whimsicott.gif\" alt=\"whimsicott\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/whimsicott\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/whimsicott.gif\" alt=\"whimsicott\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 548,
    "name": "Petilil",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 35,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/petilil\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/petilil.gif\" alt=\"petilil\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/petilil\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/petilil.gif\" alt=\"petilil\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/petilil\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/petilil.gif\" alt=\"petilil\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/petilil\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/petilil.gif\" alt=\"petilil\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 549,
    "name": "Lilligant",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 110,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lilligant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lilligant.gif\" alt=\"lilligant\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lilligant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lilligant.gif\" alt=\"lilligant\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lilligant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lilligant.gif\" alt=\"lilligant\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lilligant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lilligant.gif\" alt=\"lilligant\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 550,
    "name": "Basculin",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 92,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 98
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/basculin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/basculin.gif\" alt=\"basculin\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/basculin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/basculin.gif\" alt=\"basculin\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/basculin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/basculin.gif\" alt=\"basculin\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/basculin\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/basculin.gif\" alt=\"basculin\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 551,
    "name": "Sandile",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 72,
      "Defense": 35,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sandile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sandile.gif\" alt=\"sandile\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sandile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sandile.gif\" alt=\"sandile\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sandile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sandile.gif\" alt=\"sandile\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sandile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sandile.gif\" alt=\"sandile\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 552,
    "name": "Krokorok",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 82,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 74
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/krokorok\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/krokorok.gif\" alt=\"krokorok\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/krokorok\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/krokorok.gif\" alt=\"krokorok\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/krokorok\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/krokorok.gif\" alt=\"krokorok\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/krokorok\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/krokorok.gif\" alt=\"krokorok\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 553,
    "name": "Krookodile",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 117,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 92
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/krookodile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/krookodile.gif\" alt=\"krookodile\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/krookodile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/krookodile.gif\" alt=\"krookodile\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/krookodile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/krookodile.gif\" alt=\"krookodile\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/krookodile\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/krookodile.gif\" alt=\"krookodile\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 554,
    "name": "Darumaka",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 15,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/darumaka\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/darumaka.gif\" alt=\"darumaka\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/darumaka\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/darumaka.gif\" alt=\"darumaka\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/darumaka\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/darumaka.gif\" alt=\"darumaka\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/darumaka\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/darumaka.gif\" alt=\"darumaka\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 555,
    "name": "Darmanitan",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 105,
      "Attack": 140,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/darmanitan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/darmanitan.gif\" alt=\"darmanitan\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/darmanitan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/darmanitan.gif\" alt=\"darmanitan\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/darmanitan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/darmanitan.gif\" alt=\"darmanitan\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/darmanitan\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/darmanitan.gif\" alt=\"darmanitan\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 556,
    "name": "Maractus",
    "type": [
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 86,
      "Defense": 67,
      "Sp. Attack": 106,
      "Sp. Defense": 67,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/maractus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/maractus.gif\" alt=\"maractus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/maractus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/maractus.gif\" alt=\"maractus\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/maractus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/maractus.gif\" alt=\"maractus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/maractus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/maractus.gif\" alt=\"maractus\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 557,
    "name": "Dwebble",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 35,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dwebble\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/dwebble.gif\" alt=\"dwebble\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dwebble\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/dwebble.gif\" alt=\"dwebble\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dwebble\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/dwebble.gif\" alt=\"dwebble\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/dwebble\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/dwebble.gif\" alt=\"dwebble\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 558,
    "name": "Crustle",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 125,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/crustle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/crustle.gif\" alt=\"crustle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/crustle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/crustle.gif\" alt=\"crustle\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/crustle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/crustle.gif\" alt=\"crustle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/crustle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/crustle.gif\" alt=\"crustle\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 559,
    "name": "Scraggy",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 48
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scraggy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/scraggy.gif\" alt=\"scraggy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scraggy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/scraggy.gif\" alt=\"scraggy\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scraggy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/scraggy.gif\" alt=\"scraggy\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scraggy\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/scraggy.gif\" alt=\"scraggy\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 560,
    "name": "Scrafty",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 115,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 115,
      "Speed": 58
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scrafty\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/scrafty.gif\" alt=\"scrafty\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scrafty\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/scrafty.gif\" alt=\"scrafty\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scrafty\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/scrafty.gif\" alt=\"scrafty\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/scrafty\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/scrafty.gif\" alt=\"scrafty\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 561,
    "name": "Sigilyph",
    "type": [
      "Psychic",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 72,
      "Attack": 58,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 103,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 97
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sigilyph\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sigilyph.gif\" alt=\"sigilyph\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sigilyph\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sigilyph.gif\" alt=\"sigilyph\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sigilyph\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sigilyph.gif\" alt=\"sigilyph\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sigilyph\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sigilyph.gif\" alt=\"sigilyph\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 562,
    "name": "Yamask",
    "type": [
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 38,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/yamask\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/yamask.gif\" alt=\"yamask\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/yamask\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/yamask.gif\" alt=\"yamask\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/yamask\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/yamask.gif\" alt=\"yamask\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/yamask\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/yamask.gif\" alt=\"yamask\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 563,
    "name": "Cofagrigus",
    "type": [
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 58,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 145,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 105,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cofagrigus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cofagrigus.gif\" alt=\"cofagrigus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cofagrigus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cofagrigus.gif\" alt=\"cofagrigus\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cofagrigus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cofagrigus.gif\" alt=\"cofagrigus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cofagrigus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cofagrigus.gif\" alt=\"cofagrigus\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 564,
    "name": "Tirtouga",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 54,
      "Attack": 78,
      "Defense": 103,
      "Sp. Attack": 53,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 22
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tirtouga\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tirtouga.gif\" alt=\"tirtouga\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tirtouga\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tirtouga.gif\" alt=\"tirtouga\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tirtouga\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tirtouga.gif\" alt=\"tirtouga\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tirtouga\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tirtouga.gif\" alt=\"tirtouga\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 565,
    "name": "Carracosta",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 74,
      "Attack": 108,
      "Defense": 133,
      "Sp. Attack": 83,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 32
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/carracosta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/carracosta.gif\" alt=\"carracosta\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/carracosta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/carracosta.gif\" alt=\"carracosta\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/carracosta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/carracosta.gif\" alt=\"carracosta\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/carracosta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/carracosta.gif\" alt=\"carracosta\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 566,
    "name": "Archen",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 112,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 74,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/archen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/archen.gif\" alt=\"archen\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/archen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/archen.gif\" alt=\"archen\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/archen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/archen.gif\" alt=\"archen\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/archen\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/archen.gif\" alt=\"archen\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 567,
    "name": "Archeops",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 140,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 112,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 110
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/archeops\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/archeops.gif\" alt=\"archeops\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/archeops\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/archeops.gif\" alt=\"archeops\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/archeops\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/archeops.gif\" alt=\"archeops\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/archeops\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/archeops.gif\" alt=\"archeops\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 568,
    "name": "Trubbish",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 62,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 62,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/trubbish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/trubbish.gif\" alt=\"trubbish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/trubbish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/trubbish.gif\" alt=\"trubbish\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/trubbish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/trubbish.gif\" alt=\"trubbish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/trubbish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/trubbish.gif\" alt=\"trubbish\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 569,
    "name": "Garbodor",
    "type": [
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 82,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 82,
      "Speed": 75
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/garbodor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/garbodor.gif\" alt=\"garbodor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/garbodor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/garbodor.gif\" alt=\"garbodor\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/garbodor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/garbodor.gif\" alt=\"garbodor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/garbodor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/garbodor.gif\" alt=\"garbodor\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 570,
    "name": "Zorua",
    "type": [
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zorua\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/zorua.gif\" alt=\"zorua\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zorua\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/zorua.gif\" alt=\"zorua\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zorua\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/zorua.gif\" alt=\"zorua\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zorua\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/zorua.gif\" alt=\"zorua\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 571,
    "name": "Zoroark",
    "type": [
      "Dark"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 120,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 105
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zoroark\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/zoroark.gif\" alt=\"zoroark\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zoroark\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/zoroark.gif\" alt=\"zoroark\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zoroark\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/zoroark.gif\" alt=\"zoroark\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zoroark\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/zoroark.gif\" alt=\"zoroark\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 572,
    "name": "Minccino",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 75
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/minccino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/minccino.gif\" alt=\"minccino\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/minccino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/minccino.gif\" alt=\"minccino\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/minccino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/minccino.gif\" alt=\"minccino\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/minccino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/minccino.gif\" alt=\"minccino\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 573,
    "name": "Cinccino",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 115
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cinccino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cinccino.gif\" alt=\"cinccino\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cinccino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cinccino.gif\" alt=\"cinccino\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cinccino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cinccino.gif\" alt=\"cinccino\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cinccino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cinccino.gif\" alt=\"cinccino\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 574,
    "name": "Gothita",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 45
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gothita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gothita.gif\" alt=\"gothita\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gothita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gothita.gif\" alt=\"gothita\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gothita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gothita.gif\" alt=\"gothita\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gothita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gothita.gif\" alt=\"gothita\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 575,
    "name": "Gothorita",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 45,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gothorita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gothorita.gif\" alt=\"gothorita\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gothorita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gothorita.gif\" alt=\"gothorita\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gothorita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gothorita.gif\" alt=\"gothorita\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gothorita\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gothorita.gif\" alt=\"gothorita\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 576,
    "name": "Gothitelle",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 110,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gothitelle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/gothitelle.gif\" alt=\"gothitelle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gothitelle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/gothitelle.gif\" alt=\"gothitelle\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gothitelle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/gothitelle.gif\" alt=\"gothitelle\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/gothitelle\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/gothitelle.gif\" alt=\"gothitelle\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 577,
    "name": "Solosis",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/solosis\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/solosis.gif\" alt=\"solosis\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/solosis\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/solosis.gif\" alt=\"solosis\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/solosis\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/solosis.gif\" alt=\"solosis\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/solosis\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/solosis.gif\" alt=\"solosis\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 578,
    "name": "Duosion",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/duosion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/duosion.gif\" alt=\"duosion\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/duosion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/duosion.gif\" alt=\"duosion\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/duosion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/duosion.gif\" alt=\"duosion\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/duosion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/duosion.gif\" alt=\"duosion\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 579,
    "name": "Reuniclus",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 110,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/reuniclus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/reuniclus.gif\" alt=\"reuniclus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/reuniclus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/reuniclus.gif\" alt=\"reuniclus\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/reuniclus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/reuniclus.gif\" alt=\"reuniclus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/reuniclus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/reuniclus.gif\" alt=\"reuniclus\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 580,
    "name": "Ducklett",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 62,
      "Attack": 44,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 44,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ducklett\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ducklett.gif\" alt=\"ducklett\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ducklett\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ducklett.gif\" alt=\"ducklett\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ducklett\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ducklett.gif\" alt=\"ducklett\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ducklett\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ducklett.gif\" alt=\"ducklett\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 581,
    "name": "Swanna",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 87,
      "Defense": 63,
      "Sp. Attack": 87,
      "Sp. Defense": 63,
      "Speed": 98
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swanna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/swanna.gif\" alt=\"swanna\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swanna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/swanna.gif\" alt=\"swanna\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swanna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/swanna.gif\" alt=\"swanna\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/swanna\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/swanna.gif\" alt=\"swanna\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 582,
    "name": "Vanillite",
    "type": [
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 36,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 44
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vanillite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/vanillite.gif\" alt=\"vanillite\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vanillite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/vanillite.gif\" alt=\"vanillite\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vanillite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/vanillite.gif\" alt=\"vanillite\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vanillite\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/vanillite.gif\" alt=\"vanillite\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 583,
    "name": "Vanillish",
    "type": [
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 51,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 80,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 59
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vanillish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/vanillish.gif\" alt=\"vanillish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vanillish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/vanillish.gif\" alt=\"vanillish\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vanillish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/vanillish.gif\" alt=\"vanillish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vanillish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/vanillish.gif\" alt=\"vanillish\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 584,
    "name": "Vanilluxe",
    "type": [
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 71,
      "Attack": 95,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 110,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 79
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vanilluxe\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/vanilluxe.gif\" alt=\"vanilluxe\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vanilluxe\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/vanilluxe.gif\" alt=\"vanilluxe\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vanilluxe\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/vanilluxe.gif\" alt=\"vanilluxe\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vanilluxe\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/vanilluxe.gif\" alt=\"vanilluxe\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 585,
    "name": "Deerling",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 75
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/deerling\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/deerling.gif\" alt=\"deerling\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/deerling\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/deerling.gif\" alt=\"deerling\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/deerling\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/deerling.gif\" alt=\"deerling\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/deerling\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/deerling.gif\" alt=\"deerling\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 586,
    "name": "Sawsbuck",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sawsbuck\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/sawsbuck.gif\" alt=\"sawsbuck\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sawsbuck\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/sawsbuck.gif\" alt=\"sawsbuck\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sawsbuck\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/sawsbuck.gif\" alt=\"sawsbuck\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/sawsbuck\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/sawsbuck.gif\" alt=\"sawsbuck\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 587,
    "name": "Emolga",
    "type": [
      "Electric",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 103
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/emolga\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/emolga.gif\" alt=\"emolga\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/emolga\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/emolga.gif\" alt=\"emolga\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/emolga\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/emolga.gif\" alt=\"emolga\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/emolga\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/emolga.gif\" alt=\"emolga\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 588,
    "name": "Karrablast",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/karrablast\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/karrablast.gif\" alt=\"karrablast\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/karrablast\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/karrablast.gif\" alt=\"karrablast\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/karrablast\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/karrablast.gif\" alt=\"karrablast\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/karrablast\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/karrablast.gif\" alt=\"karrablast\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 589,
    "name": "Escavalier",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 135,
      "Defense": 105,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 105,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/escavalier\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/escavalier.gif\" alt=\"escavalier\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/escavalier\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/escavalier.gif\" alt=\"escavalier\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/escavalier\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/escavalier.gif\" alt=\"escavalier\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/escavalier\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/escavalier.gif\" alt=\"escavalier\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 590,
    "name": "Foongus",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 69,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 45,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 15
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/foongus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/foongus.gif\" alt=\"foongus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/foongus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/foongus.gif\" alt=\"foongus\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/foongus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/foongus.gif\" alt=\"foongus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/foongus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/foongus.gif\" alt=\"foongus\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 591,
    "name": "Amoonguss",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 114,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/amoonguss\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/amoonguss.gif\" alt=\"amoonguss\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/amoonguss\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/amoonguss.gif\" alt=\"amoonguss\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/amoonguss\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/amoonguss.gif\" alt=\"amoonguss\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/amoonguss\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/amoonguss.gif\" alt=\"amoonguss\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 592,
    "name": "Frillish",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/frillish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/frillish.gif\" alt=\"frillish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/frillish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/frillish.gif\" alt=\"frillish\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/frillish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/frillish.gif\" alt=\"frillish\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/frillish\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/frillish.gif\" alt=\"frillish\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 593,
    "name": "Jellicent",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 105,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jellicent\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/jellicent.gif\" alt=\"jellicent\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jellicent\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/jellicent.gif\" alt=\"jellicent\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jellicent\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/jellicent.gif\" alt=\"jellicent\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/jellicent\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/jellicent.gif\" alt=\"jellicent\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 594,
    "name": "Alomomola",
    "type": [
      "Water"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 165,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 45,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/alomomola\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/alomomola.gif\" alt=\"alomomola\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/alomomola\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/alomomola.gif\" alt=\"alomomola\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/alomomola\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/alomomola.gif\" alt=\"alomomola\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/alomomola\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/alomomola.gif\" alt=\"alomomola\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 595,
    "name": "Joltik",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 47,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 57,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/joltik\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/joltik.gif\" alt=\"joltik\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/joltik\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/joltik.gif\" alt=\"joltik\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/joltik\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/joltik.gif\" alt=\"joltik\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/joltik\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/joltik.gif\" alt=\"joltik\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 596,
    "name": "Galvantula",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 77,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 97,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 108
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/galvantula\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/galvantula.gif\" alt=\"galvantula\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/galvantula\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/galvantula.gif\" alt=\"galvantula\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/galvantula\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/galvantula.gif\" alt=\"galvantula\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/galvantula\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/galvantula.gif\" alt=\"galvantula\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 597,
    "name": "Ferroseed",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 44,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 91,
      "Sp. Attack": 24,
      "Sp. Defense": 86,
      "Speed": 10
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ferroseed\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ferroseed.gif\" alt=\"ferroseed\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ferroseed\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ferroseed.gif\" alt=\"ferroseed\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ferroseed\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ferroseed.gif\" alt=\"ferroseed\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ferroseed\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ferroseed.gif\" alt=\"ferroseed\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 598,
    "name": "Ferrothorn",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 74,
      "Attack": 94,
      "Defense": 131,
      "Sp. Attack": 54,
      "Sp. Defense": 116,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ferrothorn\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/ferrothorn.gif\" alt=\"ferrothorn\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ferrothorn\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/ferrothorn.gif\" alt=\"ferrothorn\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ferrothorn\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/ferrothorn.gif\" alt=\"ferrothorn\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/ferrothorn\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/ferrothorn.gif\" alt=\"ferrothorn\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 599,
    "name": "Klink",
    "type": [
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 40,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/klink\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/klink.gif\" alt=\"klink\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/klink\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/klink.gif\" alt=\"klink\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/klink\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/klink.gif\" alt=\"klink\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/klink\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/klink.gif\" alt=\"klink\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 600,
    "name": "Klang",
    "type": [
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 80,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/klang\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/klang.gif\" alt=\"klang\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/klang\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/klang.gif\" alt=\"klang\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/klang\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/klang.gif\" alt=\"klang\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/klang\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/klang.gif\" alt=\"klang\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 601,
    "name": "Klinklang",
    "type": [
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 100,
      "Defense": 115,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 85,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/klinklang\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/klinklang.gif\" alt=\"klinklang\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/klinklang\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/klinklang.gif\" alt=\"klinklang\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/klinklang\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/klinklang.gif\" alt=\"klinklang\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/klinklang\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/klinklang.gif\" alt=\"klinklang\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 602,
    "name": "Tynamo",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 35,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tynamo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tynamo.gif\" alt=\"tynamo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tynamo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tynamo.gif\" alt=\"tynamo\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tynamo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tynamo.gif\" alt=\"tynamo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tynamo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tynamo.gif\" alt=\"tynamo\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 603,
    "name": "Eelektrik",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 75,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/eelektrik\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/eelektrik.gif\" alt=\"eelektrik\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/eelektrik\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/eelektrik.gif\" alt=\"eelektrik\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/eelektrik\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/eelektrik.gif\" alt=\"eelektrik\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/eelektrik\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/eelektrik.gif\" alt=\"eelektrik\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 604,
    "name": "Eelektross",
    "type": [
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 115,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/eelektross\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/eelektross.gif\" alt=\"eelektross\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/eelektross\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/eelektross.gif\" alt=\"eelektross\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/eelektross\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/eelektross.gif\" alt=\"eelektross\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/eelektross\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/eelektross.gif\" alt=\"eelektross\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 605,
    "name": "Elgyem",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 85,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 30
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/elgyem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/elgyem.gif\" alt=\"elgyem\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/elgyem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/elgyem.gif\" alt=\"elgyem\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/elgyem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/elgyem.gif\" alt=\"elgyem\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/elgyem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/elgyem.gif\" alt=\"elgyem\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 606,
    "name": "Beheeyem",
    "type": [
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 75,
      "Attack": 75,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beheeyem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/beheeyem.gif\" alt=\"beheeyem\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beheeyem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/beheeyem.gif\" alt=\"beheeyem\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beheeyem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/beheeyem.gif\" alt=\"beheeyem\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beheeyem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/beheeyem.gif\" alt=\"beheeyem\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 607,
    "name": "Litwick",
    "type": [
      "Ghost",
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 30,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 20
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/litwick\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/litwick.gif\" alt=\"litwick\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/litwick\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/litwick.gif\" alt=\"litwick\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/litwick\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/litwick.gif\" alt=\"litwick\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/litwick\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/litwick.gif\" alt=\"litwick\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 608,
    "name": "Lampent",
    "type": [
      "Ghost",
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lampent\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/lampent.gif\" alt=\"lampent\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lampent\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/lampent.gif\" alt=\"lampent\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lampent\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/lampent.gif\" alt=\"lampent\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/lampent\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/lampent.gif\" alt=\"lampent\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 609,
    "name": "Chandelure",
    "type": [
      "Ghost",
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 60,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 145,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chandelure\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/chandelure.gif\" alt=\"chandelure\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chandelure\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/chandelure.gif\" alt=\"chandelure\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chandelure\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/chandelure.gif\" alt=\"chandelure\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/chandelure\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/chandelure.gif\" alt=\"chandelure\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 610,
    "name": "Axew",
    "type": [
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 46,
      "Attack": 87,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 30,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 57
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/axew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/axew.gif\" alt=\"axew\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/axew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/axew.gif\" alt=\"axew\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/axew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/axew.gif\" alt=\"axew\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/axew\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/axew.gif\" alt=\"axew\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 611,
    "name": "Fraxure",
    "type": [
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 66,
      "Attack": 117,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 67
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/fraxure\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/fraxure.gif\" alt=\"fraxure\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/fraxure\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/fraxure.gif\" alt=\"fraxure\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/fraxure\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/fraxure.gif\" alt=\"fraxure\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/fraxure\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/fraxure.gif\" alt=\"fraxure\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 612,
    "name": "Haxorus",
    "type": [
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 76,
      "Attack": 147,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 97
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/haxorus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/haxorus.gif\" alt=\"haxorus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/haxorus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/haxorus.gif\" alt=\"haxorus\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/haxorus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/haxorus.gif\" alt=\"haxorus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/haxorus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/haxorus.gif\" alt=\"haxorus\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 613,
    "name": "Cubchoo",
    "type": [
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 40
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cubchoo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cubchoo.gif\" alt=\"cubchoo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cubchoo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cubchoo.gif\" alt=\"cubchoo\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cubchoo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cubchoo.gif\" alt=\"cubchoo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cubchoo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cubchoo.gif\" alt=\"cubchoo\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 614,
    "name": "Beartic",
    "type": [
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 70,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 50
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beartic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/beartic.gif\" alt=\"beartic\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beartic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/beartic.gif\" alt=\"beartic\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beartic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/beartic.gif\" alt=\"beartic\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/beartic\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/beartic.gif\" alt=\"beartic\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 615,
    "name": "Cryogonal",
    "type": [
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 50,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 135,
      "Speed": 105
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cryogonal\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cryogonal.gif\" alt=\"cryogonal\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cryogonal\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cryogonal.gif\" alt=\"cryogonal\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cryogonal\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cryogonal.gif\" alt=\"cryogonal\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cryogonal\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cryogonal.gif\" alt=\"cryogonal\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 616,
    "name": "Shelmet",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 50,
      "Attack": 40,
      "Defense": 85,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 25
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shelmet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/shelmet.gif\" alt=\"shelmet\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shelmet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/shelmet.gif\" alt=\"shelmet\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shelmet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/shelmet.gif\" alt=\"shelmet\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/shelmet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/shelmet.gif\" alt=\"shelmet\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 617,
    "name": "Accelgor",
    "type": [
      "Bug"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 80,
      "Attack": 70,
      "Defense": 40,
      "Sp. Attack": 100,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 145
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/accelgor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/accelgor.gif\" alt=\"accelgor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/accelgor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/accelgor.gif\" alt=\"accelgor\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/accelgor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/accelgor.gif\" alt=\"accelgor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/accelgor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/accelgor.gif\" alt=\"accelgor\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 618,
    "name": "Stunfisk",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 109,
      "Attack": 66,
      "Defense": 84,
      "Sp. Attack": 81,
      "Sp. Defense": 99,
      "Speed": 32
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stunfisk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/stunfisk.gif\" alt=\"stunfisk\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stunfisk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/stunfisk.gif\" alt=\"stunfisk\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stunfisk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/stunfisk.gif\" alt=\"stunfisk\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/stunfisk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/stunfisk.gif\" alt=\"stunfisk\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 619,
    "name": "Mienfoo",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mienfoo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mienfoo.gif\" alt=\"mienfoo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mienfoo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mienfoo.gif\" alt=\"mienfoo\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mienfoo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mienfoo.gif\" alt=\"mienfoo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mienfoo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mienfoo.gif\" alt=\"mienfoo\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 620,
    "name": "Mienshao",
    "type": [
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 125,
      "Defense": 60,
      "Sp. Attack": 95,
      "Sp. Defense": 60,
      "Speed": 105
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mienshao\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mienshao.gif\" alt=\"mienshao\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mienshao\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mienshao.gif\" alt=\"mienshao\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mienshao\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mienshao.gif\" alt=\"mienshao\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mienshao\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mienshao.gif\" alt=\"mienshao\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 621,
    "name": "Druddigon",
    "type": [
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 77,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 48
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/druddigon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/druddigon.gif\" alt=\"druddigon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/druddigon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/druddigon.gif\" alt=\"druddigon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/druddigon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/druddigon.gif\" alt=\"druddigon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/druddigon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/druddigon.gif\" alt=\"druddigon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 622,
    "name": "Golett",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 59,
      "Attack": 74,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 35,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 35
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golett\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/golett.gif\" alt=\"golett\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golett\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/golett.gif\" alt=\"golett\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golett\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/golett.gif\" alt=\"golett\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golett\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/golett.gif\" alt=\"golett\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 623,
    "name": "Golurk",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Ghost"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 89,
      "Attack": 124,
      "Defense": 80,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golurk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/golurk.gif\" alt=\"golurk\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golurk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/golurk.gif\" alt=\"golurk\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golurk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/golurk.gif\" alt=\"golurk\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/golurk\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/golurk.gif\" alt=\"golurk\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 624,
    "name": "Pawniard",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 45,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 40,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pawniard\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/pawniard.gif\" alt=\"pawniard\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pawniard\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/pawniard.gif\" alt=\"pawniard\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pawniard\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/pawniard.gif\" alt=\"pawniard\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/pawniard\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/pawniard.gif\" alt=\"pawniard\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 625,
    "name": "Bisharp",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 65,
      "Attack": 125,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 60,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 70
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bisharp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bisharp.gif\" alt=\"bisharp\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bisharp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bisharp.gif\" alt=\"bisharp\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bisharp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bisharp.gif\" alt=\"bisharp\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bisharp\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bisharp.gif\" alt=\"bisharp\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 626,
    "name": "Bouffalant",
    "type": [
      "Normal"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 95,
      "Attack": 110,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 40,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 55
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bouffalant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/bouffalant.gif\" alt=\"bouffalant\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bouffalant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/bouffalant.gif\" alt=\"bouffalant\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bouffalant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/bouffalant.gif\" alt=\"bouffalant\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/bouffalant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/bouffalant.gif\" alt=\"bouffalant\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 627,
    "name": "Rufflet",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 83,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 37,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rufflet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/rufflet.gif\" alt=\"rufflet\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rufflet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/rufflet.gif\" alt=\"rufflet\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rufflet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/rufflet.gif\" alt=\"rufflet\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/rufflet\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/rufflet.gif\" alt=\"rufflet\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 628,
    "name": "Braviary",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 123,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 57,
      "Sp. Defense": 75,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/braviary\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/braviary.gif\" alt=\"braviary\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/braviary\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/braviary.gif\" alt=\"braviary\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/braviary\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/braviary.gif\" alt=\"braviary\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/braviary\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/braviary.gif\" alt=\"braviary\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 629,
    "name": "Vullaby",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 70,
      "Attack": 55,
      "Defense": 75,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 65,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vullaby\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/vullaby.gif\" alt=\"vullaby\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vullaby\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/vullaby.gif\" alt=\"vullaby\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vullaby\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/vullaby.gif\" alt=\"vullaby\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/vullaby\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/vullaby.gif\" alt=\"vullaby\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 630,
    "name": "Mandibuzz",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 110,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 105,
      "Sp. Attack": 55,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 80
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mandibuzz\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/mandibuzz.gif\" alt=\"mandibuzz\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mandibuzz\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/mandibuzz.gif\" alt=\"mandibuzz\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mandibuzz\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/mandibuzz.gif\" alt=\"mandibuzz\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/mandibuzz\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/mandibuzz.gif\" alt=\"mandibuzz\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 631,
    "name": "Heatmor",
    "type": [
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 97,
      "Defense": 66,
      "Sp. Attack": 105,
      "Sp. Defense": 66,
      "Speed": 65
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/heatmor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/heatmor.gif\" alt=\"heatmor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/heatmor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/heatmor.gif\" alt=\"heatmor\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/heatmor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/heatmor.gif\" alt=\"heatmor\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/heatmor\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/heatmor.gif\" alt=\"heatmor\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 632,
    "name": "Durant",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 58,
      "Attack": 109,
      "Defense": 112,
      "Sp. Attack": 48,
      "Sp. Defense": 48,
      "Speed": 109
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/durant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/durant.gif\" alt=\"durant\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/durant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/durant.gif\" alt=\"durant\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/durant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/durant.gif\" alt=\"durant\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/durant\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/durant.gif\" alt=\"durant\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 633,
    "name": "Deino",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 52,
      "Attack": 65,
      "Defense": 50,
      "Sp. Attack": 45,
      "Sp. Defense": 50,
      "Speed": 38
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/deino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/deino.gif\" alt=\"deino\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/deino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/deino.gif\" alt=\"deino\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/deino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/deino.gif\" alt=\"deino\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/deino\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/deino.gif\" alt=\"deino\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 634,
    "name": "Zweilous",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 72,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 65,
      "Sp. Defense": 70,
      "Speed": 58
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zweilous\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/zweilous.gif\" alt=\"zweilous\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zweilous\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/zweilous.gif\" alt=\"zweilous\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zweilous\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/zweilous.gif\" alt=\"zweilous\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zweilous\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/zweilous.gif\" alt=\"zweilous\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 635,
    "name": "Hydreigon",
    "type": [
      "Dark",
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 92,
      "Attack": 105,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 98
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hydreigon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/hydreigon.gif\" alt=\"hydreigon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hydreigon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/hydreigon.gif\" alt=\"hydreigon\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hydreigon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/hydreigon.gif\" alt=\"hydreigon\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/hydreigon\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/hydreigon.gif\" alt=\"hydreigon\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 636,
    "name": "Larvesta",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 55,
      "Attack": 85,
      "Defense": 55,
      "Sp. Attack": 50,
      "Sp. Defense": 55,
      "Speed": 60
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/larvesta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/larvesta.gif\" alt=\"larvesta\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/larvesta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/larvesta.gif\" alt=\"larvesta\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/larvesta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/larvesta.gif\" alt=\"larvesta\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/larvesta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/larvesta.gif\" alt=\"larvesta\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 637,
    "name": "Volcarona",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 85,
      "Attack": 60,
      "Defense": 65,
      "Sp. Attack": 135,
      "Sp. Defense": 105,
      "Speed": 100
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/volcarona\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/volcarona.gif\" alt=\"volcarona\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/volcarona\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/volcarona.gif\" alt=\"volcarona\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/volcarona\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/volcarona.gif\" alt=\"volcarona\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/volcarona\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/volcarona.gif\" alt=\"volcarona\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 638,
    "name": "Cobalion",
    "type": [
      "Steel",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 91,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 129,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 72,
      "Speed": 108
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cobalion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/cobalion.gif\" alt=\"cobalion\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cobalion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/cobalion.gif\" alt=\"cobalion\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cobalion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/cobalion.gif\" alt=\"cobalion\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/cobalion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/cobalion.gif\" alt=\"cobalion\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 639,
    "name": "Terrakion",
    "type": [
      "Rock",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 91,
      "Attack": 129,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 72,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 108
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/terrakion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/terrakion.gif\" alt=\"terrakion\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/terrakion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/terrakion.gif\" alt=\"terrakion\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/terrakion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/terrakion.gif\" alt=\"terrakion\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/terrakion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/terrakion.gif\" alt=\"terrakion\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 640,
    "name": "Virizion",
    "type": [
      "Grass",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 91,
      "Attack": 90,
      "Defense": 72,
      "Sp. Attack": 90,
      "Sp. Defense": 129,
      "Speed": 108
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/virizion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/virizion.gif\" alt=\"virizion\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/virizion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/virizion.gif\" alt=\"virizion\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/virizion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/virizion.gif\" alt=\"virizion\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/virizion\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/virizion.gif\" alt=\"virizion\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 641,
    "name": "Tornadus",
    "type": [
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 79,
      "Attack": 115,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 111
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tornadus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/tornadus.gif\" alt=\"tornadus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tornadus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/tornadus.gif\" alt=\"tornadus\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tornadus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/tornadus.gif\" alt=\"tornadus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/tornadus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/tornadus.gif\" alt=\"tornadus\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 642,
    "name": "Thundurus",
    "type": [
      "Electric",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 79,
      "Attack": 115,
      "Defense": 70,
      "Sp. Attack": 125,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 111
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/thundurus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/thundurus.gif\" alt=\"thundurus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/thundurus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/thundurus.gif\" alt=\"thundurus\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/thundurus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/thundurus.gif\" alt=\"thundurus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/thundurus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/thundurus.gif\" alt=\"thundurus\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 643,
    "name": "Reshiram",
    "type": [
      "Dragon",
      "Fire"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 100,
      "Sp. Attack": 150,
      "Sp. Defense": 120,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/reshiram\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/reshiram.gif\" alt=\"reshiram\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/reshiram\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/reshiram.gif\" alt=\"reshiram\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/reshiram\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/reshiram.gif\" alt=\"reshiram\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/reshiram\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/reshiram.gif\" alt=\"reshiram\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 644,
    "name": "Zekrom",
    "type": [
      "Dragon",
      "Electric"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 150,
      "Defense": 120,
      "Sp. Attack": 120,
      "Sp. Defense": 100,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zekrom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/zekrom.gif\" alt=\"zekrom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zekrom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/zekrom.gif\" alt=\"zekrom\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zekrom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/zekrom.gif\" alt=\"zekrom\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/zekrom\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/zekrom.gif\" alt=\"zekrom\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 645,
    "name": "Landorus",
    "type": [
      "Ground",
      "Flying"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 89,
      "Attack": 125,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 115,
      "Sp. Defense": 80,
      "Speed": 101
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/landorus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/landorus.gif\" alt=\"landorus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/landorus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/landorus.gif\" alt=\"landorus\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/landorus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/landorus.gif\" alt=\"landorus\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/landorus\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/landorus.gif\" alt=\"landorus\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 646,
    "name": "Kyurem",
    "type": [
      "Dragon",
      "Ice"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 125,
      "Attack": 130,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 130,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 95
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kyurem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/kyurem.gif\" alt=\"kyurem\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kyurem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/kyurem.gif\" alt=\"kyurem\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kyurem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/kyurem.gif\" alt=\"kyurem\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/kyurem\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/kyurem.gif\" alt=\"kyurem\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 647,
    "name": "Keldeo",
    "type": [
      "Water",
      "Fighting"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 91,
      "Attack": 72,
      "Defense": 90,
      "Sp. Attack": 129,
      "Sp. Defense": 90,
      "Speed": 108
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/keldeo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/keldeo.gif\" alt=\"keldeo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/keldeo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/keldeo.gif\" alt=\"keldeo\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/keldeo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/keldeo.gif\" alt=\"keldeo\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/keldeo\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/keldeo.gif\" alt=\"keldeo\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 648,
    "name": "Meloetta",
    "type": [
      "Normal",
      "Psychic"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 100,
      "Attack": 77,
      "Defense": 77,
      "Sp. Attack": 128,
      "Sp. Defense": 128,
      "Speed": 90
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meloetta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/meloetta.gif\" alt=\"meloetta\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meloetta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/meloetta.gif\" alt=\"meloetta\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meloetta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/meloetta.gif\" alt=\"meloetta\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/meloetta\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/meloetta.gif\" alt=\"meloetta\"></a>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 649,
    "name": "Genesect",
    "type": [
      "Bug",
      "Steel"
    ],
    "base": {
      "HP": 71,
      "Attack": 120,
      "Defense": 95,
      "Sp. Attack": 120,
      "Sp. Defense": 95,
      "Speed": 99
    },
    "normal": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/genesect\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/normal/genesect.gif\" alt=\"genesect\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/genesect\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-normal/genesect.gif\" alt=\"genesect\"></a>"
    },
    "shiny": {
      "front": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/genesect\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/shiny/genesect.gif\" alt=\"genesect\"></a>",
      "back": "<a href=\"https://pokemondb.net/pokedex/genesect\"><img src=\"https://img.pokemondb.net/sprites/black-white/anim/back-shiny/genesect.gif\" alt=\"genesect\"></a>"
    }
  }
]